Look who we have here.
I've been expecting you,
the legendary Horu—
Excuse me.
I'm sure you would prefer Takanashi Hoshino.
What is it this time?
There's been a change of plans.
I'd like to once again extend an offer to you,
wielder of the strongest Mystic in Abydos.
Don't screw with me!
Come on, now. No need to get angry.
I am extending an offer you cannot possibly refuse.
I assure you will find this proposal quite fascinating.
We end today's segment
with a report from the Abydos district.
Despite the recent explosion,
the desert shows no signs of change.
This concludes our news for today.
We'll see you again tomorrow.
How did things end up like this?
Did you say something?
What I meant was, how many more
should I write, President Hina?
You've written about two hundred so far, right?
Weren't you the one who said you'd write a thousand?
What I meant was that I was so ashamed
I could write a thousand!
Less chatter, more writing.
Y-Yes, ma'am.
Incidentally, have you met
Hoshino from Abydos before?
No. I had done research on her
while I was in intelligence.
This was the first time I met her.
I see.
You sounded like you knew her well,
so I presumed you had met her before.
Takanashi Hoshino.
A true elite, a genius by all standards.
The intelligence division's analysis two years ago
listed her as a latent threat to Gehenna.
She certainly didn't give me that impression.
Ako, you should refrain from
making judgments based on appearances.
But...
She really did seem like
a completely different person.
In the past, she was extremely aggressive,
specialising in assault tactics.
Based on the reports, she struck me as a rough,
yet dangerously sharp individual.
Well, let's set her past aside for now.
Had we carelessly engaged Abydos,
we would have lost more than half our forces.
All because you jumped the gun, Ako.
I had analysed their combat capability,
but there was nothing like that in the report.
Well, she did just fall off the grid one day.
At some point, intelligence may have
stopped viewing her as a threat.
If you're curious, I recommend
digging through the old reports.
Ako. Those letters aren't going to write themselves.
Y-Yes, ma'am!
Takanashi Hoshino.
You were still in Abydos after all this time?
Um, where should I put this?
Oh, right, the crime against calligraphy
Aru poured all her talent into.
Just chuck it in the bin.
A-Are you sure?
That's the thing she made for calligraphy class, right?
Well, I guess she may wanna keep that anyway.
Miss Aru...
It's so obvious she doesn't wanna move.
I get it, but the Prefects
will be swarming this place soon.
And since we messed up,
the client'll want a piece of us too.
No sense crying over spilt milk.
Speaking of enemies, our little dispute
with Abydos ended up unresolved, huh?
Wh-What other option did we have?
We couldn't just turn around and attack
the very people who fought alongside us!
I see.
Outlaws have to know when to let go of the past.
Exactly!
So chin up and say goodbye to this old place.
Kayoko, what do we do with this?
Do we really need that?
Of course we do!
We have smartphones, though.
It's not about convenience. It's about atmosphere!
Oh, come on.
Isn't this retro design just right for an outlaw's office?
I-I think so, yes!
I-I mean...
I think it's cool.
I knew you'd understand, Haruka!
This isn't a step back. It's only a brief detour.
No matter how dire things seem now,
we'll be back in this office one day. Just you wait!
Why?
Because we're real, bona fide outlaws!
We're Problem Solver 68!
Tomorrow, we finally bid this place adieu.
Boss.
We didn't pay last month's rent,
so they want us out today.
Miss Aru.
Guess we're pitching tents tonight!
Wh-Wh-What?
What do you mean?!
That was the last box.
Cheer up, Aru.
This isn't the first time we've camped out.
We're just going back to how things used to be.
Going back...
No, we're not going back!
We're moving up!
Yeah!
Well then, where to?
Well, not like we have anywhere to go.
Should we go back to Gehenna?
Moving somewhere?
Um, you're Sunaookami Shiroko, right?
Yeah.
Wh-What are you doing here?
You're not here for a rematch, are you?
No.
I was biking in the area,
and I happened to see you.
U-Um...
About the other day...
Thank you very much for helping us!
A-And also, about the ramen shop...
That's different.
But you do seem like you're sorry.
You owe us one. How's that?
After all, you were the ones
who left that bag, right?
I-I have no idea what you mean!
I don't know anything about a bag filled with money!
In fact, I've never even heard of such a thing!
Aru, you know you gave the game away
by mentioning the money, right?
Y-You stole that money
when you robbed the bank, right?
We're not so desperate
that we'd claim it for ourselves.
Outlaws have standards, too!
Well, look who's sassy now.
I went ahead and delivered the bag to the boss.
I see. Thanks.
Where will you go?
Wherever there's clients in need of
Problem Solver 68's services!
Aru, we should get going.
R-Right.
We need to find a place to camp for tonight.
Don't want to?
I-I have no intention of acting like
I'm all chummy with you.
After all, I'm—
An outlaw, right?
Will I see you again?
W-Well, if that ramen shop ever opens again,
maybe we'll meet there again someday?
I'll be waiting.
Now, it's time for us to venture out ourselves!
Out where?
Into the sunset!
It's still the middle of the day.
Don't worry about the details. Let's go!
Hello!
We came to visit you, boss.
How are you feeling?
Aw, don't worry 'bout me.
'Tis but a scratch.
Rather, that was a mighty fine blast.
Sure glad no one 'sides me was caught up in it.
Well, yes, but...
Shiba Seki Ramen, your store...
Right. Sorry Serika,
but I can't hire you part-time anymore.
It's not about that, boss!
It's fine.
I was thinkin' 'bout closing up shop either way.
The closing date just came knockin' a bit early is all.
You were going to close?
Y'see, I received an eviction notice a while back.
A-An eviction notice? That shouldn't be possible!
Our school owns all the buildings in the Abydos district.
I see. So you girls didn't know, huh?
The buildings and the land stopped bein' the property
of the student council a few years ago.
But they're within the Abydos district.
Serika, did you know about this?
No, this is the first I've heard of it.
Does this mean there's another debt
Abydos had to pay off?
I was also unaware of this.
Then who does the property belong to now?!
Could it be the Kaiser Corporation?
That name does ring a bell.
But sorry. I just can't remember it well.
We should probably investigate this further.
Ayane, let me help out, too.
Me, too. I'll help however I can.
Sorry 'bout that. Seems things
have only gotten more complicated.
Don't worry about it.
This is our problem, not yours.
But enough about that.
Don't you dare retire on me, boss!
You got it?
Oh, uh... Yeah.
Oh, that reminds me.
There's somethin' under the bed.
Mind pulling it out real quick?
Here we are.
Do you know anythin' about this?
W-Well, I mean...
I suppose you could say that.
Isn't this...
Well, y'see, Shiroko came by
and dropped it off earlier.
Said she found it in front of
what little's left of my restaurant.
So obviously I got curious and opened it up.
And wouldn't ya know, it's stuffed full of cash!
Guessin' this ain't just a tip for good service, huh?
Wh-Who knows, maybe it is?
I'm sure it's from a well-meaning stranger!
That's right! I think it's perfectly fine
to use this money to rebuild your restaurant!
Yeah! I'm sure whoever left this behind
was touched by your ramen!
Y'all gotta be kiddin' me.
If that's true, I can't even tell ya
how happy that makes me.
All I want in life is to see my hungry customers
eatin' their fill of delicious ramen.
That's what kept me goin' all these years!
Everyone's waiting to have your ramen again.
So hurry and get better,
and then rebuild your restaurant!
And once that's done,
you'd better hire me again, boss.
You got it! Leave it to me!
The moment I'm back on my feet,
I'll feed ya all the ramen you can stomach!
Yeah! Looking forward to it!
Heya, Hoshino.
The weather's nice.
Out for a nap on the roof today?
Yeah, well, you know.
What about you, Teacher?
I was thinking of taking a little break myself.
You've been here for a good while now, huh?
Huh?
Now that you mention it, I guess you're right.
I gotta be honest, at first I thought
you were just another weirdo.
Turns out I'm pretty reliable after all, huh?
Oh, please. You're all over the place,
and you're constantly playing catch-up.
But y'know...
The Task Force seems
a lot happier now with you around.
I can't take credit for that. That's because
they got a clear direction for the future now.
Yeah, you could be right.
Serika no longer tries to do
everything on her own anymore.
Ayane's not looking down as much, I guess?
Nonomi laughs for herself now,
not just to make the others happy.
And as for Shiroko...
I think she's breathing easier now.
You're doing your best, too.
Everyone trusts in you.
This seasoned bird just wants to see
her fledgelings soar free through the skies.
Yeah.
Letting them soar free is the only way
they'll find happiness for themselves.
And that's why I have to continue forward.
What's that?
Man, I feel a lot better after hearing you say that.
Now I can really enjoy my nap!
And here I thought you were finally
being serious for once.
Hello, Arona.
Wait, where did my strawberry cake go?
And my banana cake?
Is this my punishment for trying to eat two at once?
Arona?
Just one bite would have been enough...
Wait, Teacher?!
I'll be sure to bring some cake next time.
Strawberry and banana, right?
I'm sorry you had to see that.
But thank you! I look forward to them!
What brings you here today?
Ah, there was something I wanted to ask.
Can you look into the Kaiser Corporation?
The Kaiser Corporation?
Looks like they're up to no good
in the Abydos desert.
Understood!
Is there anything else you'd like me
to look into in the meantime?
Hoshino...
Sorry?
No, that's all.
This is something I need to do on my own.
I'm their teacher, after all.
Are you sure?
Very well, if you say so.
Thank you. You're always a big help.
You can count on me!
I'm both the talented systems administrator
of the Shittim Chest and its main OS, after all.
And above all,
I'm your helpful personal assistant!
Now then. I wonder if everyone's back.
Hello, Teacher!
Welcome back, everyone.
How was the boss doing?
He was doing great, in both health and spirit!
He said he'll rebuild Shiba Seki Ramen soon, too.
I see. That's good to hear.
Yes, it is.
What's the matter?
We've actually run into another problem.
We were just about to dive into it.
Simply put, it seems that Abydos High
does not own the rights to this area.
What? Doesn't the land within
a school district belong to the school?
According to the boss, even the building
Shiba Seki Ramen was in
doesn't belong to Abydos High anymore.
Since when?
We don't know for sure,
but the boss said it was a few years ago.
So who owns it now?
The Kaiser Corporation.
It didn't start just recently.
This had been going on since before we ever met
Problem Solver 68 or the Helmet Gang.
We've been dancing to the tune
of Kaiser Corporation all along.
God, now I'm pissed!
W-Well, we won't know
for sure until the results come out.
We may be jumping to conclusions.
Feels like I can never get enough sleep
no matter how many naps I take these days.
Maybe I'm just getting old.
Oh!
Hey, take a look at that!
Doesn't that cloud look kinda like a whale?
Um, Hoshino?
Come on, it's right there! The big one!
You can't see it from all the way back there.
Come closer. I promise I won't bite.
S-Stop pushing me!
Excuse me? We're in the middle of
a serious conversation! This isn't the time for—
Come now, why don't we take a look too, Serika?
Y-You, too, Nonomi?
What's going on with everyone?
You mean that cloud right there?
I'd say it looks more like a dolphin than a whale.
What? Really?
I'm sure Hoshino means the cloud
above that one. Right, Hoshino?
When you put it that way,
the one under it does kinda look like a dolphin.
Then I guess that makes the one
underneath that one a jellyfish?
I don't remember jellyfish
looking quite like that.
There may be some kinds that do.
And now that we're on the topic,
let's all go to an aquarium together!
But...
We haven't found anything yet anyway, right?
Sitting around with a frown on our faces
won't change the outcome.
So in that case,
I'd like for us to at least smile while we wait.
And besides, Serika, there's
tons of jellyfish over at the aquarium.
They're so nice to look at.
All wiggly and squiggly!
Come on, won't you indulge me?
Just this once?
Fine, fine, I'll go. Happy?
I agree. A break every once in a while
may be just what we need.
Right! Breaks are important!
You're coming too, right, Teacher?
Huh?
What do you mean, "huh"? You busy?
I believe we need a teacher to chaperone us.
That's true. Sure, let's all go together!
I look forward to it!
We're gonna have so much fun!