Well, well
I have been waiting for you,
Horus of Dawn—
Or rather,
Miss Takanashi Hoshino
What do you want this time?
The situation's changed a bit
Once more,
I have a proposal for you, Hoshino—
or should I call you
"Abydos' Greatest Mystery?"
- Don't be ridiculous!
- Oh my?
Please calm down
I think you'll find my
offer difficult to refuse
(Contract)
It should be rather enticing, in fact
(The 177th Abydos Oasis Festival)
The sky blue archive!
I pedal on my bike seeking new sights
We'll break the monotony,
no longer trapped in place
Daydreaming on the rooftop,
gazing at a sky so blue
Those clouds like whales are always changing
We'll embrace a past that can't be altered
Sharing juice in this world made of sand
is a taste so divine
If I were here alone, here without all of you
I couldn't laugh, I couldn't cry
A fateful coterie
Even if the world's memories blow away
like grains of sand one day
The sky, sea, wind, and you,
our youth will never end
It's easy to see why we protect what we do
Because this is the only place where we belong
We'll wrap up
with some recent events
from the Abydos District
While there were reports of explosions,
(Clear skies!
Expect clouds next week!)
it's been business as usual
for the desert district
And that's the news for the day!
We'll see you tomorrow!
(Shiba Seki Ramen)
(Keep Out)
(Danger!)
How did I end up here?
Did you just say something?
Um, Head Prefect?
How much longer do
I have to do this for?
You're at around 200, yes?
Didn't you tell me you
would complete 1,000 pages?
Well, that was⋯
It was a metaphor for my deep remorse⋯!
Use your hands, not your mouth
I-I'll do my best
So, um,
are you well-acquainted
with Abydos' Hoshino?
No, I just investigated her when
I was on the Intelligence Committee
That was my first time
meeting her in person
I see
It's just, you spoke as if you knew her well
Takanashi Hoshino
She was hailed as a genius, An elite
The Intelligence Committee's
analysis two years ago identified
her as a potential threat
to Gehenna's security
She didn't give me that impression
Ako
Don't judge a book by its cover
But⋯she does seems a bit
different from two years ago
She's an aggressive frontliner,
so she was inherently combative in nature,
She had a vicious, cutthroat aura
Well, regardless,
if we hadn't retreated then,
most of the Prefect Team
would've been incapacitated
Ako, your lack of
preparation is to blame here
I thought my analysis of
their capabilities was flawless,
but I just didn't know⋯
Well, her name did stop appearing
in activity reports out of the blue
The Intelligence Committee
deemed her negligible after that
If you're curious, dig
through some old records
Ako, you've stopped writing
Oh, sorry!
Takanashi Hoshino
I didn't think she'd
still be in Abydos
Um⋯
(An Evil a Day)
Where should I put this?
Aru made that with her
esteemed calligraphy talents
Throw it in the trash pile
Are you sure?
It's just something she made
during calligraphy class
Well, knowing her, Boss might want it
Aru⋯
She's bummed about having to move
I get how she feels,
but the Prefect Team
found out about this place,
and our client might come after
us since we failed the job
There's no other choice
Now that you say it,
the way things ended with
Abydos was kinda awkward
W-Well, that situation is out of our hands
I can hardly attack them after
we fought together, side-by-side!
I see
We may be outlaws,
but that's just the proper way⋯
I agree! So let's get moved
out right and proper too!
Kayoko, what should
I do with this?
Do you need it?
Of course I do
Just use your cellphone
Convenience is nice, but
this has sentimental value!
- What even is that?
- Look at its antique design!
It fits an outlaw's
aesthetic perfectly!
I-I agree!
Because⋯
it's cool
As expected of Haruka
This isn't a retreat
We're taking a step back to spring forward
We'll overcome all adversity
and return to this office!
Because
we are true hardboiled outlaws,
Problem Solver 68!
Tomorrow, we say
goodbye to this place
Boss,
the landlord says to leave by today
since we couldn't pay
last month's rent
Aru
Then we're homeless now
Wh-Wh-What⋯
What did you say?!
I've loaded everything
Okay
Cheer up, Aru
It's not our first time
being homeless
It's just going back to
our roots for a little bit
Going back⋯
No, no! We're moving forward!
Exactly
Where to now?
I mean, there's nowhere else to go,
so back to Gehenna?
Are you leaving?
Um⋯
Sunaookami Shiroko, right?
Yeah
Wh-What are you doing here?
You can't be looking for another fight!
No
I was just riding my bike
in the area and spotted you
U-Um
About yesterday⋯
We really owe you
And about the ramen shop⋯
I can't forgive you for that
But you seem remorseful,
so I'll consider it a debt
And you're the ones who
left the bag there, right?
I-I don't know what
you're talking about
We don't know anything
about any bag of money
Never heard of it, never seen it
Aru, the way you said "bag of money"
makes it super obvious
Th-That's⋯
You're the ones who stole that
money by robbing the bank
We're not so corrupt as
to keep someone else's spoils
Even hardboiled outlaws
have their principles
Ah, Aru's back
I gave the bag to the master
I see, Thanks
Where will you go?
To meet a client who needs
Problem Solver 68's services
Aru, shall we go?
Y-Yeah
We need to find somewhere
to sleep tonight
O-Okay
No handshake?
I-I don't do goodbyes
- Because—
- You're an outlaw
Will we meet again?
Well, if that ramen shop reopens,
maybe we'll see you there
I'll be waiting
Then, it's time to head out!
- Where to?
- We're riding off into the sunset!
It's the afternoon⋯
Anyway, let's go!
Hello
We've come to visit, Master!
How are you feeling?
What're you worrying about?
It's just a few scratches
More importantly, considering
the size of the explosion,
I'm relieved no one else was hurt
Yes, but⋯
- The Shiba Seki Ramen shop⋯
- I know
I'm sorry I can't offer you
a job anymore, Serika
That's hardly the issue here, Master
I'm fine
I've been thinking about
closing up shop anyway
It's just happening a little
earlier than expected
Closing up?
Yes, I got an eviction notice recently
What do you mean
an eviction notice?
Abydos High School owns
the land and buildings
within the Abydos District
Ah, you didn't know
A few years ago, the student council
transferred ownership of
the land to another entity
Even though it's the Abydos District?
Serika, did you know about this?
No, it's the first
I've heard of it
Does that mean there's some other debt
besides the one we're paying off?
I didn't know about this either
Then who owns the buildings now?!
Could it be⋯
Kaiser Corporation?
Something like that⋯
Sorry, I can't remember the details
We need to dig into this more
Ayane, let me help
Me too!
Just say the word
I'm really sorry about this
It's a weird situation
No, it's our problem too
Besides, Master,
don't think about retiring just yet
- Got it?
- Ah, okay
Oh, right
Could you pull out the thing
under the bed for me?
Do you recognize this?
- No, well⋯
- I wouldn't say that⋯
This is⋯
Really? Shiroko
dropped it off earlier
She said she found it
in front of the exploded shop
So I opened it to see what it was⋯
and there was an astonishing
amount of money inside
There must be a story
behind it, right?
I don't think so
Someone with good intentions
must have sent it
Right
They probably wanted you to
use it to repair Shiba Seki Ramen
Yeah! The people
who left this money
must have been moved
by the taste of your ramen!
Is this real life?
If that's the case, I'll have
to repay them with a hot meal
I've kept the shop running all this time
because I wanted to
serve delicious ramen
to hungry customers
Everyone's waiting for
your ramen, Master
Get well and reopen
the shop soon, please
And I want my old job
back again, Master
Okay! Don't you worry!
When the shop reopens,
you'll be my first customers!
I'll be looking
forward to it!
Hi, Hoshino
Nice weather today
Taking a rooftop nap?
Yeah
Something like that
What about you, Sensei?
I was looking for
somewhere to take a break
It's been a while since
you first came here, huh?
Huh?
It has, now that you mention it
At first, I thought you
were some weird adult
But I'm pretty reliable, right?
No way
You're clumsy and a bit naive
- But⋯
- Huh?
The Foreclosure Task Force kids
seem more lively these days
That's not anything I did,
but rather you all chasing
after the goals that matter to you
You're probably right
Serika's started to rely on others,
Ayane's been looking up
more than down lately,
Nonomi has had this big smile
meant for herself rather than others,
and Shiroko⋯
It's like she can breathe again
You're working hard too, Hoshino
Everyone depends on you
This old-timer just wants
to protect their youth
That's right
So those kids can keep on smiling
To do that, we have to
keep moving forward⋯
Huh?
Nothing, Hearing you
say that makes me
feel free to nap all I want!
Just when I thought we were
having a serious conversation!
How like you!
Good morning, Arona
Eh?
Where's my strawberry bread?
Banana bread?
Am I being punished
for trying to eat both?
- Arona?
- Just one bite, please⋯
Huh, Sensei?!
I'll bring you bread next time
Strawberry and banana
I'm so embarrassed
But thank you!
I'll look forward to it!
Anyway, didja need something?
There's something
that's been bothering me
Could you look into
Kaiser Corporation for me?
Kaiser Corporation?
They seem to be up to something
in the Abydos Desert
Understood!
Anything else to
investigate while I'm at it?
- About Hoshino's⋯
- Huh?
No, it's nothing
I think that's something
I need to do myself
Because I'm her teacher
Is that so?
Whatever you say, Sensei⋯
Thank you
You're a great help
You can count on me!
After all,
I'm the Shittim Chest's system manager,
main OS,
and, of course, your trusty secretary!
Now then, is everyone here?
Hello, Sensei
Welcome back, everyone!
How is the master?
He's doing well in body and spirit!
He plans to reopen
Shiba Seki Ramen soon!
Really? That's great news
Yes
Is something wrong?
There's a new problem actually⋯
We were just about
to discuss it
To cut to the point,
it seems the ownership
of this district
doesn't belong
to Abydos High School
How?!
I thought the school owned
all the land in the district
The master told us that the building
Shiba Seki Ramen was in
isn't owned by Abydos
Since when?
We don't know exactly
According to the master,
it's been that way for a few years
Then who owns it now?
Kaiser Corporation
This isn't a recent development
From Problem Solver 68
to the Helmet Gang,
since the beginning, really,
we've been trapped under
Kaiser Corporation's thumb
Ugh, this is so frustrating!
W-We haven't confirmed anything,
so we don't know for certain yet⋯
Lately,
no matter how much I sleep,
it never feels like enough
I really am an old-timer now
Hey! Look, look, Doesn't
that cloud look like a whale?
Uh, Hoshino?
C'mon! Look at that big ol' cloud!
Ayane, you can't see well
from where you're sitting!
Come over here
I won't bite
- Come on!
- Don't pull me!
Wait, this is a serious matter!
- Now's not the time for⋯
- Come on
Serika, you take a look too
Why are you joining in, Nonomi?
That cloud, right?
Doesn't it look more like
a dolphin than a whale?
Hm? Maybe?
Hoshino, are you referring
to the one above that?
Oh, I see
The one right under does
look like a dolphin
Then,
what about the one under
that? Is that a jellyfish?
What kind of jellyfish
have you seen before?
I guess there might be
some that look like that!
Since we're talking about it,
should we all go to the aquarium?
B-But⋯
Nothing's certain right now
Sitting around moping
won't change that!
And so,
at the very least, I'd like to
keep smiling while I can
Besides, Serika,
the aquarium has lots of jellyfish
They're so beautiful,
gracefully floating around!
Let's go together, just this once!
Fine, I'll go!
That's right, Taking breaks is important too!
Of course! We need to keep our spirits up!
Sensei, you'll come too, right?
What? You're gonna
just abandon us?!
We're students, so Sensei
has to chaperone us
That's true
All right! Let's all go
We're counting on you!
This will be fun!
I'll take a window seat on this journey to find
the place where my heart belongs
So I can see beyond this sorrow chasing me
We were losing track of time without ever knowing why
With all those laughs we shared⋯
Even if⋯those moments were just ordinary
Those days⋯
One more time, one time more,
Knowing they won't come around again!
If only I could stay as resolute and beautiful
As the moon hanging in the bright noon sky
Would that let me finally forgive
All those regrets we made so willfully?
We only recognize the important things
Once they're gone and lost out of sight
We stretch up to the moon in the bright noon sky
Even though it will always be beyond our reach
Oh, those unforgettable, beautiful days⋯