The markings match.
The location lines up with Teacher's intel, too.
This must be the target facility.
Thank you, Ayane.
Hoshino is in there...
Everyone ready to go?
Back then...
Hoshino saved me when I had nothing.
Now it's my turn to help her.
I'm coming,
Hoshino.
You're in our way!
That's right, scram!
What the hell is this?
Damn kids! Do you have any idea
who you're messing with?!
Of course.
The front gate seems to be
the only feasible infiltration route.
But we're not making any progress.
Shiroko!
Hold the line!
Nice shot, Nonomi!
It was nothing!
We've lost half of our intercept unit.
The front line is requesting backup!
Fine.
Send backup!
Hold them back at all costs!
They opened the front gate!
They're sending reinforcements.
We have to push.
Huh?
I agree we won't get anywhere by staying here, but...
It's too dangerous!
Don't worry. They've got each other's backs.
Isn't that right, Shiroko?
Yeah.
I can't believe you, Shiroko.
Just one wild idea after another with you.
It's quiet.
Did they retreat?
No, I doubt they would at this point.
Go!
Yeah!
Stop her!
She's going for the main gate! Close it!
Not happening.
What?!
Dammit.
Come in! Code Red!
They've breached the perimeter!
I say again, Code Red!
Intruders in the base!
They broke through?
Where is the director?
Give me a status report.
Y-Yes, sir.
Intruders have breached the main gate
and are advancing into the base!
Those damn brats, still stubbornly clinging
to the name of Abydos High School!
Your orders, sir?
Which forces are ready for deployment?
The third through fifth platoons
can sortie immediately!
What about the rest?
They're still recovering from the previous battle.
Useless bunch.
I'll confirm with them again to be sure.
He's one to talk, after he forced us to deploy
that prototype and lost anyway.
You said it. He should take a look in the mirror.
Hey, shut it! He'll hear us!
Dammit!
I can't just withdraw our northern forces, either.
Should we consult with HQ?
No! I'll handle this.
S-Sir, yes, sir!
Sir, an update!
We're still being pushed back, but we could deploy
the mass-produced units at any time.
What are you waiting for?! Deploy them already!
And send out all available platoons!
We'd be leaving this facility undefended.
Are you sure?
I don't care!
Stop those intruders at all costs!
Where could Hoshino be?
This is Third Platoon!
Deploying drones!
Where's our backup?!
They're still calibrating!
Hurry it up! We're taking heavy losses!
How's that calibration looking?
All green! Deploying them now!
They have more of those?
There's so many of them!
Let's see how long you'll last against these!
What was that?
Th-That was me!
Oh, Hifumi—
No, I'm not!
My name isn't Hifumi!
It's Faust!
S-So just to make it clear!
I'm not Hifumi, and I'm not part of
any masked swimsuit gang!
Also, that wasn't artillery fire from Trinity General School!
I have no idea who could have fired those shells!
These students over here had absolutely
nothing to do with any of this!
Uh, gotcha.
Thank you so much, Faust!
Of course!
All right, then. If you would!
How dare you!
Move up! Get out of artillery range!
Nice plan, but it won't save you.
It's Gehenna's Prefects!
What a letdown.
Turns out you're all bark and no bite.
Sorry for the wait.
The Prefect Team!
CP! Requesting reinforcements!
Director, your orders?
I say again, requesting reinforcements!
Fine, I'll play their little game.
Send in everything we have!
Crush them under the might
of our entire military force!
Make them rue the day they thought they could defy us!
Iori, you're on two o'clock, the drone battalion.
You got it, Ako!
Looks like we made it in the nick of time.
You're...
The enemy must be planning an all-out push.
Hmph. Bring it on!
This is it. Let's go, everyone!
Gotcha!
Yeah!
Get out of our way!
Go nap for a little while.
I'm still in this fight, too!
Pull up and climb!
Got it!
Perfect!
This one's yours!
I got it!
Standby for drop!
Bombs away!
It's futile.
Next volley!
We'll cover your back.
Go rescue Takanashi Hoshino.
That's why you're here, right?
Right.
We've lost over half of our remaining forces!
So what do we do now?
We're screwed.
There's nothing we can do anymore.
Y-Yes, of course.
Director, we're receiving a call from HQ.
I-Ignore it! Don't open that channel!
Wh-What should I tell them?
Director! We've got more requests for backup!
What?!
The third through fifth platoons have been wiped out!
Remaining forces are down to thirty percent!
What do we do, Director?
What is it now?!
Head to the entrance!
We need to move!
Hurry up!
We're losing ground. Hold the line!
What's going on out there?
I don't know!
Your orders, sir!
Incoming!
We should help them!
Take cover!
We have to hurry!
Director!
They can't take much more of this!
Where's that backup?
So... what do I tell HQ—
Very well.
I was content to sit by while
you wasted your time, but no more.
I'll deal with them myself!
What is this place?
Isn't this a blackboard?
Y-Yeah, it is.
And not just that, everything else
looks awfully familiar, too.
Was this a school at some point?
Out here, in the heart of the desert?
Hold on, the heart?
Indeed, a rather apt description for this place.
As you may have guessed, here lies what remains
of the main Abydos High School building.
You!
You just don't know when to quit, do you,
Abydos Foreclosure Task Force?
We're here to take back Hoshino!
I've just about had it up to here with you!
Get out of our way! Or else...
It's always been you Task Force kids.
Always getting in the way,
always being a nuisance.
I've exhausted every trick in the book
just trying to get rid of you.
Yet you insist on clinging to this dying school,
desperately trying again and again
to repay that debt.
I drove you into the dirt,
crushed every ounce of hope you had!
And you still had the gall to sit there, smiling!
You've completely ruined my plan!
The plan I've worked so hard on!
We'd never bow down and let a despicable lowlife
like you get what you wanted!
We're taking Hoshino back.
We won't lose!
Definitely not to a sorry excuse of an adult like you!
You've been a pain in my ass for long enough!
I need to find that treasure.
I don't have time for you!
I don't know what you're talking about,
but you're not stopping us!
Just you try and get past me, then!
Oh, what? Another one?
Sounds like you could use a hand.
Yoo-hoo!
S-Sorry to interrupt.
P-Problem Solver 68?!
Showing up just in the nick of time...
Now this is how a first-class outlaw should be.
Whoopsie. Guess we're dropping in early!
What do you meeeaaan?!
Um...
You again!
Still hungry for more?
We took time out of our busy schedules
to come all the way out here, you know?
Though you did play it cool
and say no for the drama first.
You don't have to bring that up!
You're a big softie at heart, after all.
Wh-Whatever.
We'll take it from here.
Don't worry about us. Go!
Oh no, now I've gone and said it!
Oh my, Aru, are you trying
to make me fall for you?
Th-That's our Boss!
I'll follow you for as long as I live, Miss Aru!
Let's go.
D-Don't expect us to thank you for this.
But once this is over,
we're all getting ramen together, got it?
We'll return the favour someday!
Thank you all!
Have fun!
Well, we promised, so here goes.
My, what a pleasant surprise.
Oh, come now, Kayoko.
What's with that face?
Nothing.
We're here to help.
I'm glad nobody's hurt.
We just gotta scrap this thing, right?
H-Hold on a second!
I-I'll help, too!
Damn you all!
Why does everyone have to keep getting in my way?
Now we're talking! Right, Aru?
Let's start the party, shall we?
Right.
Bad news, mister Director.
You're dealing with us now.
I wonder how everyone's doing right now.
I disappeared without a word.
Do they hate me now?
In the end, that contract
with Kaiser Corporation meant nothing.
They attacked Abydos anyway.
Everything I did was for nothing.
Maybe... Maybe there was another way.
Maybe things turned out this way
because of my poor choices.
And now it's all gone.
The city... the school...
Nonomi...
I wonder if you're still smiling?
You would always invite me
to go shopping with you.
I'd always say no, but you never gave up
trying to get me out of my shell.
It may have seemed like a small gesture to you,
but it meant the world to me.
Serika...
You're always so uptight,
but whenever I fell asleep at school,
you always came back to wake me up.
And on days you didn't have work,
you'd even wait for me to wake up by myself.
You always hid your kindness,
but it's what kept me going all this time.
Ayane...
While I was lazing about,
you gave everyone direction.
You even took the debt seriously,
no matter how hopeless it was.
Without you, the Task Force
wouldn't be what it is today.
And finally, Shiroko...
Ever since that day I found you lost in the snow,
with no memory of who you were or how you got there,
I thought I was the one looking after you.
But before I knew it, our roles were reversed.
What you said back at the aquarium...
It really meant a lot to me.
Thanks to you guys, I was able to relax
and enjoy a peaceful school life.
I was able to look forward to tomorrow.
I could smile and laugh again, thanks to you guys.
There, in the place Yume had left us.
But even that's going to be gone soon.
All because I made the wrong choice.
Maybe if I had just talked with them,
things would have been different.
If we had come up with another solution
before I was deceived by those adults,
maybe none of this would have happened.
I was just so helpless.
I couldn't think of anything.
My actions didn't solve anything in the end.
If only I had made the right choice,
none of us would have had to get hurt.
The school...
My friends...
Yume...
They're all gone because of me.
Why did I have to be so stupid?
Why couldn't I have just asked for help?
Even though you were always looking out for me.
I'm sorry, Shiroko.
Wh-Wh-What do you mean?!
I'm taking you all down with m—
Hey, rude!
Quit making more problems for us!
D-Do you think they're okay?
Oh, for crying out loud.
Please be okay...
Hurry, Task Force.
What was that? The whole place just shook.
We can worry about that later. We gotta hurry.
You guys...
Hey, Hoshino.
You know, back when I first met you,
I kept wondering if I was dreaming.
I'd pinch my cheek constantly to make sure.
You're so adorable, and strong, and dependable.
I was just so happy you were there.
It was all too perfect.
I had to be dreaming.
Excuse me?
Maybe I'm doing a bad job of explaining it.
But the fact I'm here with you right now
feels like a miracle to me.
Well, I'm here, aren't I?
Same as every other day.
I was here yesterday, and I'll be here tomorrow.
I hardly see what qualifies that as a miracle.
Still...
Miracles are supposed to be bigger, rarer events.
Not at all, Hoshino.
I don't see it that way.
Where'd this come from anyway?
Hey, Hoshino.
One day, you'll have your own
cute little juniors following you.
And when that time comes...
Yume.
I'm so stupid.
It took me this long to finally realize what you meant.
I'll never make that mistake again.
I never want to make that mistake again.
The biggest miracle to happen to me...
...was meeting all my friends at the Task Force!
Nonomi...
Serika...
Ayane...
Shiroko...
I...
Look!
Shiroko?
Where are we?
Wait, but how?
I swear I was...
It was close.
I see.
You came for me.
Even our teacher,
an adult.
For the love of...
Do you have any idea how worried we were?
Sorry!
Wel—
Welcome home, Hoshino!
Hey! No fair, Serika!
Didn't you say that sounded too sappy?!
Oh, shut up! Who asked?
Hoshino.
Welcome home.
Welcome home, Hoshino!
Welcome home!
Welcome home, Hoshino.
I never realised how heartwarming
those words could be, Yume.
Well, you all seem to be waiting
for me to say something in return,
but sorry to say, I'm drawing a blank.
Oh, come on! Don't be like that!
You know what we mean!
Yeah, she's right!
We came all this way
to hear you say those magic words!
Oh, all right.
I guess I have to indulge my adorable little clubmates.
I'm home, guys.
Hoshino!
Let's get out of here, 'kay?
Yeah.
Back home to Abydos.