Confirmed it!
This facility perfectly matches
the intel Sensei provided
Thanks, Ayane
Hoshino is in there⋯
Everyone, are you ready?
- Yes
- Yeah
Back then,
Hoshino held her hand out to me
So this time, I will⋯
Wait for me,
Hoshino
You're in my way!
Get out of here!
What's going on? You bastards!
Do you know who
you're messing with?
Of course
It really is impossible to gain entry
anywhere besides the main gate
But we're not getting anywhere like this either
Shiroko!
Get them!
- Nice, Nonomi
- No problem!
50% of the interception unit eliminated!
Field support requested!
We have no choice
Send reinforcements!
We must stop them at all costs
The gate's opening!
But there are more enemies now
We're breaking through
What?!
It's true we'll never advance
if we don't do something⋯
But it's too dangerous!
"Don't worry
You'll have my back,”
Isn't that right, Shiroko?
Yes
As expected of Shiroko⋯
You're always so reckless
It's quiet
- Did they retreat?
- No way
They can't have
- Go!
- Yes!
Stop her!
Oh no, Close the gate!
Not a chance
What?!
Damn it!
We have an emergency! Please respond!
Intruders have infiltrated the base
I repeat, we have an emergency!
- Intruders have infiltrated the base!
- They broke through?
Where is the director?
Report the situation!
Y-Yes, sir!
Intruders have breached the main gate
and are currently inside the base!
Damn those annoying remnants
of Abydos High School!
What should we do?
How many troops are ready
for immediate deployment?
Only units 3 through 5, sir!
What about the rest?
They're still recovering from the last battle
Useless bunch
I'll double-check just in case
He's got a lot of nerve
after wrecking that prototype
Seriously, I'm amazed
he's still talking like that
Idiot, he can hear you!
Damn it
And we can't pull back
he northern units right now
Should we contact headquarters?
No! I'll handle it!
U-Understood
I've got something!
The situation is as I reported,
but we've finished production on the new weapons
Good, Deploy them immediately!
Send out units 3 through 5 too!
That would leave us defenseless here
Is that all right?
It doesn't matter!
We must stop them at all costs!
Where is Hoshino?
This is Unit 3! Deploying drones!
The other ones aren't ready yet?!
They're still being calibrated!
Hurry up! We can't
hold out much longer!
Are the calibrations still not done?
This is Command Center!
Launch is authorized!
They're like the one from last time⋯!
But there are so many of them!
How long can you hold
out with so few people?!
What was that?
Um⋯!
It's me
- Ah, Hifumi—
- You're wrong!
It isn't Hifumi,
but Faust
Th-That's why you're wrong!
I'm not Hifumi,
and I just happened to be passing by
Those aren't Trinity General School
grenade launchers or anything,
and I don't even know who fired that shot
And those students over there
have nothing to do with this either!
I-Is that so?
Thank you very much, dearest Faust!
Sure
All right everyone,
if you will!
They've managed to⋯
Regardless, charge forward!
Do you think you can win like that?
You bastards are from Gehenna⋯
Well, well
You still think numbers are everything?
Sorry to keep you waiting
The Prefect Team⋯!
Command Center,
requesting reinforcement
- Director, what should we do?
- I repeat, requesting reinforcement
Since it's come to this,
deploy all our weapons!
Crush them with our full force!
Make them regret ever challenging us
Iori, drone unit at 2 o'clock!
Got it, Ako
We arrived just in time
You are⋯
The enemy will likely
come for us at full force
Let's take them down!
All right, Everyone, let's go!
- Yeah!
- Understood!
Please get out of the way!
Take a nap for a bit
I can't lose either
- Go up from there!
- Yes!
Perfect
- I'll leave it to you
- Got it
- Ready to drop
- Here we go
Futile
Here we go!
We'll hold them here
You're going to save
Takanashi Hoshino, right?
-Yes
Remaining firepower is 50%!
- What should we do now?
- It's impossible
With our remaining power, it's just impossible
Y-Yes, sir
Director, headquarters is calling
Don't transfer it to me! Ignore it!
Then⋯what should I tell them?
Director! Another reinforcement request from the field
- What?!
- Director! Units 3 through 5 were wiped out
Remaining firepower is 30%
- What should we do?
- Director!
- We can't hold out any longer
- Give us an order!
- Where are the reinforcements?
- We're out of time
Sir, you need to respond⋯
All right
I'll crush them with my own two hands
I'll handle this myself!
This place⋯
This is a blackboard, right?
Y-Yeah
There's a whole lot of familiar objects here⋯
Is this a school?
In the middle of a desert?
Could this possibly be⋯?
Yes! Just as you suspect
This is the main building of
the previous Abydos High School
You⋯!
You just persist and persist, huh,
Abydos Foreclosure Task Force?
We're here to take back Hoshino
Do you plan on interfering with us forever?!
Move aside, or else!
Foreclosure Task Force
You've always been a thorn in our side
Despite using every possible
method at our disposal,
you've obstinately clung
to that collapsing school,
desperately working to repay its debt
Even though we harassed you so much⋯
Even though we tried to
crush you again and again,
how do you continue enjoying
yourselves day after day?!
You guys are ruining my plans!
My plans!
Do you really think we'd give in
to your evil, crude tactics?
Give us Hoshino
We won't lose!
We'll never lose to a pathetic
adult like you! Never!
I can't let you interfere a moment longer
I need to find it as soon as possible
I don't know what you're
trying to find, but move aside!
Try to make me if you can
Not again
Looks like you're in trouble, hm?
Huh?
Yoo-hoo!
E-Excuse us
Problem Solver 687!
Showing up in a crisis like this
is what makes us hard boiled outlaws
Sorry! This thing's gonna fall
What did you saaay?!
Um⋯
You bastards⋯
This guy still⋯
Huh?
We took time out of our
busy schedule to come help
You only pretended
to refuse for the drama
You don't need to tell them that!
Aru is kind, after all
A-Anyway⋯
Leave this to us
You guys keep pushing forward!
I actually said it!
I think I'm falling for you, Aru
Y-You're so cool
I'll follow you forever, Aru
Let's go
- Yeah
- Okay
I-I won't thank you now
But when this is all over,
let's go get Ramen together
- We'll repay this favor
- Thank you!
Good luck!
We have no choice now
Oh my, what a coincidence
Hey, Kayoko
What's with that face?
- It's nothing
- We came to help
Is anyone hurt?
We just need to take that thing down?
W-Wait a moment!
I'll help too
Damn it!
How dare they all get in my way!
This is getting interesting, Aru
All right, Shall we?
Yes
The ones you'll be facing⋯
are us!
I wonder what the kids
are doing right now
I disappeared without a word
Do they hate me?
(Contract)
In the end,
(Contract) my contract with
Kaiser Corporation was worthless,
and Abydos was attacked
I finally did something,
but it amounted to nothing
Was there⋯some other way?
After everything, it was my
bad choice that brought harm
to both the city and the school
Nonomi⋯ Are you still smiling?
You always invited me on shopping trips,
never deterred by my refusals
You lifted me out of my gloomy days
Back then, you made me so happy
Serika
You're usually so diligent and strict,
but you'd always come wake
me up when I'd fall asleep at school
If you didn't have to work,
you'd even stay and wait for me to wake up
That clumsy kindness of yours
kept me going
Ayane
You've led the kids in my stead,
covering for my incompetence
and working hard to
solve our money problems.
(Debt Repayment Plan) You're the reason
the Foreclosure Task Force still exists
You're the reason the Foreclosure
Task Force still exists
And⋯Shiroko
You had no memories,
and you knew nothing of this world,
so I always thought it was
me looking out for you
When did it become
the other way around?
What you said at the aquarium
made me so, so happy
Because of each of you,
I got to enjoy an unburdened school life,
continuing to move forward no matter what
Thanks to you, I was able to smile
in the place Yume left for us
But that'll be gone soon too, won't it?
All because of my bad choices
Would I be here if I'd faced
our problems head on?
If I'd managed to figure it out
before being tricked by an adult,
would the situation be different now?
I wasn't good enough, I couldn't find a solution
And I solved nothing in the end
If I had just made the right choice,
then I'd never have experienced this pain
The school,
the kids,
Yume⋯
It's all my fault, every last bit of it
Why did I make all these mistakes?
Why couldn't I have just been
honest and relied on them?
Everyone cared about me so much
I'm sorry, Shiroko
Wh-Wh-What did you do?!
- Since it's come to this⋯
- Wait!
What on earth are you doing?
A-Are they going to be okay?
- Tch, What the hell?
- Everyone⋯
Hurry, Foreclosure Task Force
What was that shaking just now?
- Not our problem, Let's go!
- Yeah
Everyone
Hey, Hoshino
You know, when I first met you,
I had to pinch my cheek a bunch of times
because I thought I was dreaming
Having a cute, strong,
dependable junior like you by my side
really felt like a dream, I was so happy
Okay?
Maybe I'm not explaining it well,
but getting to be by your side,
it feels like a miracle to me
Day after day, we're always together
Yesterday, today, and
tomorrow are all the same
That's just the way of things,
so what's the big deal?
Still!
Miracles are supposed
to be something amazing
and rare, aren't they?
No
I don't think that's quite right, Hoshino
What're you even saying?
You know, Hoshino
Someday you'll have a cute junior too
When that time comes⋯
Yume,
I've been so foolish
I had to be put in this
situation to finally understand
I'll never make this mistake again
I don't want to make
this mistake ever again
Because to me, the real miracle is
my Foreclosure Task Force juniors!
Nonomi
Serika
Ayane
Shiroko
I⋯
Is that⋯?
Shiroko⋯?
Yes
Where are we?
Huh? How did I⋯
I was sure that I⋯
It was close
Huh?
I see
You kids⋯
Sensei⋯
An adult⋯
Geez! Do you know
how worried everyone was?
Sorry
W⋯
Welcome back, Hoshino
Ah! No fair, Serika!
And you said you couldn't say
embarrassing stuff like that
Shut up, Who cares!
- Hoshino
- Huh?
Welcome back
Hoshino! Welcome back
Welcome back, Hoshino
You were right
Those words have so much warmth,
Yume
You all look so expectant now
Do you really want to hear me say it?
What the heck! If you know,
don't drag it out!
She's right
We came all the way here
to hear those words
from you, Hoshino
Well, geez
How can I say no to you youngins?
I'm home
- Hoshino!
Well, shall we head back then?
Yeah
To our school
(Abydos Foreclosure Task Force)
% Congratulations! % Approved!
Abydos Foreclosure Task Force