So you've successfully reclaimed
the Schale building, Sensei
Only thanks to everyone's hard work, Rin
Then, would you please follow me?
This is where we store the student council
president's personal effects
Take this, Sensei
A smart tablet?
The student council president left it for you
The Shittim Chest
Its OS and system structure
are complete mysteries
None of us were even able to activate it
Perhaps you can discover its secrets
Castella cake…
Banana milk goes better…
than strawberry milk…
Huh? Wha? Ah?!
If you're here in this space,
does that mean you're…?!
- Are you…
- That's right
I'm Sensei, from Schale!
Calm down, calm down!
Well, uh…
Ah, right!
My name is Arona!
I'm the system manager in the Shittim Chest
and I serve as its main OS.
Think of me as your trusty secretary!
It's nice to meet you, Arona
Yeah! It's nice to meet you too,
Sensei!
The sky blue archive!
I pedal on my bike seeking new sights
We'll break the monotony,
no longer trapped in place
Daydreaming on the rooftop,
gazing at a sky so blue
Those clouds like whales are always changing
We'll embrace a past that can't be altered
Sharing juice in this world made of sand
is a taste so divine
If I were here alone, here without all of you
I couldn't laugh, I couldn't cry
A fateful coterie
Even if the world's memories blow away
like grains of sand one day
The sky, sea, wind, and you,
our youth will never end
It's easy to see why we protect what we do
Because this is the only place where we belong
- Run!
- Out of my way!
- Help!
- Retreat!
Well done, everyone
That's another Helmet Gang outpost
we've dismantled
Right
Well done, Sensei!
Ah, thank you, Arona
Phew, I'm exhausted…
These old bones need a nap
Oh dear!
You all ready to head back to school?
- Yeah!
- Okay…
Now that we've taken down
(Foreclosure Task Force
Daily Meeting)
the Helmet Gang's nearest
base of operations,
(Foreclosure Task Force
Daily Meeting)
they'll be forced to lay low for a while
It's all thanks to you
You were the ones who did all the work!
Don't be so humble…
The Sensei of Schale is on
a whole 'nother level
Now we can focus on repaying our debt
Right, your debt…
How much do you owe, exactly?
Oh, 900 million or so?
9-900 million?
962,350,000 yen, to be precise
How did you end up in such a massive hole?
…Decades ago,
there was a massive sandstorm
in the desert surrounding Abydos
The power of that sandstorm was devastating
Parts of Abydos were completely buried in sand
The school had to raise a lot of funds
for disaster relief…
but there wasn't a single bank that would
approve such a large loan
So the school was forced into the arms of
some loan sharks called Kaiser Loans
They thought they would be able to pay
the money back quickly…
But…
The sandstorms only worsened
as the years went on
and now more than half of Abydos has
disappeared beneath the sand
As the debt ballooned with each storm,
the students began to despair
If the academy can't repay its debt,
the loan sharks will foreclose on us
They'll shut down the school
But our chances of repaying that
much money are almost zero
The other students gave up…
They left the school a long time ago
That's why we're the only ones left
Well, we shouldn't bore you with old stories
Thank you for sharing this with me
I'm starting to understand what
you've been going through
This huge debt may feel overwhelming…
But you're right not to give up!
How about this…
I'm your Sensei now, so we're in this together
Can I help you out?
Do you mean—
Yes! Thank you so much!
How is that okay?
This "Sensei" is a complete outsider
But that's why he can help us
Maybe he can see something we haven't tried
So what?!
We've been dealing with the school's
problems on our own!
Why are we taking orders from
some adult we don't know?
I just want to help you out
Stop looking down on us!
I don't accept your help!
Serika!
They're all so stupid!
"Sensei, Sensei!"
(Hoshino: We can take it a little more easy now)
(Ayane: I agree with what Shiroko said!)
(Hoshino: Eager as ever, Ayane)
(Ayane: Let's keep up the hard work!)
(Besides, whatever we say now…)
What's wrong with Sensei?
After school yesterday…
Hey, Serika! Heading home?
Hey, Serika
Maybe we could drop by a cafe and chat?
H-Hey S-Serika…
C-Can we talk for a second?
Go away, you stalker!
You know that would have annoyed anyone,
let alone Serika, right?
Speaking of…
Have you noticed that Serika always leaves
right after school?
Where does she go?
And she only responds in MomoTalk
late at night, too…
That's right
Say, everyone…
Why don't we secretly trail Serika
after school today?
I'm in!
Good morning
The target has passed point A.
Tracking target
I have her in my sights
Swapping hounds
Understood
Please stay on her trail
This is…
(Shiba Seki Ramen)
Shiba Seki Ramen?
That reminds me
The ramen there is delicious
(Shiba Seki Ramen)
Thank you!
Tasty as always!
Master, I'm back for more!
Serika isn't coming out
Think she signed up for an eating contest?
I'm hungry, Want to go inside and see?
- Sure
- I'm in!
Hey, welcome!
Welcome, how many—
Wow, Serika!
That uniform's so cute!
You guys…
Are you Serika's classmates from Abydos?
Since you're here to support her,
I'll give you a free meal on the house!
W-Well, everyone
This way…please
Serika, did you take this job
for the cute uniform?
Enough! Just order already!
- Miso Ramen
- Beef Ramen
One at a time!
What about you, Sensei?
Order what you want!
All right…
Ah, well, I'll…
Well…
Thank you for the food!
So how'd you like my ramen?
It's so good!
Of course it is!
But it's great to meet Serika's friends!
Your shop seems to be doing pretty well
Nah, business has really dried up lately
S-Sorry
Ah, there's no helping it
So long as one hungry soul
steps through my door,
I'll serve them the best ramen
in the world!
That's the motto of my shop, at any rate
That's amazing!
Master, I'll learn from your example
and do my best to help these students!
Oh, you're not half bad, Sensei!
- Please come again!
- I'll make an exception
and give you one more bowl on the house!
Serika! See you in the morning!
- Goodbye
- Good ramen, good life
They really gave me a shock…
(Shiba Seki Ramen)
Serika, go ahead and
hang up your apron now
All right!
- Oh…Serika?
- Yes?
It's nice to see an adult
with his students at heart
That's how I feel
…I'm going to head out now
Good work today, Heading home?
That master is an amazing ramen cook…
And I think he's a good person
He seems dependable
Yeah…
- You know, Serika…
- Hmm?
I think Sensei is the same way
I trust him
Night, Serika, See you tomorrow
For the master and Shiroko
to say the same thing…
That Sensei…
Can we really rely on him?
No, that's impossible!
After everything Abydos has gone though…
What is this?!
What? Are you joking?
Serika is missing?
Yes, She didn't answer her door this morning
I was worried, so I went inside
But her uniform and bag were gone!
What about her phone?
She didn't pick up any of my calls
Don't tell me that last night…
Hold on a minute, everyone
The sea is where the soul resides
- Ah, welcome back, Sen—
- Arona!
Can you do me a favor?
It's urgent
Please locate Serika!
O-Okay!
I know where Serika is!
Huh? How?
I accessed the General Student Council's
central network
and tracked the location of
Serika's cellphone!
You have the authority to do that?
That doesn't matter, Where is Serika?
It looks like she's on the move
The desert outside the city?
She's moving towards
one of the Kata-Kata Helmet Gang's hideouts!
Are they trying to force our hand
with a hostage?
We can't waste time chatting
We need to rescue Serika now!
Right
Hold on a moment!
Where am I?
Is this a truck?
Have I been kidnapped?
Are they driving through the desert?
Transport team, reporting in
Kata-Kata Helmet HQ, do you copy?
This is Kata-Kata Helmet HQ.
Transport team, what's taking you so long?
We don't have long until we're discovered
We'll be caught if you delay!
Don't worry, we'll be there
in about ten minutes
Fine, just hurry it up!
Copy
I have to escape!
Please!
What should I do?
Everyone must be so worried
Are they dragging me off to
bury me somewhere?
Everyone!
I wish you were here!
What?!
Nice going, Shiroko!
Head straight for Serika!
Ayane, where did you find this truck?
It was collecting dust in the
school warehouse
I didn't think it would ever come in handy
Hold on!
Stop her!
What's happening? What's going on?
Serika's here, with tears in her eyes
Serika!
Poor Serika
Cute kids shouldn't be left alone
Stop it!
Don't cry, Serika
We're here to wipe away your tears
I'm not crying!
Serika, it's a relief to hear your voice
S-Sensei? Why are you here too?
I'm a stalker, remember?
Wh-What?
Don't tease me at a time like this!
You're all so mean!
All right, everyone,
you know what to do next
Yes!
Let's counterattack!
Follow them!
No more dirty tricks!
No more mercy!
You'll have to aim better than that!
This is what you get for kidnapping me!
If your gun won't work…
You did it, Shiroko!
A-Ayane, watch out!
We got their car!
Try playing hide and seek now!
Sensei, are you all right?!
Y-You saved me
Let me handle this!
Take this!
Your bullets are nothing to our tanks!
They're tougher than I expected
Wait, everyone—I have a plan!
Stop cowering! Come out here!
You'll need to move together
What do you think?
Yes, I like it!
It's worth a shot!
I'll watch your back!
We're counting on you, Serika
Yes, I won't let you down!
We're ready now
Move to your positions!
Understood
You can't escape us!
Now, Ayane
Okay!
I told you it was useless!
Just give up and surrender already!
Done playing cat and mouse?
Get your hands in the air!
10, 9, 8,
7, 6, 5,
4, 3, 2,
1!
Now, Serika!
N-No way!
Run away!
- Just you wait!
- You'll regret this!
Wish you never kidnapped
me now, don't you?
We won by the skin of our teeth
Great job, everyone
You too, Sensei!
Our Sensei's truly wise beyond his years
N-No way!
We really taught the Helmet Gang
a lesson this time
Yes, definitely
Thank you, Serika
Don't thank me!
I would have escaped on my own
without you!
And I could have handled the Helmet Gang
by myself!
But, still…
Y-You rescued me, so…
Thank you, Sensei!
Ah, little Serika's shy
N-No I'm not!
- You sure?
- I said no!
Youngins are never honest with themselves
- But that's why you're so cute
- Enough!
I'll take a window seat on this journey to find
the place where my heart belongs
So I can see beyond this sorrow chasing me
We were losing track of time without ever knowing why
With all those laughs we shared…
Even if…those moments were just ordinary
Those days…
One more time, one time more,
Knowing they won't come around again!
If only I could stay as resolute and beautiful
As the moon hanging in the bright noon sky
Would that let me finally forgive
All those regrets we made so willfully?
We only recognize the important things
Once they're gone and lost out of sight
We stretch up to the moon in the bright noon sky
Even though it will always be beyond our reach
Oh, those unforgettable, beautiful days…
Wh-Who are you people?
We are Problem Solver 68!
And we'll do the crime…
…if you've got the dime!