I see you successfully reclaimed Schale HQ, Teacher.
Come now, it was a group effort, Rin.
Now, if you would follow me, please.
We've been preserving an artifact
the GSC president left behind.
Please take this, Teacher.
A tablet?
Yes. The President intended for you to have this.
It's called the Shittim Chest.
We know nothing about its OS, architecture,
anything. It's effectively a black box.
We were unable to even power it on.
However, I suspect you may succeed.
With castella cake...
Banana milk is better than strawberry...
If you made it here, does that mean you're...
Yup. I'm the teacher from Schale.
Calm down. Keep it together.
Um, uh...
Oh, that's right!
My name is Arona.
I operate as both the system administrator
and main OS of the Shittim Chest.
From now on, consider me your trusty personal assistant!
Pleasure to meet you, Arona.
Same here!
It's nice to meet you, Teacher!
Run for it!
Retreat!
Good work, everyone.
With this, we managed to recapture
another one of the Helmet Gang's hideouts.
Yep, looks like it.
Good work, Teacher.
Thank you, Arona.
This old engine's all outta gas.
I wanna go home and refuel.
My, oh my.
Let's head back and rest up.
'Kay.
Okay!
As for the Helmet Gang,
we took down their nearest base,
so I suspect they'll stop bothering us for a while.
It's all thanks to our new teacher.
You're giving me too much credit.
Oh, always the modest one!
You are the Teacher of Schale, after all.
Now we can finally focus on repaying our debt.
Speaking of which, how much do you owe them exactly?
Somewhere around 900 million, I think?
900 million?!
962,350,000 yen, to be precise.
How in the world did you rack up so much debt?
Several decades ago, a giant sandstorm
swept through the Abydos suburbs.
The scale of it was beyond anyone's imagination.
Many areas in the district were buried in sand.
It was extremely costly to repair the damage,
but they couldn't find a single bank
who would lend them the money.
In the end, they were forced to turn to
the loan sharks at Kaiser Loan.
I believe it started as a small sum,
something that could easily be paid off.
But...
Abydos kept getting struck
by sandstorm after sandstorm.
Over half of Abydos was eventually
swallowed up by the desert.
The students lost all hope, and in the end,
all that remained was the massively bloated debt.
If we can't pay off the debt, the school will go bankrupt,
and we'll be forced to close Abydos High for good.
But the likelihood of us actually
clearing the debt is practically zero.
Nearly all the students gave up and left the school.
We're the last ones holding the fort.
The end. Sorry to bore you.
Thank you for telling me.
I understand what you're going through a little better now.
The debt is truly staggering,
but you can't just give up, either.
Right, everyone?
If it's all right with you, would you mind
if I continued helping you as your teacher?
You mean it?
O-Of course!
We'd be happy to have you.
You sure about that?
At the end of the day, he's still an outsider.
He might give us a fresh perspective
on how to handle our problem.
Still!
We've always taken care of ourselves
without needing help!
But now some guy shows up and
we're supposed to just blindly follow him?
I'm just trying to help.
Oh, how noble of you!
I'll never accept you!
Serika!
What's wrong with them?
Nothing but Teacher this, Teacher that!
What's wrong, Teacher?
Well, yesterday after school...
Hey there, Serika. Heading home?
Hey, Serika. Want to chat over some coffee?
H-Hey there, Serika. Are you maybe free to...
Screw off! Quit stalking me!
I think just about anyone would
blow up at you, not just our little Serika.
Speaking of Serika, she never sticks around after school.
Does anyone know where she goes?
Come to think of it, she's usually
slow to respond on Momotalk, too.
Oh, true!
Why not tail her after school
and see what she's up to?
Huh?
I'm in!
Morning.
Target passing through Point A now.
Following now.
Will continue to tail the target.
Hounds, changing shift.
Roger that.
Hound 1, stay on her tail.
Isn't this... Shiba Seki Ramen?
Now that I think about it...
Their ramen is really good.
Thanks for the food.
It was delicious as ever!
Hey boss, long time no see.
Serika's not coming out.
Maybe she's doing one of those eating challenges?
I'm starting to get hungry,
so why don't we all head inside?
Good idea!
Yeah.
Step right in!
Welcome! How man—ugh!
Oho?
Howdy, Serika!
Your uniform is adorable!
Wh-Wha...
So yer 'er schoolmates from Abydos?
A friend o' Serika's a friend o' mine.
I'll get ya a little extra on the house.
Um, well...
Th-This way, please.
Do you pick jobs based on
what the uniform's like, Serika?
Enough about me already!
Can I take your order?
I'd like a miso ramen.
One shio ramen.
I'll take the chashu ramen, please!
Special miso! With extra grilled chashu!
One at a time!
Don't be shy, Teacher.
Order whatever you want!
Well then, I'll have...
I mean...
Thanks for the food!
Well? Enjoyin' our ramen?
It's very good.
It's great!
Ain't it just"?
I knew Serika's pals would 'ave good taste.
I see business is booming.
Well, actually, we've been seein' fewer customers lately.
Is it because...
Well, no sense worryin' 'bout it!
At the end o' the day, my job's a simple one—
Support my hungry customers with a bowl o' piping hot joy!
That's all that matters.
That's amazing!
I'll do my best to follow your lead and
give it all my all to support my students in need!
Aye, that's the spirit!
I like you! Have another bowl, on the house!
Thank you, please come again!
See you tomorrow, Serika.
See you at school.
Bye now.
Catch you later.
Sheesh, what's wrong with them?
Serika. Yer good to go home for the day.
Got it.
Hey, Serika.
That teacher cares a whole lot 'bout
his students. He's a good man.
Huh?
'Least, that's what I think.
I'll be on my way.
Good job. Heading home now?
That ramen was good.
The owner was a nice person.
He seemed very reliable to me.
Yeah.
Hey, Serika?
Hm?
I think our teacher is just as reliable.
Bye, Serika. See you tomorrow.
The boss said the exact same thing.
Teacher, huh...
I wonder if I should just accept his help.
No, no, I can't!
If I do, what'll happen to Abydos High?
What the...
Wait, are you sure?!
Is Serika really missing?
She is!
She wouldn't answer the door,
so I checked inside,
but she wasn't there,
and her bag and uniform were gone.
Did you try calling her?
Yes, but she isn't picking up.
Did something happen last night?
Everyone, stay calm.
Ah, the sea, my old friend.
Huh?
Oh, hello, Teach—
Arona!
I need your help!
Locate Serika for me, quickly!
Huh? O-Of course!
I've narrowed down Serika's location!
What? H-How?
I tapped into the GSC's central network
and used it to locate Serika's smartphone.
How did you even get those privileges?!
Never mind that. Where is she?
Here.
It looks like she's still in transit.
The desert area in the suburbs?
Wait, this is close to one of the routes
we confirmed the Helmet Gang was using!
So now they've resorted to taking her hostage, huh?
Figuring out the reason can wait.
We need to go rescue her, now!
Hold on a minute!
Is this... the back of a truck?
Was I kidnapped?
Wait, are we in the desert?
Transport squad, reporting in.
Come in, Kata-Kata Helmet Gang HQ.
Kata-Kata Helmet Gang HQ, received.
You're late, transport squad.
What's the hold-up?
The client will be here any minute.
I swear, if you don't make it to
the hand-off site in time...
Relax. We'll be there in ten minutes.
Whatever, just hurry up!
Roger.
I need to get out of here!
Damn it!
What should I do?
They must be worried sick about me.
Are they going to bury me somewhere
in the desert where no one can find me?
Guys...
Where are you?
Wh-What was that?!
Nice going, Shiroko!
Let's hurry and get Serika out of there!
Ayane! Where'd you get this buggy?
It was just gathering dust in the warehouse.
I didn't expect it to come in handy like this, though.
Hold on to something!
Stop them!
What the? What's going on outside?
I found Serika. She's crying.
Serika!
Our adorable little Serika is crying?
Gosh, she must've really missed us!
Shut up!
Don't cry, Serika.
We'll wipe those tears away!
I'm not crying!
I'm glad you're safe and sound, Serika.
Wh-What the heck is he doing here?
I didn't stalk you all that time for nothing!
What the heck?
Quit screwing around at a time like this.
What are you, stupid?!
Okay, girls. You know what to do.
Aye.
Yes!
Time to retaliate!
Don't let 'em get away!
I won't let you cause any more trouble!
No more playing nice.
I won't get hit that easily!
This is payback for kidnapping me!
How about this, then?
You did it, Shiroko!
Watch out, Ayane!
There goes your car!
Let's see you run from us now!
Are you okay, Teacher?
Y-Yeah, thanks for the save.
Here I go!
Take this!
You're gonna need a bigger gun
to get through this armour!
They're tougher than I thought.
Everyone, listen up. I have an idea.
Quit hiding! Come out and fight!
That's my plan.
What do you all think?
Yeah. I like it.
Me too. Let's go with that!
Leave the support to me!
She's all yours, Serika!
Yeah. I got this!
Preparations are ready.
All hands, commence operation!
Roger that!
Run all you like, you can't escape us!
Ayane!
You're up!
Got it!
It's pointless!
You've lost! Just give up!
What, done playing tag already?
Say goodnight!
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
Now, Serika!
Huh?
No way!
Pull back!
You'll pay for this!
That's what you get for kidnapping me!
Whew, that went surprisingly well.
Great job out there, everyone.
You too, Teacher!
Man, our teacher sure is something!
What? Nah...
I'm sure the Helmet Gang
learned their lesson this time!
Yeah, I'm sure.
Serika, thank you.
Oh, j-just shut up already!
I could've gotten out of there by myself.
I didn't need your help!
I could've handled the Helmet Gang on my own, too...
But... um...
Y-You did save me, so...
Thanks, Teacher!
Ooh, Serika's finally softened up.
N-No, I haven't!
You sure?
It's not like that!
Aw, look at you, trying so hard to hide it.
I just said thank you, that's all!
We still love that part of you.
Who... Who the hell are you?
We're Problem Solver 68.
We'll do the crime if you got the dime.
And I mean any crime.