Yes, everything in the report is accurate.
It was entirely our fault.
Yes. Yes...
What?! In one week?
Oh, no, not at all.
Please leave it to us.
Boss, are you planning on
fighting the Abydos kids again?
But we already blew all our cash.
What do you want us to do?
We're bound to run short
on funds renting this fancy office
Q-quiet, you!
What's a company without a proper office?
Honestly, I'd be fine with  pitching tents in the park like last time.
I-I would also be fine anywhere
as long as you're there, Miss Aru...
Would you all just be quiet!
We'll take out a loan.
Huh? But aren't you blacklisted from the banks?
No, I'm not!
I've just been declared a public enemy and had my assets frozen, that's all!
Oh, right.
Just you wait! I'm not letting this mission end like this!
Thank you for choosing Kaiser Loan!
I have confirmed the receipt of
788 million, 3 thousand 250 yen, in cash.
Well then, see you again next month.
Looks like we managed to scrape by this month.
By the way, I wonder why Kaiser Loan
only accepts cash for the payments?
Good point. It would be much easier to simply transfer the amount from a bank account.
No attacking the transport car, Shiroko.
I know that.
Now then, let's begin our regular meeting.
First off, about the part
that we recovered the other day.
It turns out that this part did in fact originate from the Black Market.
It's a dangerous place that deals in many illegal items
and is notorious as a hotbed for unauthorized clubs.
It appears that Problem Solver 68
are often spotted visiting the area as well.
Problem Solver 68...
It looked like they were after our school, same as the Helmet Gang.
With how often we've been attacked, there's gotta be something else going on that we don't know about.
I wonder what it could be.
Right.
Investigating the connection between these events might lead us to finding out the truth.
All right, guess that settles it.
Let's take a little field trip, shall we?
We've got some new firearms in stock.
Wait, for real?!
That's so wild.
So this is the Black Market
Look at all the people!
I can't believe the holes in the GSC's network
have gotten this big.
Well, we're always cooped up
the Abydos area.
The world's full of strange places like these.
Have you been here before, Hoshino?
Nah, this is my first time, too.
I hear there are plenty of wacky things out in the other school districts.
Like this one place has giant aquariums.
I hear they're huge!
I'd love to go one of these days.
Yeah... that sounds nice.
Everyone, there's no telling
what could happen out there.
Please be careful.
Got it.
I said quit running!
Please, stop following me!
As if!
Come on, let's have some fun!
If it's all the same to you, I'd really rather not...
Her uniform is from Trinity?!
I've got this.
Are you all right?
Huh? Oh, uh, yes.
Who the hell are you?
Back off, it's her that we want!
She's from Trinity General School,
the richest school in Kivotos.
We're just gonna borrow her for a bit
and ask for a little money in return, see!
Catch and release.
Pretty slick, don't you think?
What do you say?
Want in on this?
We'll split the ransom -
No thanks.
That was a close call.
Oh, thank you so much!
My name is Ajitani Hifumi.
Hifumi, huh. Nice to meet you.
Still, what's a girl from Trinity doing
in such a rough part of town?
Well, you see...
I'm actually looking for something.
There aren't any stores that sell it anymore.
But I heard that it's secretly
being traded around here still.
Wait, are you talking about a tank?
Illegal firearms, perhaps?
Ooh, maybe biochemical weapons?
What? No, nothing like that. It's, uhh...
limited-edition Mister Peroro merch.
Peroro?
Yes, this guy right here.
It's a Mister Peroro plush that had a very limited run.
Only 100 units were ever produced.
Oh, it's from Momo Friends!
I'm a huge fan, too!
Peroro's so cute!
You think so, too?
Of course!
Oh boy, the times have sure moved on, haven't they.
By the way, what are all of you doing here?
We're also looking for something.
It's not something you can find easily,
but we heard that it would be here.
I see.
Guess we're kind of in the same boat, huh.
Still, looks like your shopping trip took quite the nasty turn.
Well, I mean, I knew this place was bad news before.
I'd also heard that the corporations were taking advantage of the GSC's absence to run wild here...
It's apparently gotten so bad that it has
its own bank and security force.
Wait, those would also fall under unauthorized, illegal operations, right?
I've heard that the security forces
here are especially bad news.
Wow, Hifumi, you sure know your stuff.
Oh, no, I wouldn't say that.
All right, that's settled, then!
We helped you out, now it's your turn to help us with what we're looking for!
Huh? Wait, what?
Are you sure we want
a loan from these guys?
This bank is part of the Black Market.
T-The interest rates must be h-horrible...
Well, to be fair, we don't even know if
Aru will pass the background check.
Q-Quiet, you. Of course I'll pass!
Come on, let's go!
That's odd. There should be at least some
information on your illegal part, but I can't find any.
The purchase history, storage records...
Someone's gone to the effort of hiding all of it.
That's the feeling I'm getting.
Someone doesn't want us to find it?
Right. The corporations may run this place, but
even they shouldn't be able to do all this...
This isn't normal?
More like, why bother going that far?
The corporations here are almost flaunting their illegal activities at this point,
so it seems odd that they would try to hide anything.
Take that building, for example.
Even within the Black Market,
that bank is notorious for its shady business.
Shady?
From what I've heard,
nearly 15 percent of all the money that funds criminal activity in Kivotos
is being funneled straight into that bank.
Money that is obtained from various crimes like embezzlement, theft, and kidnapping
are then turned into weapons and equipment to be used in other crimes.
It's a vicious cycle.
Wait, but doesn't that mean the bank
is basically assisting those crimes?
Exactly. Even the banks here are criminal organizations.
It's the Market Guard!
The Market Guard?
They're the top of the top within the security forces here.
They're escorting that vehicle.
Looks like a cash transport.
Wait, isn't that...
The person who always collects
our money for the bank?
Thank you for your patience.
Here is this month's collection.
Thank you.
Now if you would please sign here.
Of course.
Wait, that means Kaiser Loan
has ties with that bank.
Did you say Kaiser Loan?!
You've heard of them, Hifumi?
Umm, they're the loan sharks run by
the infamous Kaiser Corporation, right?
Are they dirty?
Yes.
The Kaiser Group is a conglomerate known
for cleverly skirting the border of legality.
Definitely doesn't sound like the
cleanest place to work.
Did you borrow money from Kaiser Loan?
Well, you know, it's a long story.
So that's why they only accepted cash payments.
They must have been trying to avoid
leaving a paper trail.
I can't believe the money
was going to a bank for criminals...
You mean our money has been funding
criminal activity this whole time?
W-We don't know that for sure...
We don't have any proof that Kaiser Loan
was taking our money to the Black Market's bank.
Oh, but they have to issue a receipt
when they bring the money in, right?
If you could find a record of that,
wouldn't that serve as evidence?
Oh!
But now that I think about it,
the papers would already be inside the bank,
so there's no way to get to them.
We're talking inside of a bank that has
top of the line security,
even by Black Market standards, so...
Hey, Hoshino.
I think this calls for that plan.
Hm? Which plan? Oh, right, that plan.
I agree. That plan might be just what we need!
Wait, you don't mean THAT plan...?
Please don't tell me you mean THAT plan...
Um, I'm sorry, I'm not sure I...
There's only one thing left to do.
We're robbing that bank.
Excuse me?!
Shiroko, hold on!
There's gotta be another -
It's okay.
We're just finding evidence of their crimes.
Well, I suppose that's true...?
Fine. I doubt you'd listen
even if I said no, anyway.
Umm, what's...
Sorry, Hifumi.
I didn't think far enough ahead,
so I don't have a mask for you.
Wait, I'm doing this too?!
We couldn't just leave you
out in the cold like that.
Oh, no, no,
I wouldn't mind at all.
Here, Hifumi, this one's for you.
What?
Wait, hold on, let's talk about this,
Nono- hnggfh
It looks so cute on you!
D-Does this mean that
I'm also coming along with you, then?
Don't be silly, Hifumi.
You promised, remember?
That you'll help us find what we're looking for.
Oh, oh no...
What am I going to tell everyone
on the student council...
It'll be fine!
We're the good guys here.
What about you, Teacher?
I'm in, too.
I can't overlook the possibility that your money
is being used for evil purposes, after all.
Right.
All right, then, Masked Swimsuit Gang,
Roll out!
Thank you for your patience.
Yes, in fact I'm almost quite out of it.
What's the bottom line?
I need money, and I need it now.
I'm terribly sorry, but we are
unable to process your request this time.
Wait, what?
You mean you can't lend us the money?
That is correct.
But hold on!
We have an entire office!
What's the issue?!
Your office is a rental.
The only hard assets you own
are firearms. We couldn't possibly
lend you any money like this.
Wait, what?!
If you had something you could put up as collateral,
or if you had a strong credit history with us,
we could lend you money,
but might I suggest you start by
finding a day job?
Excuse me?!
《This little jerk...
I'm tempted to just
burn this place down
and walk out with the money.
No, that wouldn't work.
The Market Guard is here, too.
We'd never get away.
I don't have the guts to
make an enemy of the Black Market.
God, what am I even doing?
I promised myself I would become
the number one outlaw in all of Kivotos.
But look at me now, agonizing over
stupid things like bank loans...
This isn't what I wanted to be doing.
I wanted to become someone who
lived fearlessly, by my own rules.
A hard-boiled outlaw...
Or at least, that was the dream...》
Everyone, drop your weapons
and get down on the ground!
B-Bank robbers?!
Do as we say,
or prepare to get hurt!
Uh, umm, I'd hate for anyone
to get hurt, so stay calm,
and get down on the ground, please.
Hey, wise guy.
She said drop your weapons.
Hey, girls...
Do make sure not to harm any of the civilians, okay?
Got it.
Right-o. So far, so good.
Let's move on to phase 2, shall we?
Come on, Faust, you're the leader.
Give us the word!
Huh? Wait, what?
You mean me? I'm Faust?!
Of course.
Hifumi-
I mean, Faust, you're the leader!
In other words, you're our boss!
And while we're at it,
call me Christina, doll!
Huh? Aren't those the girls from Abydos...?
S-Should we beat them up?
No, looks like they're not here for us.
Don't do anything stupid.
That cash transport just now.
Yes, of course.
I'll give you whatever you want.
Bullion, cash, bonds, anything!
No, not that. We just want the receipts...
《Whoa... who are these people?!
They're hitting a bank in the Black Market of all places!
They're making it look so easy, too.
So... professional!
They're just so cool!
I can't get enough of them!
They're the picture definition of outlaw!
Oh god, I think I'm going to cry!》
H-Here it is!
Please, just take it... don't kill me...
Shiro-, sorry, Blue 2.
Do you have the package?
Oh, uh, yeah. It's just...
All righty. Let's make like a tree and skedaddle!
Everyone, we're leaving!
Adios!
Well, it doesn't look like
anyone got hurt, so... Goodbye!
A-After them!
Seal off the perimeter!
Now that's what I call an outlaw!
You're out of the hot zone.
Good work, everyone.
Heck yeah! We did it!
I feel my actions
as a teacher are questionable at best...
Shiroko, you got the receipts?
Yeah.
Whoa!
Just look at all that!
Shiroko, did you just steal money after all?!
No.
The documents we need are right here.
Yowza. There's easily 100 million in there.
That's great! Let's bring it back with us!
Serika, wait!
What? This will be a huge help for...
We can't do that, Serika!
Why the heck not?!
This is all the money we poured
our sweat and tears into earning!
And it was all going to that bank run by criminals!
True, if we hadn't done anything, it's possible that this money
would have been turned into
weapons for criminals to use.
That's right. What's wrong with stealing from criminals?!
I agree with Serika.
It's money that was funding criminal activity.
It'd be better if we used it for good instead.
And besides, this much money would
go a huge way towards paying off the school's debt!
Are you sure you're okay with doing it like that?
What do you think, Shiroko?
You already know.
You'd say no.
Huh?
Got me there, Shiroko.
You're exactly right.
What we need is the papers.
Not the money.
If we say it's okay this one time
because it's dirty money,
what happens next time?
What about the time after that?
I think if we let ourselves get used to this,
we'll just keep making excuses to
do things that we shouldn't
every time we get into trouble.
And this old man just couldn't
bear the thought of all you young ones
going astray like that.
Besides, if we were going to do something like that,
I would have just used
that fancy schmancy gold card
that Nonomi has from the get-go.
But you said that
you didn't want to...
Oh! I remember now!
If we can't pay back
the money the right way,
we'll lose the Abydos we were
trying to protect anyway.
That's right.
In that case, let's only take the papers that we need.
Are you okay with that?
Yes!
I can't say I know what you're going through,
but holding onto this money
might cause problems down the line.
I'm sure it's caused its fair share
of problems already.
Hold on a second!
Oh, uh, don't worry!
I'm not your enemy!
What's she doing here?
Do we shoot her?
I'd rather not beat up someone who
just said she's not our enemy...
Do you know her?
Yes, we've happened to bump into her before.
Um, I saw the attack you pulled off earlier.
You were in and out in minutes.
It was amazing to watch.
I've never seen such an amazing
example of true outlaws.
Honestly, I was blown away.
To witness such a daring display!
I was shaken to my core!
You've inspired me!
I'm going to do my best to become
become an outlaw just like you!
Living by my own rules,
a truly free spirit that answers to nobody!
What is she talking about?
Beats me.
Well, there you have it, so...
if you don't mind...
can I ask what your name is?
Our name...?
You know, like your group name,
or your team name?
Something I can use to remember
your brave exploits today by.
Very well! I completely understand
what you mean!
Wait, Nonomi?!
People call us...
The Masked Swimsuit Gang?!
Wh-whoa... that's so cool!
That's just too cool!
Ho, ho, ho, and once more, ho!
An eye for an eye.
A tooth for a tooth.
We tread a path that none may follow,
and we do so without mercy.
That is our motto!
So... cool!
What on earth are they up to over there...
All right, you've had your fun.
Let's just get out of here already.
Well then, adios for now!
Off we go, galloping into the sunset!
It's still the middle of the afternoon...
"We tread a path that none may follow..."
I'll remember those words for as long as I live!
I can't give up now!
So when do we tell her?
This is hilarious, so not until way later.
Um, so, what about this?
Did they forget to take it with them?
What?!
Oooh!
Does this mean we don't have to skip meals anymore?
"We tread a path that none may follow..."
Maybe I should write it down
and hang it up somewhere.
Miss Aru's been talking about
the Masked Swimsuit Gang ever since we got back.
I wonder when she'll connect the dots...
Boss.
You know the Masked Swimsuit Gang?
They're just the kids from Abydos.
Oh, really?
Huh?!
W-W-W-W-What do you mean?!
Look at her!
She's in shock!
No... no way...!