Yes.
The contents of the report are accurate.
We accept full responsibility for our mistake.
Yes. Yes...
What?! In one week?
Oh, no, not at all. We will take care of it.
Boss, are you planning on
fighting the Abydos kids again?
We already blew all our cash, though.
What's the plan this time?
We're already strapped for cash
because renting this office costs a fortune.
Q-Quiet, you!
A company without a proper office
is no company at all!
If you ask me, I'm perfectly happy to go back
to pitching some tents in the park.
I-I would follow you to the ends of the earth, Miss Aru.
Would you all just be quiet?!
We're taking out a loan.
Huh? I thought you were blacklisted from the bank?
No, I'm not!
I've just been declared a wanted criminal
and had my assets frozen, that's all!
Oh right, that was it!
Just you watch!
We'll finish the mission, whatever it takes!
Thank you for choosing Kaiser Loan!
Your cash payment of 7,883,250 yen
has been duly recorded.
See you again next month!
We made it through another month, huh?
I wonder why they only accept cash.
Good point. It would be much faster to transfer
the money from a bank account instead.
No attacking the transport car, Shiroko.
I know.
Now then, let's begin our regular meeting.
For starters, about the part
we recovered the other day.
I looked into it, and it turns out it did in fact
originate from the Black Market.
The Black Market is a dangerous place
that falls outside the jurisdiction of the GSC.
It's become notorious for its illegal dealings
and being a hotbed for unauthorised club activity.
It appears Problem Solver 68 frequents the area as well.
Problem Solver 68...
The Helmet Gang was one thing,
but now these girls are after our school too.
Given how often we're being raided,
there's gotta be more to the story.
I wonder why they're doing this.
Indeed.
Investigating the connection
might help us discover the truth.
All right, guess that settles it.
Let's have a little field trip!
We got new guns on display. Check 'em out!
Wait, for real?!
That's so wild.
So this is the Black Market.
Look at all these people!
I'm surprised such a large place
flew under the GSC's radar.
Well, you only think that because
we're always holed up in Abydos.
Strange places like this exist all over the world.
Have you been here before, Hoshino?
Nah, this is my first time, too.
From what I hear, every district
has its share of wacky places.
Apparently some schools even have huge aquariums.
I hear they've got whales and stuff!
I'd love to go one of these days.
Yeah. That sounds nice.
Stay sharp, everyone. There's no telling
what could happen out there.
Please be careful.
Sure thing.
Got it.
Quit runnin' already!
P-Please, leave me alone!
As if!
Come on, let's have some fun!
That doesn't sound like it'd be much fun for me, though!
That uniform...
Is she from Trinity?
Get behind me.
Are you all right?
Huh? Oh, uh, yes.
Who the hell are you?
Back off, losers. We got business with the girl!
That chick's from Trinity.
Y'know, the most loaded school in Kivotos?
We're just gonna borrow her for a bit
and ask for a little money in return!
Catch and release. Pretty slick, don't you think?
What do you say? Want in on this?
We'll split the ransom—
No thanks.
That was a close call.
Oh, thank you so much!
My name is Ajitani Hifumi.
Hifumi, huh? Pleasure to meetcha!
But I gotta ask, what brings a high-class girl
from Trinity to this sketchy part of town?
Well, you see...
I'm actually looking for something.
It's no longer being sold in stores,
but I hear you can find it around these parts...
Parts? Like for a tank?!
An illegal firearm, perhaps?
Ooh, maybe a biochemical weapon?
What?
N-No, no, nothing like that!
It's, uhh...
Limited-edition Peroro merch.
Peroro?
Yes, this handsome guy right here!
It's a super-limited-run Peroro plush.
Only one hundred units were ever produced!
Oh, it's from Momo Friends!
I love that franchise!
Peroro's just the cutest!
You like him too?!
Of course!
Oh boy, this topic is way past my time.
By the way, what brings you here?
We're also looking for something.
It's not something that's easy to find,
but we heard it might be here.
I see. Guess we're in the same boat, then.
It looks like your shopping trip
took a rather nasty turn, though.
Well, I mean, I knew this place was bad news.
Now that the GSC is gone, the corporations moved in
and have been up to all kinds of mischief.
It's apparently gotten so out of hand,
they even have their own bank and security now.
W-Wait, that's gotta be highly illegal, right?
I've heard that the security here is especially bad news.
Wow, Hifumi, you sure know your stuff.
Oh, no, I wouldn't say that.
All right, that's settled, then!
We scratched your back, so now it's time you scratch ours
and help us find what we're looking for!
Huh?
Wait, what?
Are you sure we want a loan from these guys?
This is the shady Black Market bank, you know?
Th-The interest rates must be a-astronomical...
Hey, let's be real. Aru won't even pass
the background check anyway!
Sh-Shut it! Of course I'll pass!
Come on.
That's odd. There should be some information
about your illegal part, but I can't find anything.
No transaction records. No storage logs...
It's almost as if someone
went through great lengths to hide it.
So someone is trying to cover it up?
I think so.
The corporations run this place, but even they
shouldn't be able to hide every trace of it.
This isn't normal?
It's more like, why bother going that far?
They're almost flaunting their illegal activities at this point,
so it seems odd that they would try to hide anything.
Take that building, for example.
Even within the Black Market,
that bank is notorious for its shady practices.
Shady?
From what I've heard,
nearly fifteen percent of all the money that funds
criminal activity in Kivotos passes through that bank.
Oh, geez.
The proceeds from crimes like
embezzlement, theft, and kidnappings
are invested into weapons and equipment
to commit more crimes.
It's a vicious cycle.
Wait, wouldn't that mean the bank is complicit?
That's the thing. Even the banks here
are criminal organisations.
That's...
The Market Guard!
The Market Guard?
They're the elite of the security forces here.
They're escorting that vehicle.
Looks like a cash transport.
Wait, isn't that...
The person who always collects our money?
Thank you for your patience.
Here is this month's collection.
Thank you.
Could you please sign here?
Of course.
Wait, Kaiser Loan has ties with that bank?
Did you say Kaiser Loan?!
You know them, Hifumi?
Umm, they're the loan sharks run by
the infamous Kaiser Corporation, right?
Are they a bad company?
Yes.
The Kaiser Group is a conglomerate known
for skirting the line of legality.
They definitely don't sound
like the cleanest business.
Did you borrow money from Kaiser Loan?
Something like that. It's a long story.
So that's why they only accept cash payments.
They must've been trying to avoid leaving a paper trail.
I can't believe the money
was going to a bank for criminals.
You mean our money has been funding
criminal activity this whole time?
W-We don't know that for sure.
We don't have any direct proof that Kaiser Loan
was taking our money to the Black Market bank.
They should have some kind of receipt
that says where the money came from.
If you can get that,
wouldn't that count as evidence?
Oh!
Oh, on second thought, they probably
already took those documents inside,
so it's too late to get them.
We're dealing with a bank that has top-notch security,
even by Black Market standards, so...
Hey, Hoshino.
I think this calls for plan B.
Hm? Plan B?
Oh, that plan!
I agree. That might be just what we need!
Wait, you can't seriously mean...
You're not thinking what I'm thinking, r-right?
Um, I'm sorry, I'm not sure I follow.
It's our only option.
Plan "Bank robbery".
Excuse me?!
Shiroko, hold on! There's gotta be another—
It's okay.
We're just finding evidence of their crimes.
Well, I suppose that's true...
Copy that.
I doubt anything I say would change your minds.
Umm, what's...
Sorry, Hifumi.
I didn't plan far enough ahead,
so I don't have a mask prepared for you.
Wait, why am I a part of this now?!
We couldn't just leave you out in the cold like that!
O-On the contrary, I'd much rather you did!
Here, Hifumi. This one's for you.
W-Wait, we can talk this out!
Nono—
It looks super duper cute on you!
D-Do I really have to do this?
Of course you do, Hifumi.
You promised, remember?
You said you'd help us find what we're looking for.
Oh no...
H-How would I ever explain this to
the Tea Party if they found out?
You'll be A-okay!
We're the good guys here.
And you, Teacher?
I'm in, too.
I can't ignore the chance that your money
is being used for malicious purposes.
Yeah.
All right!
Masked Swimsuit Gang!
Roll out!
Thank you for your patience.
Yes, I've just about run out.
What's the bottom line?
I need money, and I need it now.
I'm terribly sorry, but we are unable
to process your request at this time.
Wait, what? You mean you can't lend us the money?
That is correct.
E-Excuse me!
We have an entire office
and everything! What's the issue?!
Your office is leased.
The only tangible assets you own are firearms.
We can't possibly extend a loan
under these circumstances.
Wait, what?!
If you had collateral to offer or a solid credit history
with our bank, we could extend a loan to you,
but may I suggest you start by finding a day job?
Excuse me?!
Why, you little...
I should just grab the money
and raze this place to the ground.
No, that wouldn't work.
This place is full of Market Guards.
We'd never get away.
I don't have the guts
to make an enemy of the Black Market.
What am I even doing?
I promised myself I would become
the number one outlaw in all of Kivotos.
But look at me now,
agonising over stupid things like bank loans...
This isn't what I wanted.
I wanted to live boldly. To become someone
who lives on their own terms.
A hard-boiled outlaw.
Or at least, that was the dream.
Drop your weapons! Get down on the ground!
A-Are they bank robbers?
Do as we say or you'll eat lead!
Uh, umm... For your own safety,
please stay calm and get on the ground!
Hey, wise guy. She said drop your weapons.
H-Hey, girls...
Make extra sure you don't hurt
any innocent civilians, okay?
Got it.
Right-o. So far, so good.
Let's move on to phase two, shall we?
Come on, Faust. You're our leader,
so give us the word!
Huh?
Wait, what? Y-You mean me? I'm Faust?!
Who else?
Hifumi—I mean, Faust, you're the leader!
In other words, you're our boss!
And while we're at it...
Call me Christina, gals!
Huh? Aren't they those girls?
Yeah, from Abydos.
Sh-Should we beat them up?
No, looks like they're not here for us.
Don't try anything stupid.
That cash transport just now...
Yes, of course. Gold, cash, bonds, anything!
I'll give you whatever you want, so please spare me!
No, we just want the transport logs.
Th-That's so badass!
Who are these people?!
How do they have the guts to hit
a Black Market bank of all places?!
They're making it look so easy.
They must be professionals!
Th-They're so badass!
Now these guys are real outlaws!
Oh dear, I think I'm tearing up!
H-Here it is!
Please, just take it! Don't kill me!
Shiro—I mean, Blue Two.
Have you secured the package?
Uh, yeah. It's just...
All righty. Let's make like a tree and skedaddle!
Come on, gang, we're leaving!
Adios!
I-I'm glad no one was hurt. Goodbye!
A-After them!
Seal off the perimeter! Notify the Market Guards!
Y-You go, outlaws!
You're out of the hot zone.
Good work, everyone.
Heck yeah! We did it!
I feel my actions as a teacher are questionable at best.
Shiroko, you got the transport logs?
Yeah.
Whoa! What the heck is all this?!
Shiroko, you went for the cash instead?!
No. The documents are right here.
Yowza. There's easily a hundred million in there.
Nice! Let's bring it back!
Serika, wait.
Why? This would really help us pay back—
We can't do that, Serika!
Why the heck not?!
We shed blood, sweat, and tears to earn this money.
And it was all going to that bank run by criminals!
True, if we hadn't done anything,
this money would've been used to fund more crime.
Exactly! What's wrong with stealing from criminals?
I'm with Serika here.
It's money that was funding criminal activity.
It'd be better if we used it for good instead.
And besides, this much money would go a huge way
towards paying off the school's debt!
Are you sure you're okay with that?
What do you think, Shiroko?
No point in asking.
You would say no.
Huh?
Got me there, Shiroko.
Guess I've rubbed off on you after all.
What we need is documentation. Not cash.
If we cross this line because
we're up against criminals,
then what about next time?
Or the time after that?
If we start getting used to this way of thinking,
I think one day we're gonna
do something we'll come to regret.
And I couldn't bear to watch
my cute little juniors lose their way like that.
If this is how we wanted to do things,
we coulda just used Nonomi's
fancy schmancy gold card from the get-go.
But you said we shouldn't...
Oh! I remember now!
If we pay off the debt with someone else's money,
we'll lose the Abydos we were trying to protect.
That's right.
Let's take just the documents.
Is that okay?
Yes!
I can't say I know what you're going through,
but I feel like taking this cash would only
lead to bigger issues later down the line.
I'm sure it's already caused
its fair share of trouble, too.
Wait right there!
Oh, uh, don't worry! I'm not here to pick a fight!
What's she doing here?
Do we shoot her?
She says she doesn't wanna fight,
so I'd rather not just blast her.
Do you know each other?
Yes, you could say that.
Um, I watched you rob the bank earlier!
You were in and out in a flash.
I was gripped!
True outlaws like you come once in a lifetime!
Honestly, I was blown away.
That kind of display is a rarity these days!
I was shaken to my core!
You've inspired me!
I'll keep working hard to become a free spirit like you,
unshackled by any rules or laws!
What's she going on about?
Beats me.
Well, there you have it, so...
If you would be so kind,
could you please tell me your name?
Our name?
Like, you've got to have a team name,
or a calling card, right?
Something I can use to remember
your brave exploits today.
Of course! I totally get what you mean!
N-Nonomi, what are you doing?!
We're known as...
the Masked Swimsuit Gang!
The Masked Swimsuit Gang?!
Wh-Whoa! That's so badass!
Ho, ho, ho, and one more ho!
An eye for an eye.
A tooth for a tooth.
We tread a path none may follow,
and do so without mercy.
That's our motto!
H-Holy smokes. That's awesome!
What on earth is going on over there?
All right, you've had your fun.
Let's just get out of here already.
Well, then. Adios!
Off we go, riding off into the sunset!
It's still the middle of the day.
"A path none may follow..."
I'm gonna burn those words into my soul!
I can't give up now!
So, when do we tell her?
This is hilarious, so definitely not right now.
U-Um, what about this?
It looks like they left it behind.
Oooh!
What?!
Does this mean we won't have to skip meals anymore?
"A path none may follow..."
Maybe I should write it down and frame it.
Miss Aru has been talking about nothing but
the Masked Swimsuit Gang ever since we got back.
Think she'll ever connect the dots?
Hey, Boss.
About that Masked Swimsuit Gang.
They're the kids from Abydos.
Ah, I see.
Wh-Wh-What do you mean?!
Oh, man! You should see your face!
No... No way!