Yes
As stated in the report,
we underestimated them
Yes
Within the week?!
N-No! We can do it
You can count on us
Boss, are we going after
the Abydos students again?
But with what money?
We used up all our funds
And paying rent on this office
takes up whatever we have left
Shut up!
Every decent company
needs an office space!
Personally, I liked our tent
in the park from before
I-I don't care where
as long as I'm with the boss
Shut up already!
I'll take out a loan
What?
But you're on every bank's blacklist
No, I'm not!
My accounts are just frozen
because I'm a wanted criminal!
Ah, right!
Just you watch
I won't let our
commission end like this!
The sky blue archive!
I pedal on my bike seeking new sights
We'll break the monotony,
no longer trapped in place
Daydreaming on the rooftop,
gazing at a sky so blue
Those clouds like whales are always changing
We'll embrace a past that can't be altered
Sharing juice in this world made of sand
Is a taste so divine
If I were here alone, here without all of you
I couldn't laugh, I couldn't cry
A fateful coterie
Even if the world's memories blow away
like grains of sand one day
The sky, sea, wind, and you,
our youth will never end
It's easy to see why we protect what we do
Because this is the only place where we belong
Thank you for doing business
with Kaiser Loans
Your total was 7,883,250 yen, in cash
Receipt confirmed
Then, until next month!
Safe for one more month⋯
But why does Kaiser Loans
only accept cash payments?
Good point
A bank transfer payment
would be faster and easier
Shiroko! You can't attack
that van, okay?
Yes, I know
So, let's start
the daily meeting now
(Foreclosure Task Force Daily Meeting)
So, let's start the daily meeting now
First, regarding the
part we found⋯
As expected, it was traded
on the Black Market
A lot of banned contraband
in Kivotos can be found there,
as well as clubs unauthorized
by the General Student Council,
so it's dangerous there
Problem Solver 68 seems
to frequent that market as well
Problem Solver 68
They're just like the Helmet Gangsters,
trying to take over our school
There must be something going on
for everyone to come after us like this
It's really concerning
Yes, investigating the connections
between these incidents
might be a good idea
Okay, It's settled then
Let's check it out!
Get the newest guns here!
- Really?
- Isn't it amazing?
So this is the Black Market
It's really packed
This place isn't controlled
by the General Student Council,
yet it's unbelievably massive
I know we hardly ever leave Abydos,
but outside our campus,
there's lots of weird places
Have you been here before?
No, it's my first time as well
But other schools have weird stuff too
I've heard of a giant water tank
called an aquarium
I'd like to see it one day
Sounds nice
Everyone, there's no telling
what could happen there
So please be careful
-Yes
- Okay
Stop right there!
Please stop chasing me!
- No can do
- We told you to come with us!
But I have nothing to say to you!
This uniform is⋯
from Trinity?
- I'll handle it
- Huh?
Are you okay?
Y-Yes
Who are you guys?
All we want is that girl
She's from Trinity General School,
the richest school in all of Kivotos
We're gonna kidnap her
and demand a hefty ransom
Kidnap first, negotiate later
It's a good way to make money
We can team up
if you're interested
We're willing to split the ransom money by—
Not interested
That was close
Thank you very much
My name is Ajitani Hifumi
Hifumi, you said? Nice to meet you
Anyway, what's a Trinity
student doing here?
Actually,
I'm looking for something
It's been discontinued,
but I heard they still
sell it here
Tanks?
Or illegal guns?
Or chemical weapons?
No, no!
It's⋯
Limited edition Peroro merch!
Peroro?
Yes, this one
This limited edition Peroro doll,
with only 100 ever made
It's from the Momo Friends series,
right?
I love them!
Isn't Peroro so cute?
You think so too?
Yes!
What are they talking about?
This old-timer doesn't get it
But why are you all here?
We're looking for something too
Something very hard to get,
but we heard it's sold here
I see
Same as me
You just came here to buy a doll,
but ended up in such a mishap
Well, I knew this was
a dangerous place
It's beyond the control
of the General Student Council,
so a lot of companies work
outside the law here
They even have their own
financial institutions and security forces
And all of these organizations
are illegal and
unauthorized, right?
That's why we should
avoid any security here
Hifumi, you sure know a lot
No, not that much
Okay! It's settled then
As a reward for saving you,
can you help us find
what we came here for?
H-HUH?!
Are we really going
to take out a loan from here?
This is the Black Market Bank, you know
Th-The interest rates must be crazy
Well, that is if Aru even
gets approved for a loan
Sh-Shut up!
Of course I'll get approved
Let's go in
About the parts
you're looking for,
(Taiyaki) there should be some
kind of trail, but it's so hard to follow
Like sales channels
or storage records⋯
It's as if someone's
deliberately hidden all of it
That's what it seems like, at least
Deliberately hidden it?
Yes
Even the companies
that dominate this market
don't normally do this
Is it that unusual?
It's more like,
"Why go to such lengths?"
Everyone here openly
engages in illegal activities,
so it's even weirder that
they're hiding things
Even that building over there
That's the Black Market Bank,
notorious even in this place
Black Market Bank?
According to rumors,
nearly 15% of crime-related
financial assets in Kivotos
flow through that bank
They get money from crimes
like embezzlement,
robbery, and kidnapping,
and then use it to buy
weapons for more crimes
And the vicious circle
continues endlessly
Which means that bank is
facilitating criminal activities
Exactly
Here, even the banks
are criminal organizations
That's⋯
the Black Market Guard!
Black Market Guard?
They're the best security
organization here in the market
They are escorting that van
A cash transport vehicle
Isn't that⋯?
The bank clerk who
collects our payments?
Thank you for waiting
Here is this month's collection
Well done
Sign here
Okay
Kaiser Loans is colluding
with the Black Market Bank
K-Kaiser Loans?
Hifumi, you know them?
Well⋯
That's the loan shark company
run by the notorious
Kaiser Corporation, right?
Are they a bad company?
Yes, the Kaiser Group may be
a diversified company,
but it walks a fine line between
legality and illegality
That doesn't sound good
Did you all take out
a loan from Kaiser?
It's a long story
Then, the reason
they only accept cash is
so they won't leave a paper trail?
I can't believe our money's been
going into the Black Market Bank
Which means we've been
funding criminal activities!
W-We can't be sure yet
There's no evidence
that Kaiser Loans has been
depositing our money there
You get a receipt whenever
you make a payment, right?
You'll have your evidence
if you find their receipt records
But all those documents
must be in their vaults already,
so we've hit a dead end
The Black Market Bank has
the strongest security system
in the Black Market
Hey, Hoshino
There's no other option
Huh? What option?
Oh, that one!
Right, that should
definitely work
By "that" you don't mean⋯
You're not talking about
what I'm thinking of, right?
U-Um, I don't understand
There's only one thing we can do
Rob the bank
Whaaat?
Shiroko, wait
There has to be another way!
Don't worry, We're only trying to
find evidence of their crimes
Is that really what this is?
Understood
You wouldn't listen
even if I tried to stop you
Well, but that's:⋯
Sorry, Hifumi
I should've thought ahead
and made you a mask too
I'm going too?!
We're good people!
We couldn't just abandon you!
No, it's okay! I don't mind at all!
Hifumi, you can wear this
N-No, please wait
Yup, A perfect fit!
Does this mean
I really am going with you?
What are you talking about, Hifumi?
Didn't you promise
to help us out today?
How will I⋯
ever be able to face
the student council again?
It's fine!
We're not doing anything wrong
And you, Sensei?
I'm in too
If your money is being
used for criminal activities,
I can't accept that
- Hmm
- Yes
Well then,
Masked Swimsuit Gang,
let's go!
Sorry to keep you waiting
Yes, you should be
So am I approved?
We need this money ASAP.
I'm afraid you'll need
to look elsewhere
Wait just one second!
You won't give us a loan?!
- That's right
- Wait!
We even have an office
Why not?
You rent your office,
and your only
assets are firearms
We can't offer you
a loan with just this
If you had
bankable assets or good credit,
we could offer you a loan
So why don't you try
getting a part-time job?
Huh?!
Th-That really pisses me off
I ought to smash everything
and rob them blind!
No, I can't
The Black Market Guards are here
In the end, it really is hopeless
I don't have the guts to
pick a fight with the Black Market
What is this?
I'm so pathetic
I resolved to become
the greatest outlaw
in all of Kivotos
But now I'm being stymied
with trivial matters
like a loan approval
This isn't what I dreamed of
A hard-boiled outlaw
who fears nothing,
and isn't bound by anything--
That's who I wanted to be
Everyone drop your weapons
and get on the ground!
B-Bank robbers?
Do as you're told,
or I'll send you to hell!
Umm,
please get on the ground,
so you won't get hurt
We told you to drop your weapons
Um, everyone
Be careful not to hurt
any ordinary citizens
-Yes
- Okay
Now then, since everything's
going according to plan,
is it time for the next step?
Boss Faust, give us the command
Is Faust me?
Of course
Hifumi— No, Faust is our leader
You are the boss, And I am⋯
Christina!
Huh? Aren't they⋯
Abydos students?
Sh-Should we counterattack?
No, we don't seem
to be their targets
Everyone, don't even
think about resisting
- The delivery van that just came in⋯
- I understand
We'll give you everything!
Gold, cash, bonds!
No, all we want is
the collection records
O-Oh my, Who are they?
They have the guts to
rob the Black Market Bank!
What amazing skills
They're the ultimate professionals
C-Cool! I think I have a crush!
These are real outlaws!
Oh, I think I'm going to cry
H-Here you go
Please spare my life
Shiro— I mean, Blue 2
Did you get the goods?
Yes, but⋯
Okay, let's run
- Everyone, retreat
- Adios!
No one seems to be hurt, so⋯
Goodbye
C-Catch them!
Block the roads and
contact the Black Market Guards!
Nice villainy!
Well done on getting through
the blockades, everyone!
Yay! We made it!
Is it really okay for a
teacher to be doing this?
Shiroko, do you
have the records?
Here
What is all this?!
You just stole all
the money, Shiroko?!
No, Here are the
documents we wanted
This must be at least
a hundred million
Perfect! Let's take it all!
Serika, wait
What is it? With this, our debt⋯
We shouldn't do that, Serika
Why not?
We worked so hard
to earn this money,
and it just ended up
in that Black Market Bank!
She's right, And if we had
left this money there,
it could've been used by
criminals to buy more guns
Exactly! What's wrong with
stealing money from bad people?
I agree with Serika
This is dirty money,
so why can't we spend
it for a good cause?
And this amount of money
will really help with our debt!
Is that really okay with you?
Shiroko, what do you think?
Why're you asking me?
Hoshino will say no regardless
That's my Shiroko
You know me too well
We only need the documents,
not the money
If we justify stealing
from criminals now,
what about the next time?
And after that?
If this becomes a habit,
when we're in another tough spot,
we might become the criminals,
and say it was inevitable
As an old-timer,
I can't let you cute
youngins do that
If we end up resorting to this,
it'd have been better
to use Nonomi's glorious
gold card from the get-go
But Hoshino, you said no to⋯
I see
We need to pay off
our debt the right way,
or we won't be Abydos
High School anymore
Exactly
Then let's go back with
just the documents we need
What do you all say?
Yes!
I don't exactly know
your circumstances,
but money like this will
only bring you more trouble
It's like a cursed item
Wait just a moment!
D-Don't worry
I'm not your enemy
- Why is she here?
- Should we shoot her?
We can't shoot her
when she means no harm
Do you know her?
Yes, just a little
Well⋯
I saw you guys at the bank
Robbing and retreating
so efficiently⋯
It's rare to meet
such amazing outlaws
To be honest, I was totally shocked
I really admire how
bold you all were
I'll do my absolute best
to not be bound
by laws or rules,
and become a truly free spirit
That's the kind of outlaw I want to be!
What is she talking about?
Dunno
So if you don't mind,
can you tell me your name?
Name?
I mean the name
of your organization or team
I want to always remember
your wonderful deeds today
Okay, I understand what you're saying
N-Nonomi⋯!
People call us
the Masked Swimsuit Gang
The Masked Swimsuit Gang?
What a cool and chic name!
An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth
Forsake mercy
and walk the path of chaos
That's our motto
C-Coool!
What are they doing?
That's enough, Let's go back
Adios, then!
We're riding off into the sunset!
The sun hasn't set yet
"Walk the path of chaos,"
I'll engrave those words on my soul!
I'll keep working hard!
When should we tell her?
It'll be funnier to tell her later
U-Um⋯
Did they leave that behind?
Does this mean we won't
have to skip meals anymore?
"Walk the path of chaos,"
Maybe I should write it down?
Aru's been talking nonstop
about the Masked Swimsuit Gang
When will she realize the truth?
Boss,
about that Masked Swimsuit Gang⋯
They're the Abydos students
Oh, is that so?
What did you say?!
Aru is totally shocked
N-No way!
I'll take a window seat on this journey to find
the place where my heart belongs
So I can see beyond this sorrow chasing me
We were losing track of time without ever knowing why
With all those laughs we shared⋯
Even if⋯those moments were just ordinary
Those days⋯
One more time, one time more,
Knowing they won't come around again!
If only I could stay as resolute and beautiful
As the moon hanging in the bright noon sky
Would that let me finally forgive
All those regrets we made so willfully?
We only recognize the important things
Once they're gone and lost out of sight
We stretch up to the moon in the bright noon sky
Even though it will always be beyond our reach
Oh, those unforgettable, beautiful days⋯