Yes, this is Problem Solver 68.
Rikuhachima speaking.
Yes, of course.
Background checks, armed security—
There's no job too big for us.
We do the crime if you got the dime.
Of course.
Consider it done.
Your job is in good hands at Problem Solver 68.
Ayane, isn't this...
Yes.
It's a part we recovered from the wreckage of
one of the Helmet Gang's armoured vehicles the other day.
I did some research, and I found that
this specific model is currently banned from use.
Where could the Helmet Gang have
gotten hold of something illegal like that?
From the Black Market, maybe?
Even if they did, I feel it would be difficult for them
to secure enough units for all those vehicles.
Sure makes you wonder who's backing them.
If we could trace this part back to its supplier,
we may be able to find a lead on
who's orchestrating this.
Right. It might also shed some light on why
they're targeting our school specifically.
Yeah.
With that out of the way, let's get back
to our regular meeting, everyone.
Our teacher is present this time,
so make sure you're on your best behaviour.
C'mon! Don't paint us as troublemakers or anything!
Pleasure to have ya, Teach.
Happy to be here.
Let's start with our plans going forward.
If you have a suggestion, raise your hand.
Oh! Me!
Yes, first-year Kuromi Serika.
As the treasurer of the Task Force,
I'd like to point out that our school
is on the verge of bankruptcy!
We can only earn so much
from bounties and part-time gigs.
We gotta go big or go home!
Go big? Could you elaborate?
I'm glad you asked!
Rejected.
Serika, that's a pyramid scheme.
You're not gonna profit from that.
N-No way...
I already bought two bracelets...
Our little Serika is so gullible.
I could just gobble you up.
Moving on.
Any other suggestions?
Ooh! Me, me, me!
Oh, go ahead, President Hoshino.
I have a bad feeling about this.
Upsy daisy.
One problem clearly overshadows the others:
Look around. The entire student body
is currently here in this room!
Right.
A school is only as strong as its student body.
So, our number one priority should be
to raise our student numbers!
Astute observation, but how would we do that?
It's elementary, Ayane.
We abduct students from
another school's school bus!
Excuse me?!
You want to go busjacking?!
Either they sign the transfer papers,
or they'd better make themselves comfy!
Boom! Instant influx of new faces.
That's genius.
So, who's our target? Trinity?
Or maybe Gehenna? Millenium?
Rejected!
What?
Put yourselves in their shoes!
Would you happily sign those documents
if you were kidnapped?!
Furthermore, their school's prefects
would have our heads!
Yeah, figures that's a no-go.
I beg you, please at least try to take this seriously.
Hey, Ayane. I have an even better idea.
Go ahead, second-year Sunaookami Shiroko.
We rob the bank.
I'm sorry?!
Now we're robbing banks?!
It's guaranteed to get results.
Let's hit the First Central Bank downtown.
I've already found the vault
and know the guard patrol routes,
and I've even figured out the route
the transport car usually takes.
Also, I got masks.
Oh, wow!
Did you make these yourself, Shiroko?
We could join the WWE with these!
I see you came prepared, Shiroko.
Yeah.
Hoo boy, now we're talking.
Now this is what I call "go big or go home".
Right, Serika?
Leave me the heck outta this!
Absolutely not! Criminal activity is off the table!
Pout all you want, Shiroko, but no means no!
Come on, everyone.
We need good, reasonable ideas.
Oh! Me next!
Yes, yes. Go ahead, second-year Izayoi Nonomi.
And please, no scams or illegal activities.
You got it!
My idea is neither a crime nor a scam!
It's completely clean and 100% reliable!
Nonomi...
Idols!The secret is... idols!
We become school idols!
Idols?
Yes!
The heart and soul of any
school revival arc hinges on idols!
If all of us break into the pop industry...
Rejected!
But I already came up with a pose and everything.
Is anyone taking this seriously?!
We're not getting anywhere like this!
Hey, hey, Ayane.
Why don't we let the teacher decide?
Who, me?
All right then, Teach,
if you had to pick one of our ideas,
which one would it be?
Um... Well...
Bank robbery. All the way.
Oh, come on. Hijacking a bus is clearly better.
I much prefer the idol idea myself!
Well... I-If I had to choose, maybe the ido—
You guys...
Would you please
quit messing around!
Oh dear, Ayane's mad...
Target secured.
Yeah.
Hey, Aru.
Did we really have to go that far
just to recover some stolen goods?
Call me as "Boss" while we're
on the job, Chief of Staff Mutsuki.
You've got to break some eggs to make an omelette.
We can't go fretting over every little egg.
We're outlaws. It comes with the territory.
Aw, Aru's doing her thing again.
Hey, Boss.
Wh-What is it, Department Head Kayoko?
Just to confirm, the client's one condition
was that the target be unharmed, wasn't it?
Yes, of course.
What about it?
Hmm?
Wh-Wh-Wha?
Boss, does this mean...
Wh-Wh-Wh-Wha—
We can kiss our payout goodbye.
What do we do?!
Relax, Ayane. We're sorry, okay?
It's my treat, so stop being angry, okay?
I'm not angry.
Here, let's wipe that cute little mouth.
Would you stop babying me?
Ayane, want more chashu?
Yes.
Welcome!
How many in your party?
Um, c-could I please ask how much
the ch-cheapest item on the m-menu is?
That'd be the Shiba Seki Ramen at 580 yen.
It's our signature dish. I highly recommend it!
Oh, um, th-thank you!
Miss Aru, their signature ramen is apparently 580 yen.
Finally, a place where something costs less than 600!
See? Where there's a will, there's a way.
Trust in the process!
Welcome.
Table for four? I'll show you to your table.
Oh, no, no.
We're only ordering for one,
so we'll take it to-go.
You may as well be comfortable.
We have plenty of tables.
Aw, you're so sweet.
If you insist, we'll gladly take you up on that.
Oh, while we're at it, could you get us
four pairs of chopsticks? Thanks.
Huh? Y-You're not planning on splitting
a single bowl between the four of you, right?
S-Sorry! I'm s-so sorry we're poor!
Oh, no. That's nothing worth apologising over!
No, I mean it! Anyone without money
is just a waste of oxygen!
I don't even deserve to be alive!
I'm lower than dirt.
I'm sorry for being the scum of the earth!
Haruka, you're making a scene.
Don't say that!
Being poor is nothing to be ashamed of!
Huh?
Don't you agree, Boss?
Darn straight! Every dog will have its day.
You girls are students, aintcha?
Y-Yes, that's right.
But y'all still gathered up enough
to share a bowl o' my ramen.
I'm right chuffed!
Just sit tight, y'hear?
Please, have a seat.
O-Okay.
I feel like he got the wrong idea about us.
Yeah, not like we're usually this broke.
But if we want to point fingers,
Aru was the one who blew all our cash.
Not only did that last job end up being a complete bust,
but now we've sunk almost all our money
into hiring goons for our next job.
But you see, I made sure we had enough for ramen!
This was well within my calculations.
But still, is our next target really so dangerous
that it warrants all these precautions?
Well...
I bet Aru doesn't even know herself!
That's why she spent all our cash—
because she's too chicken!
Who are you calling chicken?!
Failure is never an option.
We make full use of every resource available to us.
That's Problem Solver 68's motto!
First I've heard of it.
Oh, come on. She clearly made it up on the spot.
Q-Quiet, you!
Thank you for waiting!
Wh-What on earth?!
Look at all that ramen!
This is enough to feed ten people!
Th-This has to be a mistake.
I-I'm sorry, but we couldn't possibly afford this.
This is exactly what you ordered, right?
One regular-sized Shiba Seki ramen for 580 yen.
Isn't that right, Boss?
Had a li'l mishap in the kitchen, y'see?
No use in lettin' it go to waste.
I can't say I saw this coming.
We won't let this goodwill go to waste.
Come on, Aru! Let's dig in already!
Yes, let's.
Thanks for the food!
Yummy!
Heh.
I know, right?
Isn't the ramen here just the best?
I can tell. I've had my fair share
of delightful dishes from many restaurants,
but ramen this good is hard to come by.
Are those uniforms Gehenna's?
You're a long way from home.
Oh, uh, yes.
We're regulars here.
Really?
I'm jealous.
Hey, Kayoko, is it just me, or...
It's not.
They're from Abydos.
I didn't expect to run into
so many kindred spirits out here.
Life sure is full of pleasant surprises, wouldn't you say?
Yeah, you may be right.
I don't think she's put two and two together.
Should we tell her?
Nah, this is way funnier.
All right, take care.
I hope your job goes well.
Good luck revitalising your school.
I'll be rooting for you!
Bye, now!
What great kids, huh?
Hey, Boss.
What is it, Department Head Kayoko?
Did those uniforms look familiar to you?
Huh? No? What about them?
Those were Abydos students.
Huh?
Wh-Wh-Wha—
They were?!
You should see the look on your face!
B-But doesn't that mean they're our targets?
Should I go back and eliminate them?
Way too late for that.
We're gonna raid them in a bit anyway,
so save the fun for then, Haruka.
R-Right.
No way... There's no way...
Those sweethearts are our targets?
"No morals, no mercy."
"We do the crime if you got the dime."
Wasn't that our motto?
No point overthinking it now.
I-I mean, that's true, but...
This job's really tearing you apart, huh?
Come on, Aru. Get a grip!
You're the boss of this company!
Let's do it!
Ah, so that's what you were up to yesterday.
Yes! And now we're friends
with some students from Gehenna.
They were really wowed by the boss's ramen.
They were!
I'm not surprised to hear that. It's great.
By the way, what were they like?
It sounded like they had their own company—
A security camera captured an armed group
advancing on the school from the south.
Is it the Helmet Gang again?
It's not them.
They look like a group of private mercenaries!
Are you all prepared?
Of course.
We'll fight who you want,
but we're clocking out on the dot.
Especially since you were stingy with our pay.
Leave the fine print for later!
Let's go! Prepare to assault Abydos High School!
Yes, ma'am.
Aren't those the girls we met at Shiba Seki Ramen?
Nonomi?
Teach, those are the kids from Gehenna
we were talking about earlier.
Huh?
You traitors!
We give you an extra large serving of ramen,
and this is how you repay us?!
We really did appreciate it,
but that was then, and this is now.
Right now, we're on the clock.
Business is business.
Once we take on a job,
we see it to completion.
Exactly. That's how Problem Solver 68 operates!
I see. So you're fixers.
Come on! There's more than enough normal,
clean part-time jobs students can do!
We're not some piddling part timers!
We're first-class entrepreneurs!
We even have proper titles!
I'm the boss.
She's the chief of staff.
And she's the department head.
This really isn't helping your case, you know?
Who hired you?
That's confidential.
Then I'll just have to make you talk.
We're just doing business.
Don't take it personally.
Come on, everyone, let's do this!
Right!
Let's get this over with.
With you on that one.
Just give up and let us have your school!
That's not going to happen!
Kayoko, she's all yours!
Huh?
Good going, Mutsuki.
Drop your weapon, now!
Serika!
I'm good! Don't worry about me!
The next one won't miss.
Whoopsie!
Detonating C4.
Detonating claymore.
Shiroko!
I'm okay.
Whew, in the nick of time.
It's not looking good.
Try this on for size!
They're tougher than you'd think.
Keep going! Show them who's boss!
Even if we can hold them off for now,
they'll eventually overwhelm us with numbers.
We have to make a move!
Girls! I have a plan.
Will you hear me out?
Teacher?
Shiroko. I need you to do something for me.
Okay.
I imagine they're just about to break.
Keep up the fire until they surrender!
Here I come!
Wh-What the heck?
Are they just getting desperate?
Oof!
Oww!
We're done letting you do whatever you want!
Stop causing problems for us!
Huh? Huh?!
Miss Aru!
Haruka?!
They're rushing us?
Their goal must be...
Boss! Watch out!
Huh? For what?
Don't tell me...
What?!
Boss!
Aru!
We're Problem Solver 68!
We took on the job, so we'll finish it!
Give up and hand over your school!
No can do.
Phew, time to go home.
Good luck. We're clocking out.
Huh?
Welp, done for the day.
Yeah.
W-Wait a second!
We're so close to winning!
We're not doing overtime, so...
The rest ain't our problem. Have fun.
I'm beat.
Wanna go grab some burgers?
I'm down!
What are you getting?
Well, they're mercenaries.
Their loyalty stops when the money does.
Looks like they all left.
That's a loss.
Well, aren't we in a pickle.
What now, Aru? Wanna bail?
You haven't seen the last of us, you hear me?!
Come on, Aru, you sound
like a B-movie villain right now!
Shut up! We're running away!
—I mean, retreatShut up! We're run—I mean, retreating!n away
Miss Aru, wait for me!
Peace.
Well, they sure were interesting.
What in the world was all that about?
Beats me.
I'm starving.
Well, we're just about done here.
Why don't we go find something to eat?
I'm in!
Your treat, right, Teacher?
What?!
C-Could I discuss this with my wallet first?
You're the best!
Pathetic.
It appears those Abydos High School students
are more persistent than our data suggested.
The essence of data is all about change.
But rest assured.
I'll isolate the cause.