Hoshino's cell phone?
Yes, I'd like you to
use it to track her down
Understood
Please wait
How did it go?
No luck
I accessed the General Student
Council's central network
But I couldn't determine her current location
Really?
But we need a lead
In that case⋯
Come in
Who is it?
Could it be Hoshino?
(Sensei's Office)
What's this?
The sky blue archive!
I pedal on my bike seeking new sights
We'll break the monotony,
no longer trapped in place
Daydreaming on the rooftop,
gazing at a sky so blue
Those clouds like whales are always changing
We'll embrace a past that can't be altered
Sharing juice in this world made of sand
Is a taste so divine
If I were here alone, here without all of you
I couldn't laugh, I couldn't cry
A fateful coterie
Even if the world's memories blow away
like grains of sand one day
The sky, sea, wind, and you,
our youth will never end
It's easy to see why we protect what we do
Because this is the only place where we belong
Is this the place?
This is definitely the right floor⋯
I've been expecting you, Sensei
I wanted to speak face-to-face
at least once
The General Student Council
president's inscrutable advocate⋯
Sensei, from Schale's
Federal Investigation Club
Don't worry
We don't intend to fight you
We want to work with you
You see, a small school
like Abydos is no problem for us
But you, Sensei, you're different
We're very wary of you
Who are you?
Ah, yes, I haven't introduced myself
For now, you can call me
Black Suit
I prefer that name
We're very similar, you and I.
Similar?
Yes, we're similar in that
neither of us is from Kivotos
In fact, my people are from
a different realm altogether
Gematria
You may call us that
To put it in terms you'll understand,
you could say it's my organization
Gematria prefers to
observe, explore, and study
In that way, we remain
just as inscrutable as you
Now before we discuss
any more, I must ask⋯
Are you willing to work with us?
I refuse.
What do you seek in
Kivotos that makes you
so quick to reject
our knowledge?
I'm here to get Hoshino back
You have no right
to make such a demand.
(Name, Advisor)
She is no longer an Abydos student
You're wrong
Didn't you receive her withdrawal letter?
I saw it, yes
Then you already know
There's nothing you can do, Sensei
That's not true
You see⋯
I haven't signed it yet
(Name, Advisor)
Which means Hoshino's still part
of the Foreclosure Task Force
She's still the vice president
of Abydos High School
And she's still my student
I see, As their teacher, you must sign
all withdrawals to finalize them
How irritating
You⋯
You tricked Hoshino and the others
You crushed their spirits
and made them suffer
Yes, that's exactly right
If you must define us by our actions,
then we are undoubtedly evil
Nonetheless, we have
played by the rules
I hope that's clear
We are not to blame for
the disaster that struck Abydos
A sandstorm of that magnitude,
though rare, is not unheard of
It's completely natural
It only follows that, as people die of thirst,
someone should appear to sell them water
It's all part of the process
And is it natural for that water
to cost them everything they have?
Yes, It's common practice
That's the way of this world
The haves exploit the have-nots
The weak do not decide their fate
Sensei
If you relinquish Hoshino,
we'll protect Abydos for you
and restore its former glory,
so its students can be carefree
It's what Hoshino would want
Even if you could do that,
my students would never agree to it
Why are you determined to oppose us?
You're powerless
You have no means to fight us
That may be so
But if someone needs help, I'll fight,
no matter how great the opponent
If they keep calling out,
eventually someone will answer
I'm determined to prove that
That's absurd
You're here, and those
kids still ended up alone
At least
I heard them
I heard their voices
Can't you just ignore them?
This isn't really your problem
I refuse
Why?
Why? Why? Why? Why? Why?
Why? Why? Why? Why?
I don't understand
Why do you refuse?
Those kids suffered so much
And no adult took responsibility
So you're going to do it for them?
You're not even their family
You're right, I'm not
family—or anything like it
Pure chance brought me to Abydos
And chance brought me to those kids
It's as simple as that
But so what?
You want a reason?
It's because they asked for my help
And that's enough
That makes you a responsible adult?
Yes
When kids laugh, you laugh with them
When they're sad, you stay by their side
When they're in trouble, you help
That's what adults do
You couldn't be more wrong
Adults mold society to their vision
They make the rules
They define common sense
They determine what's extraordinary
They use power
to rule the powerless
They use knowledge
to control the ignorant
They use strength
to dominate the weak
That's what adults do
I don't understand
You could have ruled Kivotos
The immense power and
authority this city affords,
the Mystics who reside within,
all of it was in your grasp,
even if only temporarily
Yet, you did not hesitate to discard it
Truth, secrets,
power, money, strength
You abandoned it all for nothing, Why?
Even if I told you,
you'd never understand
Then this negotiation is over, Sensei
It's too bad, I like you
But it can't be helped
You'll find Hoshino in a lab
at the Kaiser PMC base
in the Abydos Desert
"Mimesis” revealed the Mystics' other side:
Terror itself
We suspect a living
student could harness it
Hoshino was to be our test subject
You suspect?
Since negotiations have failed,
we will be unable to confirm it
I regret that we must retreat now
- What about Hoshino?
- Do as you wish
Take her
If you can get into the base, that is
And if the Director allows it
It was nice talking to you
Let's meet again someday
I wish you some small
measure of luck.
(Abydos Foreclosure Task Force)
A lab at the Kaiser PMC base?
Yes, I'm sure
Hoshino's there
To think she's being
held in such a place⋯
-We can't waste any time
- Let's rescue her
Right
But wait a moment
What should we say
when we find Hoshino?
That's not as important as—
- We should scold her
- Huh?
She broke her promise
and should be punished
Thoroughly
We should scold her
We'll tell her, "Welcome back!”
And she'll say, "I'm home,”
How embarrassing!
It's like a cheesy youth drama!
Like we're living some
pure, innocent school story
That's not our style!
I'm going to say it
whether Serika does or not
Me too, even if it is embarrassing⋯
Do whatever you want
But I'll never say
something that corny
Okay, but before that, right now—
Right now,
we can't beat them on our own
Then we need to find help
Problem Solver 68?
Yes, they've helped us before but⋯
About that⋯
It's been a while, everyone
How have you been, Hifumi?
Good, thanks to you
I'm sorry, I wanted to visit you first—
Huh?
Where's Hoshino?
Well, you see⋯
So⋯
That's what happened
Yes, we should've caught it sooner
and stopped Hoshino
But we were just as helpless
So then your visit today has
something to do with Hoshino?
That's right
We need Trinity's help to rescue her
I'll talk to the Tea Party
What should I do?
What do you think, Nagisa?
Which one should I choose?
A strawberry cream shortcake
pairs perfectly with the tea
But I can't give up this Mont Blanc
Well, Nagisa⋯
The Abydos students saved me once
So⋯
That Kaiser PMC company is sure to be
a bad influence on our students
- Then will you help them—
- However,
with the treaty signing so near,
we can't afford to be reckless
Can you give us some time?
So they're on hold?
I'm sorry for suggesting this
I knew it wouldn't be easy
It's so hard to get
another school's help
We can't give up
True
But the next place
might not help either
Still, we can't give up
It'll be all right
I'm really sorry it's just me
It's okay
I wish Chinatsu could be here too
But our school has its own issues
Thanks for working so hard, Chinatsu
Sorry I'm late
- Would you like a drink?
- Huh?
Th-Thank you
But that's mine⋯
I apologize for making you wait
- But everything's finally sorted⋯
- Excuse me
I'm sorry to disturb your rest,
but there's a problem in the cafeteria
I see, Thank you so much
I'm sorry once again
Enjoy your stay
Is she always running around like that?
Actually, today's better than usual
Anyway,
Where were we?
The head prefect's busy
You can't see her
But⋯
Tell you what
Get down on your knees
and lick my feet like—
Wh-What are you doing?!
Don't you have a shred
of dignity?! Or propriety?!
This is an emergency!
He's staring straight at me⋯
Stop it! Let go of me!
Looks like you're having fun
Head Prefect Hina!
If you're bowing that deeply,
there must be a serious problem
Well, that's—
Head Prefect⋯
Sensei was just—
He's not bowing, He's⋯
Huh?
⋯licking my feet⋯?
Oh, Hina!
So, the Prefect Team
is on hold too?
Rest assured, I did
everything I could
Our last hope is
Problem Solver 68
But will they accept our request?
Have no fear, This time⋯
Huh?
What's going on now?
This is strange
This is definitely the right address
Is this supposed to be
the Problem Solver office?
Could we have made a mistake?
If so, we have no idea
where they are now
Another dead end
Let's get out of here
Where are they anyway?
(Problem Solver 68 / CEO: Rikuhachima Aru
Call us anytime!)
- Long time no see, Master
- Huh?
(Ramen)
Ah, welcome
This food cart looks great
(Ramen)
It feels so nostalgic
Really?
(Shiba Seki Ramen)
(Shiba Seki Ramen) Shiba Seki
Ramen did start out as a food cart
How should I put it?
I feel young again
I'm glad to see you're well
Now we can eat your Ramen again
If not for that windfall, who
knows what would've happened
You would have figured something out
Well, I couldn't quit, could I?
Plenty of people still want my Ramen
I served the cutest customers earlier
They said they were exhausted,
but my Ramen gave them strength
I'm really grateful
How about you all?
Well, we're a bit⋯
We've been asking around for help
There's one team left,
but we can't find them
We might have to give up
Master, the check, please
- There they are!
Huh?
You want us to fight
Kaiser PMC⋯for free?
There's nothing
in it for us at all?
I'm really sorry about that
Kayoko, take a closer look at Aru
Huh?
"Eating this Ramen is payment enough,”
That's what her face says, right?
That's right!
As expected of Aru
Not a word
She just runs headlong
into hell for a bowl of Ramen
That's what being
hard boiled is all about!
-I'm sorry
- Huh?
But I'll have to think about it
Aru?
Boss, are you serious?
Yeah, I get it
Let's go, everyone
Wait, Aru!
Sensei, sometimes this happens⋯
- It's all right
- Huh?
Those kids will show up
I have faith in them
- Yeah!
Faith, huh⋯
Right, As long as the shop has
faith in its customers, it'll live on
That's the way it goes
If it doesn't work out,
you can always start over
As long as you believe,
the path will continue
Go, Foreclosure Task Force
Then⋯
Come back for delicious Ramen!
Is everyone ready?
Yes
We can go anytime
We've got plenty of ammunition
And we had a good night's sleep
Kaiser PMC can't beat us!
According to Sensei's intel,
Hoshino's in District 51
of the Kaiser PMC base
Then let's move out
All right! Hoshino Rescue Mission⋯
Start!
I'll take a window seat on this journey to find
the place where my heart belongs
So I can see beyond this sorrow chasing me
We were losing track of time without ever knowing why
With all those laughs we shared⋯
Even if⋯those moments were just ordinary
Those days⋯
One more time, one time more,
Knowing they won't come around again!
If only I could stay as resolute and beautiful
As the moon hanging in the bright noon sky
Would that let me finally forgive
All those regrets we made so willfully?
We only recognize the important things
Once they're gone and lost out of sight
We stretch up to the moon in the bright noon sky
Even though it will always be beyond our reach
Oh, those unforgettable, beautiful days⋯