Hoshino's smartphone?
Yes. I need you to find her location.
O-Okay!
Give me one second.
How's it looking?
No good.
I tried accessing the GSC's central network,
but I couldn't identify her location.
I see...
I hope we can find at least some clue...
In that case,
Come on in.
Who is that?
Could it be...? Hoshino?
What's this?
Is this the place?
I'm sure the note said this floor...
I've been expecting you, Sensei.
I had been hoping for an opportunity to
have a talk with you like this, face to face.
The teacher in charge of the
Federal Investigations Club SCHALE,
that mysterious organization
invoked by the GSC President.
Do not be alarmed.
We have no intention of becoming your enemy.
Quite the opposite, in fact.
We couldn't care less about what happens
to such an insignificant school as Abydos.
But you, on the other hand...
You're different.
I consider you an extremely potent threat.
Just who are you?
Of course, where are my manners?
I haven't introduced myself.
Let's see. Why don't we call me... Black Suit?
I'm rather fond of this name, you see.
We are just like you.
Like me?
Yes, like you.
We also hail from outside of Kivotos.
We've simply occupied a different realm from you.
Gematria.
That is our name.
To put it in terms you would be familiar with,
it is an organization, of which I am a member.
Gematria's mission is in observation,
exploration, and experimentation.
From that perspective, you may think of us
as an undefined existence, similar to you.
By the way, if I might be so bold...
Could I interest you in working together with us?
I refuse.
Interesting...
You would turn down this opportunity
to glimpse mystical truths?
Then what do you seek here in Kivotos?
I'm just here to get Hoshino back.
And what exactly gives you
the authority to make this demand?
Miss Hoshino is no longer a student of Abydos.
You're wrong.
Surely you've been reading the
forms your students give you?
Yeah, I saw the withdrawal form that she left.
Then you should understand.
There's nothing more that you can do, Sensei.
I wouldn't be so sure about that.
You see,
I haven't signed that form yet.
So Hoshino's still part of the Task Force.
She's still the vice president of Abydos.
And she's still one of my precious students.
Interesting.
As long as you are their teacher,
anything your students do requires your signature.
Such an inconvenient concept.
You were the ones who
deceived my students, all of you.
You toyed with their feelings
and took advantage of their pain.
Yes, that's exactly right.
If you were to classify our actions as "good" or "evil",
I'm sure they would fall into the latter category.
But they are still within the rules.
That is a distinction I must insist on.
Besides, the disaster that struck
Abydos was not our doing.
The sandstorm that engulfed Abydos
was extremely rare, yes.
But like any natural phenomenon,
it could have happened at any time.
The people may suffer from thirst as a result.
And when that happens, those looking
to sell water are bound to appear.
It's simply the natural course of events.
Even if that water is sold at an exorbitant price?
It's hardly a rare occurrence.
Such scenarios are commonplace in the world.
Those that have exploit those that have not.
The weak have no right to choose their own future.
Sensei.
If you could simply give up on Hoshino,
I can offer protection for Abydos in exchange.
It can be theirs again. A life where
they can go to school without fear.
It's what Hoshino would want, I'm sure.
Even if that were true, those girls wouldn't want this.
So no matter what I say,
you insist on opposing us.
You are powerless.
You lack any means of fighting us.
That may be true.
If there's someone who needs
my help, I'll stand and fight.
The odds don't matter.
I need to prove to them that their voices will
reach someone as long as they keep trying.
How absurd.
Then why are those girls still alone?
If nothing else, their voices reached me.
That's enough for me.
Why don't you just walk away?
This is their problem. It doesn't concern you.
I won't.
Why? Why?
Why why why why?
Why, why, why, why?
I don't understand. Why do you refuse?
This entire time, those girls were in pain,
and not a single adult took responsibility.
So you're saying you'll take responsibility?
You're not even their family. Why should you?
You're right. I'm not their family.
I just happened to be there,
and I just happened to meet them.
That's all I am to them.
So what?
You want a reason?
Children are crying for help!
What more reason do you need?!
Is that what it means for an adult
to take responsibility in your eyes?
That's right.
If the children laugh, you laugh with them.
If they're sad, you stay by their side.
If they're lost, you show them the way.
That's what it means to be an adult!
No, it's not.
You couldn't be more mistaken.
Adults shape society to their own will.
They decide what is right, what is proper.
What is normal and what is not.
The powerful dominate the lowly.
The educated rule the ignorant.
The strong devour the weak.
That's what it means to be an adult.
I cannot understand.
You could have held dominion over all of Kivotos.
It could have been yours. The authority, the privileges...
the Mystics that fill this academy city.
It may have been for a brief moment,
but you held it all in the palm of your hand.
And yet you let it all go without a second thought.
Truth and mystery. Authority. Money. Power.
To throw it all away is nonsense. Meaningless.
So why did you?
Even if I told you, I'm sure you wouldn't understand.
Very well.
Then there is no point in talking further.
I had such high hopes for you.
It's truly a shame.
You'll find Miss Hoshino in the laboratory
beneath Kaiser PMC's desert base.
With Mimesis, we had observed the reverse of Mystic - in other words, Terror.
We were interested in whether it
could be applied to a living student.
She was supposed to be a
test bed for confirming our theories.
Your theories?
Now that negotiations have failed,
there is naught I can do.
It is regrettable, but our involvement ends here.
So then Hoshino...?
Go ahead, take her.
It is no longer any concern of ours.
Of course, this is assuming that director
will allow you to reach her in the first place.
I'm glad we were able to have this talk.
May we meet again, somewhere.
I wish you the best of luck.
A laboratory under the Kaiser PMC base...
There's no mistake.
Hoshino's there.
That's where they've been holding her captive...?
Well then, what are we waiting for?
Let's go save her.
Yes, absolutely.
But we can't be hasty.
By the way, what do we even
say to Hoshino when we find her?
Well, I mean, more importantly,
We have to scold her.
She went back on her own word.
She must be punished.
So we'll scold her.
For her sake.
Let's all meet her together and say, "welcome home."
What?! Where did that corny line come from?
That's way too romantic!
It just screams blue skies and shiny memories!
There's no way we could pull that off!
I'll say it.
Even if you won't, Serika.
No way!
I-I'll say it, too!
Though it is a little embarrassing...
D-Do whatever you want!
But you won't catch me dead saying that!
Um, but there's only five of us -
But...
We can't win with just us.
Then we need to find some allies.
What about PS68?
I mean, they did help us before, but...
About that...
Hello, everyone. It's been a while!
I'm glad to see you're doing well, Hifumi!
Yes, it's all thanks to your help.
I'm sorry.
I meant to go visit you at your school, but...
Huh?
Wait, where's Hoshino?
Actually...
So that's what happened...
Things have certainly changed since we last met.
Yes. I wish we'd known sooner
what Hoshino was going through.
Maybe we could have stopped her.
But we just couldn't do anything.
Then does that mean you're here about Hoshino?
Yes, about that...
We'd like Trinity to help us save Hoshino.
I'll try asking the Tea Party.
Hmm, what to do...
Could I ask for your help, Miss Nagisa?
Which one should I eat?
This shortcake is bursting with cream
and pairs beautifully with the tea.
But this mont blanc is hard to pass up as well.
Um, Miss Nagisa?
The students of Abydos have helped me in the past.
So please -
This company, Kaiser PMC, certainly seems like
it would be a bad influence on our students.
So you'll hel-
However.
We have that treaty to worry about as well.
We cannot afford to act carelessly.
Might I have some time to consider?
So no answer yet, huh...
Sorry, this was my idea...
Guess it's not that easy.
Looks like finding help is going
to be harder than we thought.
We can't give up.
Well, yeah, but...
I can't imagine this next group will help us, either...
Even so, we can't give up.
It'll be fine.
I'm sorry that the others couldn't attend this meeting.
No, it's no problem.
I would have liked Chinatsu to be here, at least.
But this school has a bit of trouble following the rules.
Welcome back, Chinatsu.
Excuse me... for being late.
Want some?
Huh?
Oh, thank you.
No, but, that's... mine...
I'm sorry for keeping you waiting.
We just managed to finish up -
Excuse me!
I'm sorry to interrupt your break!
There's trouble in the cafeteria!
Understood!
Thank you for the tea!
I'm sorry for all the confusion!
Please take your time!
A-Are things always like this around here?
Today's actually a bit on the quiet side.
Speaking of which, I wonder how
the talks are going on their end?
The Head Prefect is busy at the moment.
She's not available to meet right now.
There has to be a way!
Well, if you insist...
If you bow down and lick my feet -
Wait, what are you doing?!
D-Do you have zero pride as an adult?
Wouldn't you normally hesitate at least?
This is an emergency!
I've never seen such clear eyes...
Hey! Get off of me already!
You look like you're having fun.
P-President Hina!
Look at him. He's on his knees.
The situation must be quite serious.
Well, actually, President Hina...
He's not actually kneeling, he's... um...
Licking... my feet...
Hina!
So the Prefect Team didn't give us an answer, either...
Don't worry! We did what we could!
The only ones left are Problem Solver 68!
But will they agree to help us...?
It's okay. This one's the one.
Hey, what gives?
That's weird...
This is definitely the address they gave me.
So what? You're telling me this is the PS68 office?
Maybe there was a miscommunication?
This was our only lead on where to find them.
Great, we came all this way for nothing.
Come on, let's get out of here.
Geez, just where did they disappear off to?
Hey, Boss, been a while!
Oh, welcome in!
What a beautiful stall!
It almost feels nostalgic, somehow.
That so?
Shiba Seki Ramen actually started out of a stall, y'know.
Feels like I'm back in those days, almost.
I'm glad to see you're doing well.
Now we can eat your ramen again.
Gosh, I don't know what would've
happened if it weren't for that money.
I'm sure you would have kept on anyway.
Well, not like quitting was a choice anyway.
There's still plenty of people out there
who're waiting to eat my ramen.
These two adorable girls showed up earlier.
They looked right happy eating, said my
ramen was just the thing after a tiring day.
Can't ask for more than that.
How're things for you?
Well, you see, not great...
We tried asking different people for help, but...
And then there's one group
we haven't been able to find.
If we can't find them, I guess we just have to give up.
Boss, can we get the cheque?
It's them!
You want us to fight Kaiser PMC for free?
I don't see what that does for us.
I know, and I'm really sorry.
Come on, Kayoko, take a closer look.
"We don't need payment. Being able
to eat this ramen is enough for us."
That's what this face says, don't you think?
I see! Yes, that's just how brave Miss Aru is!
She doesn't waste time with words as
she marches into hell for a bowl of ramen.
She's the picture of hard-boiled!
Sorry.
But can I think it over first?
What?!
Miss Aru?
Are you for real, Boss?
I see.
I understand.
Come on, let's go.
Hey, wait, hold on, Aru!
Don't beat yourself up over it, Sensei -
It's okay.
I have faith that they'll come help us.
Faith, huh.
Come to think of it, my restaurant will always be here
as long as the customers believe.
It's the same idea in the end.
If everything goes wrong,
just start over and try again.
There'll always be a path forward,
as long as you believe.
Go get 'em, Task Force.
And when you're done...
Make sure you come back
for a bowl of delicious ramen!
Is everyone ready?
I'm ready to go whenever.
I've packed plenty of ammunition.
I got a good night's sleep.
Kaiser PMC doesn't stand a chance!
According to the information Sensei gave us,
Hoshino is being held in District 51,
inside the Kaiser PMC base.
Right.
Then let's get moving.
All right.
Our objective is to rescue Hoshino.
Let's do this.