Hey
Hey, listen to me!
- Hoshino
- What is it?
Ta-da! Look at this
An Oasis Festival?
Yes! Back then, the oasis
was as big as a lake
Here, Keep this as a souvenir
Isn't it amazing?
It would take a miracle,
but it would be great
if people gathered here
like old times—
That'll never happen
Why not?
Because miracles don't happen
Be realistic
Why would anyone
come to this wasteland?
You can't keep daydreaming
But⋯
S-Sorry
You're too preoccupied with
miracles and nonsense⋯
You're the Abydos Student Council president!
Focus on your responsibilities!
The sky blue archive!
I pedal on my bike seeking new sights
We'll break the monotony,
no longer trapped in place
Daydreaming on the rooftop,
gazing at a sky so blue
Those clouds like whales are always changing
We'll embrace a past that can't be altered
Sharing juice in this world made of sand
Is a taste so divine
If I were here alone, here without all of you
I couldn't laugh, I couldn't cry
A fateful coterie
Even if the world's memories blow away
like grains of sand one day
The sky, sea, wind, and you,
our youth will never end
It's easy to see why we protect what we do
Because this is the only place where we belong
Good morning, Shiroko
Hoshino
Can we talk for a sec?
About yesterday⋯
-I'm sorry
- No
What I said was unfair
Only because you were
worried about me⋯ Right?
Of course, I was
The Abydos Foreclosure Task
Force includes all five of us
I'm glad to hear you say that
Now⋯ Hoshino
I don't know what you're hiding
But I trust you
You're such a great friend
Everyone!
As you may have heard,
a third party has taken control
of the Abydos District
I looked into it and
discovered something
(Real Estate Title)
The land Abydos occupies
is owned by Kaiser Construction
(Kaiser Construction Co, Ltd)
But that means⋯
The Kaiser Corporation
is behind this after all
This building, the surrounding area,
the school's buried main building,
the wastelands around it,
even the land the city occupies⋯
It's all changed ownership
That far?
But how did they do it?
Not just anyone can
sell the District's land
It must have been the
Abydos Student Council
- Huh?
- That's correct
The Student Council sold the land
What were they thinking?!
How could they just hand over Abydos?!
They already own every
other school district
It's common knowledge
But we were so focused
on paying off our debts
that we didn't even notice
I'm sorry
I should have caught this sooner
Ayane, it's not your fault
It happened before we even enrolled
Hang on⋯
Hoshino, weren't you on
the Student Council?
Really?
Yeah, As the vice president
That's right
But it was just me and the president
What? Only two of you?
Mm-hmm
There were only a handful
of students left at the time
We had no staff
All the classes were canceled
The Student Council room
was nothing but storage
Our president was infamous
for being a reckless idiot
And I was pretty ruthless for a freshman
It was a disaster
What kind of Student Council was that?
We were just a couple of
fools with titles⋯
wandering aimlessly⋯
completely clueless
You shouldn't blame yourself
I don't know exactly what happened
But you're the reason the
Foreclosure Task Force exists
Huh?
Yes, you're lazy
And you're careless
And that's definitely a problem
But you always come
through when it counts
I respect you for that
Shiroko, what is this?
You're talking like we're in
some kind of teen drama!
(Kaiser Group, Kaiser Construction)
Why did the Student Council
sell to Kaiser Corporation?
Maybe they were trying
to pay off their debts?
I'm just guessing
But, the school had a lot
of problems to solve
I agree
But Abydos is half-buried in sand
It wouldn't have been worth much
(Loan Agreement, Proof of Transfer
Real Estate Sales Contract)
(Loan Agreement, Proof of Transfer Real Estate Sales Contract)
Maybe enough to cover the interest, but not the principal
It was a vicious cycle
They had to keep selling land⋯
Do you think that's what happened?
What a mess!
It's been a lost cause from the start
It was a scam
Huh?
(Kaiser Construction (Kaiser Group) / Loan - Abydos High
School - Unable to Repay Land and Buildings, Interest)
(Kaiser Construction (Kaiser Group) / Loan - Abydos High School - Unable to Repay
Land and Buildings, Interest) They lend more money than the school can ever repay
(Kaiser Construction (Kaiser Group) / Loan - Abydos High
School - Unable to Repay Land and Buildings, Interest)
(Kaiser Construction (Kaiser Group) / Loan - Abydos High School - Unable to
Repay Land and Buildings, Interest) Then they demand at least the interest
And when the school can't pay,
they're forced to sell property
Yes, that must be it
Given enough time, Kaiser Corporation
could take the entire Abydos
District piece by piece
That sounds plausible
Maybe they planned it from the start
Yes, from the moment they
loaned money to Abydos
They must've set this trap ages ago
Decades, even⋯
So we've been playing into
their hands all along?
To think we fell for such a scam!
Calm down, Serika
The fault lies with the deceiver,
not their victim
I know
But still⋯
People get desperate when
they feel cornered
They'll try anything, even if it
makes things worse
That's just how it goes, Serika
The school's debt,
Abydos' predicament,
and this new information⋯
Little by little, it's all becoming clear
Once the Abydos Student Council folded,
they couldn't buy the land anymore
So they hired the Helmet Gang
to take the school and
the remaining land
But if that's true, then it was
never about the money
Kaiser Corporation was only
interested in the land
You may be right
But that raises another question
Why would anyone want
this barren wasteland?
That's a good point
In its present state,
Abydos isn't very profitable
Listen⋯
It's about the desert
After the fight with Gehenna⋯
Kaiser Corporation has
been up to something
in the desert of Abydos
Really?
Why would Gehenna's Head
Prefect say such a thing?
Sensei, why didn't you tell us this before?
Ah! I-I had a lot on my plate!
And I had no idea what to do
You should have told us anyway!
I'm sorry
Kaiser Corporation bought the land
And they're up to something⋯
Serika's right
The truth lies in the Abydos Desert
Yeah
- Right
- Yes
Okay, then, Let's go
To the Abydos Desert!
From here on, we'll have to walk
If anyone passes out,
we'll have problems
Leave it to us!
I'm really sorry, everyone
I haven't seen this view in a while⋯
You've been here before?
A few times, yes, for
Student Council work
A bit further
The oasis is just ahead!
What? An oasis?
Yes, but it's dried up now
This is where they held the
Abydos Oasis Festival
- Oasis Festival?
- I've heard of that!
It was well known in Abydos
Tons of people attended
Exactly
It was so popular that it drew
people from other districts
To the middle of a desert?
I heard it was a nice place to live once
Hey, Hoshino! Look!
Look over there!
- Can we really trust this?
- Yeah
(Drawn by Yume / Desert / Here / School)
That's definitely the oasis
where they held the festival
There's a huge facility up ahead
In a place like this?
Maybe that's what
Hina was talking about
Listen, everyone
We don't know what's there
So be very careful while
you investigate
- Got it
- Okay
Look at all those guards
What is this place?
Kaiser PMC.
It's another
subsidiary of Kaiser Corporation
- PMC.
- You know it?
Yes, it's short for
Private Military Company
It's a civilian military operation
They're a step above
the Helmet Gang
Professionals
Are those⋯
- Intruders!
- Capture them!
- Surround them
- To the right!
Darn
There are too many of them
It's worse than handling
the Prefect Team
What should we do, Hoshino?
Don't be reckless! Retreat!
Well, well⋯
I heard there were intruders
I didn't realize they were
Abydos students
That looks like⋯
No way!
Huh?
You're the Student Council
president Gematria was after
No⋯the vice president
Who are you?
You don't know who I am?
I am⋯
the Kaiser Corporation Director
I knew it
He's the one⋯
He tricked the Abydos Student
Council out of their land
Choose your words carefully
After all, you're trespassing on
Kaiser PMC property
You do know that's a crime
But to your point⋯
the Abydos District
Yes, we bought it
It was entirely legal
We have the records to prove it
But why buy land
in the middle of a desert?
I'll tell you why
We're looking for buried treasure
It's somewhere here in Abydos
You're lying!
We're not falling for
that nonsense!
And it doesn't explain
all these soldiers
They're here to take
the school by force,
aren't they?
Preposterous
They're here to ensure no one
interferes with our search
We couldn't care less about you
You're nothing but pests,
easily crushed
Observe
It's me
What? Who is he calling?
Proceed
You're about to get some bad news
What is he doing?
(Kaiser Loans Abydos High School's credit rating has dropped to the lowest tier, Consequently, the variable interest
rate has increased to 3,000%, As such, next month's interest will total 91.3 million yen, Please ensure timely payment)
(Kaiser Loans Abydos High School's credit rating has dropped to the lowest tier, Consequently, the variable interest rate
has increased to 3,000%, As such, next month's interest will total 91.3 million yen, Please ensure timely payment) Wh-What?!
Our interest rate just went up—
3,000% starting next month!
What?
Now do you understand
who's holding the noose
around your necks?
This is cruel
How can we possibly pay that?
You're right, You should
probably give up now
Transfer to another school
This debt is the school's problem
Why take that burden on yourselves?
No, We can't give up
We won't abandon our school
Abydos is our school and our home
What exactly are you
going to do about it?
W-Well⋯
We have to go back
Hoshino
There's no point arguing
They'll only mock us
Spoken like a true
vice president
You're quite smart
Ah, I remember now⋯
You were the brains
Forced to serve at that
idiotic president's side
The new terms for your
loan take effect next month
Thank you for your cooperation,
valued customers
Who do they think they are?!
They say they're looking for treasure
But there's nothing left
in that desert, oil or otherwise
We surveyed it ages ago
Shiroko?
I'm going back
I'll find out what they're really up to
You're going back to the desert?
With enough preparation,
we can infiltrate their base
W-Wait a minute!
Paying off our debt is more—
There's no way we can pay,
not legally anyway
Shiroko, you can't go!
No, Shiroko is right
If we lose the school, it's over
This is no time for scruples!
Think logically, Serika
It's just like when we raided
that Black Market Bank
If we use stolen funds
to save Abydos,
could we ever
hold our heads high?
But—
I understand your frustration
But I won't let you
become criminals
Then what are we supposed to do?
Well⋯
Okay, everyone, calm down
Emotions are running
pretty hot right now
Aren't they, Shiroko?
Sorry, That wasn't my intention
Yeah, we know
Why don't we call it
a day for now?
Go home, Cool off
We'll regroup tomorrow
President's orders
- Okay
- You're right
Y-Yes
All right
Good, See you tomorrow, everyone
⋯too preoccupied with
miracles and nonsense⋯
Right?
- Hoshino
-Hm?
Oh, Sensei, It's just you
Just me? What's that
supposed to mean?
Oh, Right
Hey, since when can you talk
to Shiroko with just a look?
I really can't let my guard
down around you, Sensei
Hoshino, can I ask you something?
Sure, what is it?
(Withdrawal Form)
Oh, that
Can you explain?
I suppose so
But it's a bit awkward
to talk face-to-face
Would you walk with me?
Sensei⋯
Isn't it sad that my high school life
is the color of this sand?
I thought you loved
this place, Hoshino
They say Abydos was a powerful school
before the desert took it
But I don't have
any memory of it
The school was a
mess from day one
They didn't do anything right
But it's your one and only Alma mater
Abydos' main building was buried
long before this old-timer enrolled
This is just an annex
We relocated several times
before we settled here
Still, this is where I met the
Foreclosure Task Force⋯
So I suppose I do like it after all
Sensei
I feel⋯
relieved
If the youngins hear
about this, they'll worry
But I shouldn't keep secrets
from them either
I'll explain everything
to them tomorrow
The truth may upset them⋯
No, I'm glad you told me
I'm sure they'll understand too
It'll be all right
We have a lot of problems
But we'll figure them out together
Yeah
It might take a miracle
Together, we can make a miracle
I'm sure of it
All right, well, enough of this chit chat!
Bye, Sensei
Yes
See you tomorrow
I'll take a window seat on this journey to find
the place where my heart belongs
So I can see beyond this sorrow chasing me
We were losing track of time without ever knowing why
With all those laughs we shared⋯
Even if⋯those moments were just ordinary
Those days⋯
One more time, one time more,
Knowing they won't come around again!
If only I could stay as resolute and beautiful
As the moon hanging in the bright noon sky
Would that let me finally forgive
All those regrets we made so willfully?
We only recognize the important things
Once they're gone and lost out of sight
We stretch up to the moon in the bright noon sky
Even though it will always be beyond our reach
Oh, those unforgettable, beautiful days⋯