...no. Hey, come on, listen!
Hoshino!
What is it?
Ta-dah! Look at what I found!
Sand Festival?
This was back when the oasis
was still the size of a lake.
Here, you can have it.
Isn't that just precious?
What if a miracle happened
and Abydos started booming agai—
Miracles don't exist, Yume.
Huh?
They're only in fairy tales.
Face reality.
Why would anyone ever come
to the middle of the desert?
Even entertaining the idea is a waste of time.
Well, I mean...
S-Sorry.
You're always going on and on
about useless stuff like miracles.
You're the president of the Abydos student council.
You have a lot of responsibilities,
so get your act together already!
Good morning, Shiroko.
Hoshino?
Hey, Shiroko, got a second to talk?
About yesterday, well... I'm sorry.
It's fine. I was also being too pushy.
I know you're just worried about little ol' me.
Well, of course.
The Abydos Task Force
isn't complete without all five of us.
You sure know how to keep your elders happy.
Hey, Hoshino.
I don't know what you're hiding from us,
but I trust you.
Man, I really lucked out having you as a clubmate.
Hey, everyone.
Remember how the land Abydos owned
was transferred to a third party?
We looked deeper into it,
and it turns out that the land is currently
owned by "Kaiser Construction".
Then that means...
Kaiser Corporation is behind it after all?
Yes. We only own this school building
and part of the surrounding area.
Everything else - the main Abydos
building buried under the desert,
the miles of wasteland surrounding it,
and even the buildings and the land
inside the city belong to them now.
That much?
But how?
Normally you can't just trade a school district's land.
It must have been the student council.
What?
That's correct.
The author of this deal was the student council.
What the hell? What were they thinking?
How could they have just handed
over Abydos land to those creeps?
Each school's district is the property of that school.
It's simply common sense.
We were so caught up with repaying our debt
that we never even suspected this could happen.
I'm sorry. If only I had realized this sooner...
Don't worry about it, Ayane.
This all happened before everyone enrolled -
Oh, that reminds me.
You were also a member of the
student council, weren't you, Hoshino?
Wait, really?
If I remember correctly,
she was the vice president, right?
Yeah, well, you know.
Then again, it was just me and the president.
What? Just two of you?
Yeah. By that time, the student population
was already in the double digits.
The staff had all left, and actual
classes were a thing of the past.
Even the student council room
was just a glorified closet.
The president was the biggest klutz
in the school, not a thought in her head.
Back then, I was the new kid with the bad attitude.
Everything about it was just a mess.
What the heck? How is that even a student council?
Well, it was just a couple of idiots
doing stupid things together at the end of the day.
Man, we really were just loitering
around all sorts of places back then.
Just a few idiots, blissfully unaware of anything.
It's not something you should blame yourself for.
I don't know what happened in the past.
But what I do know is that without you,
the Task Force wouldn't be here today.
You're always lazing about.
You never give a straight answer.
And you've got lots of other problems.
But you're always the first to step up when we need you.
And I respect you.
Where's this coming from, Shiroko?
You can't just drop a line like that out of nowhere!
Speaking of which, why did the student council sell
the land to Kaiser Corporation in the first place?
I'm guessing they were just
trying to pay off the debt at first.
I wasn't involved in it, though, so this is just speculation.
But I think they were trying their best for the sake
of the school, and more things just kept happening.
I think so, too.
But there's no way all the land covered by desert
would have been worth very much.
They may have paid back the interest,
but they couldn't have reduced the principle.
So then they would have been trapped
in a vicious cycle of selling more land.
Is that correct?
What the heck!
That means the game was rigged from the start!
You might be right about that.
What?
First, they make a loan that could never be paid off.
Then, they pressure the school to sell their land
in order to pay even a portion of the debt.
That has to be it.
And so the entire Abydos school district slowly falls
into the hands of the Kaiser Corporation.
True. They may have planned for this all along.
That was why they lent Abydos
the money in the first place.
The trap may have been set
far earlier than we realized.
Decades ago, even.
What? That means Kaiser just
played them like a damn fiddle!
I can't believe they fell for this scam...
Calm down, Serika.
I think the perpetrators are
to blame here, not the victims.
I know that!
But still...
People will do anything when
they're driven into a corner.
Even if they know it'll only make things worse.
That's all that this is, Serika.
The school's debt...
This situation Abydos is in now...
And these new discoveries we've made together...
I think all the pieces are starting to fall into place.
After the Abydos student council disappeared,
they lost their ability to buy more land.
So in order to take over this final piece of land,
they hired the Helmet Gang.
Does that mean Kaiser Corporation
was never after the money?
Their true goal was the land itself all along?
It would make sense.
But then this raises another question.
Why would they want this land
when it's buried under the desert?
That's true.
What could they possibly stand to gain
from taking over Abydos as it is now?
Actually...
Speaking of the desert, right after we fought Gehenna,
The abandoned desert outside Abydos.
The Kaiser Corporation is plotting something there.
Wait, what? How does the Head Prefect
of Gehenna know about that?
Sensei, why didn't you tell us?
W-well, I mean, there was a lot going on.
It felt like sensitive information, so...
Yeah, okay, but you should have just told us!
Sorry...
Anyway, now we know that Kaiser Corporation
was the one buying out the land.
And if they're plotting something...
Serika's right.
The answers to all of our questions
must be in the Abydos Desert.
Yes.
Yeah.
Let's go.
To the Abydos Desert!
Looks like we'll have to hoof it from here.
Can't have you collapsing on us out here.
Just leave this part to us!
Sorry, girls...
Man, now this is a blast from the past.
You've been here before?
A few times, for student council work.
Just a bit further and there's a
giant oasis just waiting for us!
What? An oasis?
Yeah! Well, to be fair, it's all dried up now.
They used to hold the Abydos
Sand Festival there every year.
Sand Festival...
I've heard of that!
It was very well known within Abydos.
Apparently it attracted a ton of people!
Yeah, that's it!
It was big enough of an event that tons of people
from other schools would come to see it, too.
Out here in the middle of the desert?
Well, actually, I hear this place
used to be quite pleasant.
Look! Look, Hoshino!
It's right there!
Are you sure your lead is good?
Right there is the very oasis where
they used to hold the Sand Festival!
I see a large structure ahead!
Huh? Out here?
This might be what Hina was talking about.
Everyone, we have no idea what's out there.
Please stay on your guard as you look around.
Roger!
That's a lot of guards.
What the heck even is this place?
Kaiser PMC.
It looks like this is another one of
Kaiser Corporation's subsidiaries.
PMC...
An abbreviation?
Yes.
It stands for Private Military Company.
In other words, a company of soldiers for hire.
These aren't like the Helmet Gang.
They're professional fighters.
Who's there?
Intruders spotted!
Get to positions!
Ugh, this could get messy.
The Prefects were already bad enough.
What do we do, Hoshino?
Don't do anything dangerous! Pull back!
My, what a pleasant surprise.
I heard there were intruders.
But I didn't expect to see the students
of Abydos High School here.
That man...
It couldn't be!
Oh?
You're that student council president
that Gematria was after.
Or rather, was it the vice-president?
Who are you?
Well I'll be.
I'd expect you to know at least that much.
I am a director of the Kaiser Corporation.
So it was him...
Then that means he's the one who...?
He's the one who swindled the Abydos
student council out of their land?
I'd advise you to watch your tone, young lady.
You're currently standing on the
property of our company, Kaiser PMC.
Property that you're currently trespassing on.
Now, back to the topic at hand.
You mentioned the land in Abydos.
Yes, we did in fact purchase that.
It was a completely legitimate transaction.
We even have the records to prove it.
You must be wondering why we
would bother buying so many miles of sand.
Well then, allow me to elucidate.
We're looking for a certain treasure,
said to be buried somewhere in Abydos.
Give me a break!
You really expect us to believe that crap?
Then why do you have the army?
You were planning on taking
Abydos by force. Am I wrong?
Don't be ridiculous.
This is simply a contingency in case anyone
decides to interrupt our little treasure hunt.
We didn't bring them for you.
I could deal with you whenever I wanted.
In fact...
It's me.
A phone call? Now?
Yes, that's right.
Do it.
I've got some very bad news.
What is he doing?
Huh?!
What? Why?
The interest rate starting next month
has increased 3000%!
What the heck?
Now do you understand?
You're all nothing more than dogs on a leash.
And I'm the one holding that leash.
You monster.
There's no way we could pay that interest rate!
Then why don't you just
give up and leave your school?
Withdraw from school,
or transfer somewhere else.
This debt is the school's responsibility.
What reason do you have to
carry the burden yourselves?
There's no way we could do that!
She's right! We're not abandoning Abydos!
Abydos is our school. It's our hometown!
Then what will you do?
Do you have any better options?
Well...
Come on, let's go home.
Hoshino?
There's no point staying and arguing.
He's just playing with us.
A wise choice, Miss Vice President.
You do seem like a smart one.
That reminds me.
There was that bumbling fool of a president
who was always drooling at your heels.
Well, then, I expect continued
payments from next month on.
Once again, thank you, dear customers,
for choosing Kaiser Loan.
God! What the hell was that crap!
He said they were looking for a treasure
There's no crude oil or other valuable
underground resources left in the desert.
Those survey reports came out a long time ago.
Shiroko?
I'm going again.
We need to know what they're up to.
Wait, you want to go back there?
If I take time to prepare, I think I can infiltrate that base.
H-Hold on!
We need to think about
how to deal with the debt first.
The debt's too big to pay by playing fair.
Don't say that, Shiroko!
I'm with Shiroko here.
If we lose the school, it's all over!
We can't afford to be picky!
Think about it, Serika!
If we do this, it'll be just like
when we robbed the bank!
Could we really say that we saved Abydos
if we used money we stole from someone else?
But...!
I understand your impatience.
But I can't let you become criminals!
Then what do you want us to do?
Well...
Come on, everyone, let's all calm down a bit.
I can see steam coming out your ears.
Am I right, Shiroko?
Sorry. I didn't mean for it to get like this.
It's fine. We all understand.
In any case, let's leave it here for today.
Why don't we all cool off and
then meet up again tomorrow?
Make that an order from your president!
That's a good idea.
Hoshino's right!
Y-Yeah.
Okay.
All righty.
See you tomorrow.
Wasting time talking about useless things
like miracles and happy endings, huh.
Hoshino.
Oh, it's just you.
Oh come on, that's a bit harsh.
Speaking of, when did you and Shiroko get so close?
I saw you reading each other's minds there.
I'll have to keep a closer eye on you, Sensei.
Hoshino, can I ask you something?
About what?
Ah. Okay.
Could you tell me?
Well, if you insist.
It's a bit awkward to say face to face.
Mind if we walk and talk, Sensei?
Hey, Sensei.
High school is supposed to be fun, right?
Kind of sad if it's all covered in sand, don't you think?
But you like this school, don't you?
They say that before the desert moved in,
Abydos was known for its size and influence.
But that was before my time.
I never personally saw anything like that myself.
It was a complete mess from the start.
There wasn't one thing the school actually did right.
But despite everything, it's still
the school that you love, right?
By the time I had enrolled, the Abydos
main building was already deep under sand.
The school kept moving as the desert expanded,
and this annex is just where it ended up.
But you know, I did get to meet everyone
at the Task Force since I came here.
I guess I do like this school after all.
Sensei.
The truth is...
Whew, I feel better.
If I told everyone about this,
they'd all just worry, you know?
But I can't go keeping secrets from my
cute little classmates forever, either.
I'll explain everything to them tomorrow.
Not like they need more on their plate, though.
No, thank you for telling me.
I'm sure they'll understand
what you're going through, too.
It'll be fine!
The road ahead is long, but if we all
work together, I'm sure it'll all work out.
Yeah.
Who knows? Maybe a miracle will happen.
I'm sure we can make one happen if we're all together.
All righty then.
That's enough of this conversation.
See you around, Sensei.
Yeah.
See you tomorrow!