To The Abydos Desert
Real Estate Registration Information
Proprietor and Other Stakeholders
Owner:
Kaiser Construction, Ltd.
Proprietor and Other Stakeholders
Desertification and
Environmental Protection
A scientific approach towards achieving sustainability
Institute for Ecological Research
... Ecology
Yakisoba
HERE
DESSERT
By Yume
Director of Kaiser Corporation
Mail
Kaiser Loan
Effective immediately, we have updated Abydos
High School's credit rating to the minimum rank.
As a result, your variable interest rate has been
increased by 3000%. In accordance with these
changes, your balance due for next month is
91,300,000 yen.
Please pay the amount due by the payment
deadline.
close