- What'd you say?
- Hm?
Ayane⋯
Read it again?
Calm down first, Serika⋯
I'm perfectly calm!
She's right, Serika
We can't lose our heads
You're shaking, Sensei
Ayane, is it true?
Yes
Based on these documents⋯
Kaiser Loans is
funding the Helmet Gang
What?
No way
If that's true,
not only did the Helmet Gang
try to ambush us⋯
⋯but our money paid
for THEIR guns!
The sky blue archive!
I pedal on my bike seeking new sights
We'll break the monotony,
no longer trapped in place
Daydreaming on the rooftop,
gazing at a sky so blue
Those clouds like whales are always changing
We'll embrace a past that can't be altered
Sharing juice in this world made of sand
Is a taste so divine
If I were here alone, here without all of you
I couldn't laugh, I couldn't cry
A fateful coterie
Even if the world's memories blow away
like grains of sand one day
The sky, sea, wind, and you,
our youth will never end
It's easy to see why we protect what we do
Because this is the only place where we belong
(Cash/Interest)
According to this,
(Cash/Interest from Abydos Mission Fund for Kata-Kata
Helmet Gang) they've received about 7.88 million yen
That's⋯
Yes, Exactly
Um, what is so important
about this 7.88 million yen?
Wait, don't tell me—!
Yes, It's our last
loan payment
7.88 million⋯
You really owe that much?
That's just a fraction
We really owe 900 million
Hey, why don't we
talk about that later
This document is a
balance sheet from Kaiser Loans
You can see the
7.88 million yen
that we paid back
This paper must've come from
the cash delivery van
that came to our school
What about this?
Right after they took our 7.88 million,
(Deposit)
(Collection)
Right after they took our 7.88 million,
(Mission Fund for Kata-Kata Helmet Gang)
They set aside 5 million as mission funds
(Withdrawal)
for the Kata-Kata Helmet Gang
Mission funds?
They handed over 5 million
to the Helmet Gang
to pay for their
campaign?
What campaign?
I assume it's the one
to get rid of us
But that means⋯
Our true enemy is Kaiser Loans
Why would they do this?
If the school goes bankrupt,
they still won't get their money
K-Kaiser Loans?
That's the loan shark company
run by the notorious
Kaiser Corporation, right?
I doubt Kaiser Loans
is acting alone
Shiroko?
The Kaiser Corporation
must be behind this too
It's possible
Thanks for your
help today, everyone
No, we should
thank you
Sorry for the trouble
I'll let the Tea Party know!
Hifumi?
The Kaiser Corporation
Is working with criminals
and other shadowy forces
Your situation is proof
Now that I know,
I can't just avert my eyes
Hifumi⋯
Thank you so much!
If Trinity's student
council can help us,
maybe we can fix this
Right, Hoshino?
Uh⋯
One thing that did
surprise me is
the fact your debt
is around 1 billion
It's not a billion!
It's 960 million!
Serika, you're
missing the point⋯
Anyway, once the Tea Party
hears about this, surely they'll⋯
The Tea Party
already knows
Pardon?
And not just the
Tea Party
Gehenna and Millennium
probably know too
Wait, then why haven't they⋯?
They're playing
blind on purpose
On purpose?
Hifumi, you're
really sweet
But the world isn't
If the other schools intervene,
it'll just create
more trouble
What do you mean?
Right now, Abydos High
is on the verge of a shutdown
If larger schools like Trinity or Gehenna
stepped in, we
couldn't really object
Do you follow?
You're saying
that if they did something bad
while pretending to help,
you couldn't stop them⋯
Is that it?
Hm
Hoshino, isn't that
a little cynical?
Right! Why wouldn't
they help us?
I agree
Don't ignore the "what-ifs,"
"What-ifs?"
I don't get it!
Don't fret
We'll find a solution!
Right?! Maybe⋯?
Hopefully⋯
Sensei, you're supposed
to inspire confidence!
Let's calm down and think⋯
This is no time to be calm
Hey, don't stare
at me like that
"What-ifs⋯"
Right
We ignored the
"what-ifs" back then⋯
Now Abydos⋯
Wait a minute!
What are you youngins
talking about?
Hifumi was just
about to say something
What's the matter,
"Faust?"
Please don't
call me that
Okay⋯
Hifumi, mastermind of
the Masked Swimsuit Gang!
Please! Stop saying that!
Knock it off
You're embarrassing her
I need to get going
I had a nice
time today
Shiroko, you're the
only one who had fun
Let's have some fun
at your school next time
Do your best, Hifumi!
You too! I know
things are hard,
but don't give up!
Right
See you later
Are we gonna be okay?
We can worry
about it later
This old-timer's exhausted
Let's meet tomorrow then
Go home and get some
rest, everyone
- Great
- Agreed
Staying up all night's
bad for your complexion
Morning
Aru, were you up late?
I slept great
We planned the next
attack on Abydos
Right, Kayoko?
We'll plant dozens
of bombs in advance
Then detonate them
when our enemies pass by
Haruka will also⋯
Paying attention?
Course I am!
- But you just⋯
- I was thinking
Look, please just confirm
- Is this plan good?
- Yeah
Aru, if you're worried
about money so much,
let's just use the cash
from that bag we found
No way
That's money they
dropped by accident
Only losers would use that
It'd tank our reputation
Could we ask our client
for a deposit then?
No deposits
That's against our code
Didn't I already tell you?
"If we take the client's money,
we must follow the client's orders,"
- That so?
- Exactly
Right, I remember
you said that before
We only take their money
once the job's done
Otherwise we'd never
be able to achieve
our vision
We have a vision?
Of course!
"Hardboiled outlaws,
untethered by rules or laws,"
That's what Problem Solver 68 is
Boss, can we
just give up
and go home
to Gehenna?
You think the
Prefect Team will let us?
Right
The Prefect Team is a pain
They're one of the
strongest groups in all of Kivotos
That's just because of the
Head Prefect, Hina
It's not a stretch to say
the bulk of that
team's strength is hers
In other words,
we can beat all the
other prefects except her
That's a take
IF we have a
foolproof plan
We're not going
back to Gehenna
We have to be hard boiled outlaws
untethered by rules and laws
Isn't that the vision
of Problem Solver 68?
Exactly
- Welcome back, Haruka
- Nice job
I'm back
Aru
If you ever need me,
let me know
I'll crush anyone
with these two hands
These hands
Oh my, Aru
So you were just hungry?
- You're annoying
- Let's go eat
All right
Where to?
Shiba Seki Ramen?
- Don't worry
The Abydos part-timer
only works afternoons
Guess we have
no other choice
Let's go, Haruka
Okay
Good morning
You're in early today
Morning, Sensei
Hoshino, Nonomi⋯
What are you two
doing here?
Forget it, This is my spot
That's not what I meant
Right, Hoshino
Didn't anyone teach
you to share?
That's not what I
meant either!
Oh my!
Hoshino, where are
you going?
Today's my day off
I'll be relaxing
Let me know
if anything comes up
Another nap?
Looks like
It's a nice day for it
Hoshino's changed
Huh?
She's usually zoned out
these days
But when we first met
she moved like something
was chasing her
What was chasing her?
Honestly?
Everything
From what I've heard
when Hoshino first arrived,
there was this senior
She was the last head
of the Abydos Student Council
(Student Council Room) She was the
last head of the Abydos Student Council
She left
And Hoshino took
on her role
(No Entry) And
Hoshino took on her role
(No Entry)
She was only a first year
Maybe that's why
she never reached out
to the other schools
Now she's a lot
more laid-back
Still, I don't know
all the details
- You think I'm the reason?
- Huh?
For her change
No?
Sorry, what I meant was⋯?
I definitely believe it was you
(Shiba Seki Ramen)
Thank you for waiting
At last!
Thanks for the grub!
So good!
A bowl for each of us
Are you sure this is okay?
You came all this way
to eat my ramen
Why not?
Thank you
Thank you so much!
I'm truly grateful
Don't mention it
We'll cherish every bite
It's on the house
Just dig in
After all,
you lot are
Serika's friends
No one's here, even
with ramen this good
Probably the location
This area's been losing
residents from the desertification
No⋯
We are not friends!
- Don't shout
- I get it now
This shop is the problem
This shop!
What do you mean?
Don't you like the ramen here?
Of course I do!
It's savory
The portions are huge
Even the cook is great
Then what's the problem?
Everything!
We're here to work
Hardboiled outlaws
like us
shouldn't be swayed
by cheap kindness
-I don't get it
- I understand
Haruka
Haruka, you
understand me right?
Yes
We've got to destroy
this shop, right?
Haruka, what do you mean by
"destroy?"
Just that
Why do you—?
Fire in the hole
Wait, Haruka!
There was an explosion
within 10-kilometers of here
The location was⋯
Ayane?
Shiba Seki Ramen
Why there?
What could they
possibly be after?
Maybe Serika?
Me? Why?
For now,
let's head over
What about Hoshino?
I'll tell her
We have to rescue the master
Right
Wait for us,
Master!
Ow⋯
What happened?
Found you, Aru
Mutsuki, Kayoko⋯
You okay, Boss?
Y-Yeah
Where's Haruka?
She should be nearby⋯
So she really planted a bomb
at Shiba Seki
Come to think of it,
what was our plan, exactly?
We went over it this morning⋯
But this wasn't
a part of it
What?
What do we do now?
What's the problem?
Isn't this what you wanted?
You said "Destroy this shop,"
No, I said that
Haruka, are you all right?
Yes, I'm fine
Hey Aru⋯
Did I mess up?
I'm so sorry
I was the one who
set off that bomb
As penance,
I offer up my life!
Stop that
We need to figure out
our next move
Boss?
Look at this situation
We're real villains
now, huh?
Huh?
So we met our goal?
What are you
talking about?
You wanted to be
a villainess, right?
Huh?
You blew up
the ramen shop
They fed us, and you
nuked them on a whim
You're so diabolical,
Aru
Of course I am!
Merciless and ruthless!
"We'll do the crime
if you've got the dime,"
That's our motto
Problem Solver 68!
Look over there
It's that part-timer
from the ramen shop
What are you
doing here?
What do you think?
Did you really blow
up Shiba Seki Ramen?
If we did?
We won't let you
get away with it
You hear that, Aru?
The timing's awful
But we have to deal
with them eventually
I won't fail you again, Aru
Wh-What do I do?
Should I just tell the
truth and say sorry?
What about
our reputation?
What about my pride
as an outlaw?
Hey, don't just stand
there glassy-eyed
Answer us
Zip it!
You're right
We were the ones who
blew up Shiba Seki Ramen
Us, Problem Solver 68!
Now you know just
how nasty we can be
Aru!
Serika
The master's safe
How is he?
Just some minor injuries
What a relief
We'll get him to safety,
then head your way
Got it
- Serika, good news!
- Unforgivable
Serika⋯
Shiroko
I'm sorry, but I
can't just stand by
Me neither
All right, bring it
Let's go!
What now?
- It's them
- Them?
Why now of all times?
Aru, wake up
Aru, Aru!
Is everyone okay?
I'm fine
Where'd that
artillery come from?
That was⋯
The attack came from over there
Shelling successful
Targets are on the back foot
What's our next move, Iori?
It seems we have some
unexpected guests
Who are they?
What was the name⋯
Abydos?
Right, The Abydos High
School Foreclosure Task Force
(Prefect Team) What to
do? That's obvious, Chinatsu
Anyone who gets in
the way of our duties
IS an enemy
I'll take a window seat on this journey to find
the place where my heart belongs
So I can see beyond this sorrow chasing me
We were losing track of time without ever knowing why
With all those laughs we shared⋯
Even if⋯those moments were just ordinary
Those days⋯
One more time, one time more,
Knowing they won't come around again!
If only I could stay as resolute and beautiful
As the moon hanging in the bright noon sky
Would that let me finally forgive
All those regrets we made so willfully?
We only recognize the important things
Once they're gone and lost out of sight
We stretch up to the moon in the bright noon sky
Even though it will always be beyond our reach
Oh, those unforgettable, beautiful days⋯