What did you just say?!
A-Ayane, c-could you repeat that one more time?
Serika, calm down, please!
I am calm!
Sh-She's right, Serika!
We shouldn't panic!
Teacher, you're shaking.
Ayane, are you sure?
I am.
I went through all the documents we acquired,
and it definitely seems that Kaiser Loan
has been funding the Helmet Gang.
No...
You're kidding.
If that's really true,
then those jerks from the Helmet Gang,
the same people who've been trying to gun us down,
have been buying their weapons using our money!
Yup, there it is.
Collected 7.88 million.
Hang on, isn't this...
Yes. It's exactly what you think it is.
Is there something special
about this 7.88 million?
Wait, could this be...
Yes. This is the exact amount we paid them.
7.88 million is a lot.
You were in that much debt?
This is only a fraction. The total is over 900 million.
Well, well, we can get into
the finer details some other time.
This document lists all of Kaiser Loan's cash flows.
And here we see a figure that matches
our 7.88 million payment down to the yen.
This has to have come from
the debt collector that visits our school.
And then there's this.
Right after depositing the 7.88 million yen,
they allocated 5 million yen towards
"strategic allocations" to the Kata Kata Helmet Gang.
Strategic allocations...
They sent the Kata Kata Helmet Gang
five million yen to help fund their job.
Job?
It was probably to take us out of the picture.
So that means...
It means Kaiser Loan has been
our true enemy all along!
But why would they do this?
If the school went bankrupt,
they wouldn't be able to get back
the money they loaned us.
D-Did you say Kaiser Loan?!
They're the loan sharks run by
the infamous Kaiser Corporation, right?
I doubt Kaiser Loan is acting on its own.
Shiroko?
Kaiser Corporation's main branch
must be involved in this as well.
You may be right.
Thank you for helping me earlier!
Don't mention it. If anything, we should be
apologizing for dragging you into our mess.
I think I'll report this situation to the Tea Party.
Hifumi?
The Kaiser Corporation must have ties
to criminals and other underground dealings.
And this could help prove it!
Besides, now that I've gotten to know you,
I can't leave you to fend for yourselves.
Hifumi...
We appreciate it!
If Trinity's student council could lend us a hand,
we'd be in a much better position.
Isn't that right, Hoshino?
Honestly, this has been quite a shock.
I can't believe you're a billion yen in debt.
Hey, it's not that much! It's only 960 mil—
Serika, she was just rounding it.
I-In any case, I'm sure once
the Tea Party hears about this—
Pretty sure it's old news to them.
I'm sorry?
And not just over at the Tea Party.
I bet the hotshots over at Gehenna
and Millenium all know already.
Really? But if they know what's going on, then why?
They knew, and simply chose not to do anything about it.
They chose not to?
I know you mean well, and I appreciate it,
but the world's a bit more complex than that.
Even if you went ahead and told them,
it might just complicate things for us.
Why would it?
Think about it. Abydos is
on the verge of shutting down, right?
Not a whole lot's gonna stop these schools
from asking us to "return the favour" for helping us.
You see what I'm getting at?
Umm, basically, if they said they'd help
but then took advantage of the situation,
you would be powerless to stop them?
Yup.
Hoshino, aren't you being a bit too cynical?
Yeah. We could really use all the help we can get.
I agree.
But there's always the off chance, right?
The off chance...
Ooooh, this is a tough one.
It'll be fine!
I'm sure we'll find a way.
There has to be something we can do, r-right?
Oh, c'mon!
Show some conviction at least!
I mean, thinking about this logically...
Well, then quit thinking.
I mean, everyone was looking at me, so...
Of course everyone was gonna look at you
if you said something at that moment.
The off chance, huh?
C'mon, you should be used to this by now.
It's precisely because we neglected
the off chance that Abydos ended up like this.
And anyway you're—
Teacher is doing the best he can to help us.
Hey there, let this old soul in on the fun.
What's all the chatter about?
You won't believe this.
Hifumi was just saying—
Saying what? Mind repeating it, Faust?
Please stop calling me that!
Oh, that's right.
She's the proud leader of the Masked Swimsuit Gang!
I am most definitely not!
Hey, quit picking on Hifumi!
Well, I should get going.
Today was a lot of fun.
I'm sure you had fun,
but what about the rest of us?
We'll drop by one of these days,
so let's hang out then.
Hifumi, good luck out there.
You, too.
I know it's tough, but I'll be cheering you on!
Yeah!
Goodbye for now!
I wonder if we'll really be okay.
Well, let's not dwell on it anymore for today.
I'm all tuckered out.
In that case, let's meet back up tomorrow.
Go home and rest up for today, everyone.
Good idea.
Sounds good to me.
Staying up late is bad for your skin, y'know?
Morning.
Good m—Whoa!
Aru, were you up all night or something?
No, I caught a few winks.
Hey, Aru. We've come up
with a new plan to attack Abydos.
Right, Kayoko?
We plant explosives in key locations ahead of time,
and when they get near them,
we blow them to kingdom come.
Haruka's out making preparations...
Are you listening?
Y-Yes, I heard you!
But you were...
I was just thinking about some things.
Just to be sure, can we go ahead with this plan?
Yeah.
You know, if you're losing sleep over it,
why don't we just take the money
they left behind and put it towards our funds?
We can't do that.
This money is something
those girls left behind by accident.
Using it would just be uncool.
True outlaws wouldn't do that.
Then why didn't we get an advance from the client?
No upfront payments.
That's the one policy I refuse to break.
We've been over this, haven't we?
Because accepting payment in advance
means we're forced to comply with their demands.
That's why, right?
Exactly.
Now that you mention it, that may ring a bell.
We only take money for
a job well done. No exceptions.
If we waver, we'll never achieve the vision
we've strived for for so long.
Our vision? We had one?
Of course we do!
To be a group of hard-boiled outlaws,
unshackled by rules or laws!
That's the vision of Problem Solver 68!
Y'know, boss, we could always just
throw in the towel and go back to Gehenna.
But wouldn't the Prefect Team
be all over us if we did that?
Good point. The Prefect Team would be a problem.
A big problem. They're the
strongest group in all of Kivotos, no?
Yeah, but that's only because of
the Head Prefect, Hina.
It's no exaggeration to say the bulk
of their firepower comes from just her.
In other words,
the rest of them should be easy pickings.
Now that's some confidence.
Well, only if we play our cards right.
No. Going back to Gehenna is not an option.
Not for a group of hard-boiled outlaws,
unshackled by rules or laws.
Oh yeah, Problem Solver 68's
vision or whatever, right?
Exactly.
Welcome back, Haruka.
Had fun out there?
I'm back.
Miss Aru.
Just say the word.
I'll blow it all to smithereens for you.
With my own two hands.
Oh man, Aru.
Sounds like someone's hungry!
S-Shut it, you!
Wanna grab a bite?
Yes. Let's.
What are we thinking? Ramen over at Shiba Seki?
Umm...
Don't worry about the part-timer.
She only works in the afternoon, so we're good.
All right, then. Come on, everyone.
Come on, Haruka. We're leaving.
Oh, coming.
Good morning.
You're early today.
Morning, Teacher.
Umm...
What are you two doing here this early?
Sorry, but I've got dibs on this lap.
This is my special napping spot.
No, I wasn't going to join you.
C'mon now, Hoshino.
There's enough lap for both of you.
No, really. I wasn't going to join her...
Upsy daisy.
Where are you going?
Today's my day off.
I'll go kill time somewhere else,
so give me a holler if you need me.
I suppose she's off to take a nap?
Yes, probably.
Well, it's good weather for a nap.
Hoshino's changed a lot.
She acts like a lazy sleepyhead nowadays,
but back when I first met her,
she always looked like she was
weighed down by something.
Weighed down? By what?
Anything and everything, I suppose.
From what I heard, back when Hoshino enrolled,
there used to be another older student here.
Apparently, she was the last
student council president Abydos ever had.
So once she was gone,
Hoshino ended up shouldering
all the responsibilities alone.
She was only a first-year at the time, too.
I'm not sure if that was why,
but she's always been against involving other schools.
She's mellowed out a lot since then.
Well, it's not like I was there,
so I only know so much.
Maybe it's because I'm here now?
Huh?
Maybe that's why she changed.
Just kidding.
I-I mean, you know...
What I'm trying to say is...
Yes, I'm sure you're right.
Thanks fer waiting!
Aw, yeah!
I've been looking forward to this!
So good!
O-One bowl per person?
Is it really okay for us to have all this?
Don't worry 'bout it.
Y'all came all the way over just for my ramen.
What more's there to say?
Th-Thank you so much!
From the bottom of my heart!
Thank you!
We really can't thank you enough.
Don't mention it!
Well then, I'll have to enjoy this gracious gift.
I'll give ya a li'l extra on the house,
so eat your fill, y'hear?
A friend o' Serika's a friend o' mine.
Strange how it's so empty when the food's this good.
Isn't it just the location?
People have been leaving
because of the desertification, right?
We're not...
We're not their friends!
Hey, you're making a scene.
I get it now!
I've figured out what my problem is.
It's this restaurant!
Uhhh, what?
I thought you liked the ramen here.
Of course I do!
This place has good food,
gives very generous portions,
and the people here are nothing but nice!
So what's the problem?
Don't you see? All of it!
We're here on business!
We're supposed to be hard-boiled outlaws!
But this cozy atmosphere is turning us
into soft-boiled outlaws!
I'll be honest, you've lost me.
I understand.
Haruka?
You understand what I'm trying to say, Haruka?
Yes.
You're saying this restaurant should go, right?
Huh?
Haruka, could you clarify what you mean by "go"?
Exactly what I said. It has to go.
Wha—
What are you doing with that?
Here goes.
Wait, Haruka!
There's been an explosion in town,
ten kilometres from here!
The exact site is...
Ayane?
The exact site is Shiba Seki Ramen.
Why would anyone target that place?!
What—No, who are they after?
Could it be Serika?
What? Why me?!
We can figure that out once we get there!
What about Hoshino?
I'll let her know.
We need to hurry and help the boss!
Right!
Just hold on, boss!
Owww...
What happened?
There's our Aru. Found her!
Mutsuki, Kayoko…
Are you okay, Boss?
Y-Yes, I'm fine.
Where's Haruka?
She should be somewhere around here.
I can't believe she even planted C4
in the ramen place...
Oh, speaking of, what even was the plan with that?
Exactly what I told you before.
Except this bit wasn't part of the plan.
Excuse me?!
So, what now?
Huh?!
I mean, think about it.
Wasn't this exactly what you wanted?
You said you wanted the restaurant gone, right?
A-Actually, I-I was the one who said that.
Haruka, are you okay?
Yes, I'm completely fine.
But more importantly, Miss Aru.
Have I perhaps just made things worse?
I-I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
I thought it would be better to have
more bombs in more places, so...
At this point I should just die for my...
Maybe later.
First things first, we should talk about...
Boss?
L-Looking at this situation...
Are we the baddies? We are, aren't we?
Hm?
Well, then. Mission accomplished, right?
Huh? Wh-What do you mean?
I mean, wasn't the whole point to become a bad guy?
After everything those nice people did for you,
you were so terrified you'd grow a conscience,
you decided to blow up the entire place.
You're as cold-blooded and ruthless as they come, Aru!
Th-That's right! No morals! No mercy!
Pay us the dime and we do the crime!
That's our motto!
Problem Solver 68!
Well, well, well, if it isn't that
cute little part-timer from Shiba Seki Ramen.
You four... What do you think you're doing there?
Who knows. Why don't you take a guess?
Were you the ones who destroyed Shiba Seki Ramen?
So what if we are?
Then we'll respond with appropriate force.
You heard the girl, Aru.
I didn't think it'd be so soon,
but we were going to have to
settle the score one of these days anyway.
I-I'll make it right to you
this time, Miss Aru! I promise!
Wh-Wh-Wh-What now?
Should I just come clean and give an honest apology?
But if I do, then our reputation as Problem Solver 68...
Our pride as outlaws is toast!
Hey, she asked you a question!
Don't just stand there, say something!
Q-Quiet, you!
Yes, that's right!
The ones who blew up Shiba Seki Ramen
were none other than us,
Problem Solver 68!
Finally getting the picture now?
We're bad to the bone!
Miss Aru!
Aru!
Serika...
The boss is secure!
How is he?!
Only minor injuries!
Thank goodness.
I'll escort him to the nearest shelter.
Then I'll rendezvous with you!
Got it!
Aren't you glad he's okay, Serika?
Too damn far.
Serika?
Shiroko,
I'm sorry,
but I'm not calming down this time!
I'm with you.
Come on, then, have at you!
You're dead!
Oh come on, what now?!
It's them.
"Them"?
But why now, of all times?
Miss Aru! Please, wake up!
Miss Aru! Miss Aru!
Is everyone okay?
I'm fine!
For the love of—Now what?!
What just happened?
It looks like we've been shelled by someone up ahead.
Targets appear to be in disarray
following our mortar strike.
Now then, how should we do this, Iori?
There are a couple unexpected guests with them.
Oh yeah, what's-their-face?
Abydos, I think?
Correct. The Abydos High School
Foreclosure Task Force.
Why bother asking? The answer's
always going to be the same, Chinatsu.
Anyone who interferes with our official duties...
is an enemy.