Miss Aru! Miss Aru!
Hoo boy. That looks like bad news.
I can't believe they chased us all the way here...
But why?
They just opened fire! In our school district!
Were they aiming for us? Or Problem Solver 68?
Sensei, are they…?
Yes.
Those girls...
are the Gehenna Prefect Team.
Sensei, it’s dangerous here.
Get clear and keep your head down.
Right, thanks.
God, what a pain.
Don’t complain, Iori.
Why can’t we just attack them?
We need to talk to them first.
We’re here to catch troublemakers from our school, not talk.
If they get in our way, we’ll just-
First we explain why we’re here.
Then we listen to what they have to say, and we negotiate.
And only if that doesn’t solve the problem, we fight.
Do we really need to do all of that?
These people aren’t from our school.
We may not have meant to attack them earlier,
but under normal circumstances, it would have been a grave offense.
Fine, I get it.
I’ll just hurry up and tell them, then.
Iori, wait!
Relax. I got this.
Wakey wakey, Aru(-chan)
Miss Aru!
Good morning, sunshine.
Boss. We need to hurry and get out of here.
Get out?
Why?
The Prefect Team is here.
Prefect…
Why- (muffled)
Quiet.
They’ll hear us if you shout.
Has Hoshino(-senpai) still not responded yet?
She’s never gone dark for this long before…
Hello there, everyone from Abydos High School.
What business does the Prefect Team from Gehenna have here?
And why did you shell us?
Oh, you know. Just thought we’d drop some tough love on a few rule breakers hiding in the area.
Are you talking about Problem Solver 68?
Right on.
So you see, we’re not actually here for you.
That’s why I’m letting you walk away.
I suggest you take the hint and leave.
And if we don’t?
This is the Perfect Team we’re dealing with.
If we’re not careful, we could end up seriously hurt.
It could even spark a larger international incident.
I hate that they’re allowed to just do this,
but we wouldn’t stand a chance against them.
I think we have to obey.
That’s not an option.
She’s right! PS68 still needs to pay for what they did!
But…
The boss had nothing to do with this, and look what they did to him.
Serika(-chan)...
We’re not leaving.
They refused a demand from the Prefects?
You’re kidding. They’re so screwed.
Miss Aru, now’s our chance.
We should leave while we can.
…Miss Aru?
You know, a true outlaw wouldn’t spend her days regretting her past actions forever, would she?
She wouldn’t pin her mistakes on someone else and slink off like a coward, either.
Don’t be ridiculous. This isn’t the time for -
A true outlaw…
The outlaws that we strive to become
would never betray what they believed in, no matter the enemy. Am I wrong?
Aru…
I’ll take that as your response, then.
After I went to the effort of playing nice…
Don’t say I didn’t warn you.
Ayane(-chan)!
Iori? For the love of-
Not bad.
Shiroko(-chan)!
Why, you little!
Serika(-chan)!
Hardly worth the effort.
Wait!
And who are you?
Wait, Iori!
Get out of here, Sensei!
Sensei?
Wait, are you that teacher from SCHALE?
You’re wide open.
Is everyone okay?
I’m okay.
I thought I recognized you, Sensei.
I didn’t expect to meet you here, of all places.
You’re…
It’s been a while, Chinatsu.
If we had known you were here…
We have no excuse for this.
I’m Okusora Ayane, Abydos Foreclosure Task Force.
I see you’re with the Gehenna Prefect Team,
but could you please explain yourselves?
Well…
Allow me to answer your question.
Hello, students of Abydos.
I am the Senior Administrator of the Prefect Team at Gehenna Academy.
My name is Amau Ako.
Now, before we go any further,
members of the Foreclosure Task Force…
I would like to apologize for this treatment.
It would be better if you said that after you lowered your guns.
My, how thoughtless of me.
All hands, stand down.
They seriously lowered their weapons?
As I was saying, allow me to apologize for my colleague’s foolish behavior.
Foolish behavior?
I did exactly as ordered.
Iori?
You remember where the templates for written apologies are, don’t you?
Hold on, Ako(-chan)?
Did your orders include the words “begin by firing indiscriminately at people” anywhere?
That wasn’t… I mean…
And to top it off, you did it outside of Gehenna,
near another school’s district.
Shouldn’t you know enough to take the location into account first?
I’m going to ask you again, Iori.
You remember where the templates for written apologies are, don’t you?
Inside your desk, left drawer.
Perfect. You know what to do, I’m sure.
Now, back to your question.
We’ve simply come here to apprehend some rule-breaking individuals from our school.
Can we ask for your cooperation in performing our duties as the Prefect Team?
Is that a request, or…?
Yes, it’s a request.
For now.
We can’t do that.
Oh? And why not?
It goes without saying.
This is our district.
It’s a clear violation of the rules for you to openly attack us like this.
We’ll decide how to deal with Problem Solver 68.
And what about the teacher from SCHALE? Do you share her view?
Yes.
In this case, I fully support their decision.
And I was so hoping for a peaceful resolution.
What a shame.
All hands, prepare to engage!
What was that?
Ambush?
Keep calm!
Check your surroundings!
How dare you do that to Miss Aru.
Unforgivable.
Unforgivable. Unforgivable!
Iori!
Heya! Did you miss me?
That went well.
Now then, let’s get this show started, shall we?
You! You’ll pay for what you did to-
I’m sorry.
Huh?
I’m surprised you chose to show yourselves.
But I suppose this saves us the trouble of searching for you.
They had a second group waiting.
Well, guess it couldn’t have been that easy.
I must say, this is quite the coincidence.
Who could have thought chasing Problem Solver 68 would lead to a meeting with the teacher of SCHALE?
Cut the act, Ako.
My.
Kayoko?
None of this was a coincidence.
You wanted this to happen from the start.
It’s too inefficient.
You brought far too many forces for a school like Abydos.
There’s no way your Head Prefect would ever authorize an operation like this.
You’re here for SCHALE.
This teacher is the reason you came all this way in the first place.
Me?
What is she talking about?
I’m impressed, Kayoko(-san). You’re quite observant.
Very well. I’m feeling generous, so I’ll explain everything.
It all started with the Tea Party.
As you may know, Trinity General School has a long history of conflict with Gehenna Academy.
Apparently their student council got their hands on a report regarding SCHALE,
and when our intelligence division brought word of this report to my desk, I simply couldn't ignore it.
At first, I had no idea what SCHALE even was,
but if it’s something the Tea Party knows about, then it’s something we need to know about.
I just so happened to have a report that Chinatsu(-san) had prepared, so I took the opportunity to read through it.
Except I had sent that report quite a while ago…
Just think. A mysterious organization,
left behind by the General Student Council President and headed by that teacher over there.
There’s no telling how this might tip the scales going forward.
That’s why we, the Gehenna Prefect Team,
would like to take him into our custody, at least until the Eden Treaty is safely signed.
Quit dreaming.
Did you really think we’d just hand him over?
We’ll protect our teacher.
I was afraid this would happen.
It seems we have no choice but to take drastic action.
If the Head Prefect were to find out about this, I’d be joining Iori in writing apologies.
Ako(-chan)?
Do you honestly think you can win with only the five of you?
Actually, it’s nine of us.
But they’re not after you.
Only a third-rate villain would run away without repaying a debt.
There’s our boss!
I’m not letting those prefects walk away without putting a bullet in each of their smug faces first.
Right on.
Kuromi Serika.
We’re going to be fighting together, so at least get my name right.
It’s not “part-timer”.
The name’s Rikuhachima Aru.
Onikata Kayoko.
And I’m Asagi Mutsuki.
I-I’m Igusa Haruka.
C-Charmed.
I’m Izayoi Nonomi.
And my name is Okusora Ayane.
Sunaookami Shiroko.
Hey!
This is your last chance to change your mind.
After this, you can beg, you can pay money, you can lick my feet -
I’d love to, but I’ll have to pass this time.
That’s quite the unlikely alliance you’ve made.
But no matter.
You’ll soon know the true terror of -
You talk too much.
Begin the attack!
Nonomi, Haruka! Take 3 o’clock!
Got it!
Serika, Mutsuki! You two take 9 o’clock!
Leave it to me!
Okay!
Shiroko, Aru! You’re up front, high noon!
Roger!
Ayane and Kayoko, support the others.
Understood.
Got it!
Haruka(-san), what should we do?
I'll go first.
Wait, hold on!
Die, please, die, please, die, please!
Haruka(-san)!
T-T-T-Thank you…
Oh, no, don’t mention it!
Heads up, part-timer!
Hey, you're not half bad, part-timer!
Of course I’m not.
All right, let’s keep the party going!
Another grenade!
No way!
Oh sh-
There you are, you little rats.
You’re not getting away this time.
Great work, Haruka(-san)!
Oh, no.
It was all thanks to your help, Nonomi(-san)
No, no, you did great.
Drop your gun and surrender, please.
Quit running around, you little jerks.
Come out and take your beating!
She’s fast!
I’ve got you now!
It’s all you, part-timer.
What?
My name’s not “part-timer”!
Well, what do we have here?
You’ve got some guts, calling me a rat.
Dammit. You think you’re so tough?
I’ll kick your asses!
What are you waiting for? Come on!
3 o'clock, 9 o'clock, all clear. No hostile presence.
All right. All that’s left is 12 o’clock.
Shiroko, Aru. Just a little bit more!
You know, we were interrupted earlier, but I wonder.
If we did end up fighting, who do you think would win?
It’s obvious.
You’re right, it is.
We would win.
Here they come!
Fire!
Shiroko! We need to close the distance, or we’ll be sitting ducks!
You may have joined forces,
but you’re still powerless against the might of -
Did we get her?
It’s over.
It appears asking nicely for you to hand the teacher over to us…
is no longer an option.
I’m impressed that you can still talk big at this point.
Just give up already.
I don’t think you understand the situation.
You have no choice but to comply.
We still have many soldiers just waiting for my command to -
Ako.
Huh?
President Hina?
I expect an explanation for all of this.
I, well, you see…
I was just trying to capture those no-good students over there, and
You mean Problem Solver 68?
I don’t see them anywhere.
What do you mean? They’re right -
Huh?
What? How? They were right there!
President Hina! There’s a perfectly good reason for all of this.
No, it’s fine. I’ve got the general picture.
Ako, we’re the Prefect Team, not the student council.
I, well, I mean…
We’ll talk when I get back.
Stay put in the school building until then
Yes, ma’am…
Now, then.
Gehenna’s Head Prefect.
Are you already aware of what has happened here?
An unauthorized military operation within another school’s district without prior notification,
resulting in conflict with said school’s students.
Yes. In other words -
But it’s also true that you obstructed the duties of the Gehenna Prefect Team.
Am I wrong?
Looks like things have taken quite the turn.
Hoshino(-senpai)?!
Where have you been this whole time?
Sorry about that, I was having a little nap.
A nap?
Hoshino, from Abydos…
Could she be Takanashi Hoshino?
Not sure what’s going on,
but what’s with the army?
Miss Head Prefect.
You’ve changed quite a bit since your first year.
I almost didn’t recognize you.
My my, you know about me?
While I was in the intelligence division,
I maintained a working understanding of all the persons of interest from each school district.
You’re telling me this old man’s famous or something?
Takanashi Hoshino,
I could never forget you.
I thought you had left Abydos following the incident.
I see.
So that’s why SCHALE -
What’s that now?
This old man can’t keep up if you don’t say what you mean.
Prepare to withdraw.
We’re leaving?
President Hina?
For executing an unauthorized military operation without prior notification,
and for causing trouble in another school’s district,
I, Sorasaki Hina, hereby issue an official apology to the Abydos Foreclosure Task Force.
We’re done here. Let’s go.
Ma’am!
Sensei, what did she say?
Oh, right.
The abandoned desert in Abydos.
Kaiser Corporation is plotting something there.
Sensei?
Hoo, man.
I gotta say, I’m feeling kind of lost here.
So, what happened?
I can’t believe you, Hoshino(-senpai)!
I agree! Where were you when we needed you?
Sensei! They’re being mean to me!
All right! Let’s all go home.
I’m pooped.