(Prefect)
Aru, Aru!
Oh, geez, We need to
get out of here fast
I didn't think they'd
chase us all the way here
There's no way⋯ Why?!
Why're they attacking unprovoked?
This is still Abydos!
But are they targeting us?
Or Problem Solver 68?
Sensei, those students are⋯
I know
They're⋯
The Gehenna Prefect Team
The sky blue archive!
I pedal on my bike seeking new sights
We'll break the monotony,
no longer trapped in place
Daydreaming on the rooftop,
gazing at a sky so blue
Those clouds like whales are always changing
We'll embrace a past that can't be altered
Sharing juice in this world made of sand
Is a taste so divine
If I were here alone, here without all of you
I couldn't laugh, I couldn't cry
A fateful coterie
Even if the world's memories blow away
like grains of sand one day
The sky, sea, wind, and you,
our youth will never end
It's easy to see why we protect what we do
Because this is the only place where we belong
Sensei, it's too dangerous
Go find cover behind us
Okay, Thank you
What a bother
Patience, Iori
Why do we have to wait?
Because there is such
a thing as procedure
So much red tape just to catch
a handful of delinquents
If anyone wants to
get in our way, then⋯
First, we need to explain the circumstances
and assess the opponent's position
We'll negotiate from there
If we can't come to an understanding,
then we can fight
Is all of that really necessary?
This is foreign territory
Even if it wasn't directed at them,
our earlier attack wouldn't have
gone unpunished anywhere else
I get it
Then I'll head over
and explain the situation
Wait a second, Iori!
It's okay, Leave it to me
Hey, Aru
— Aru
— Good morning, Aru!
Boss, we need to hurry up and leave
Leave? Why?
The Prefect Team's here
The Prefect Team⋯?
- Why are they—
- Keep it down
They'll find us if you're too loud
You still can't get a hold of Hoshino?
No⋯ She's never gone
dark on us like this before
Hey, Abydos High School students
What is the Gehenna
Prefect Team doing here?
And why did you bomb us?
About that, Some criminals
ran away to your district,
and we were teaching them a lesson
Are you talking about Problem Solver 68?
Exactly
So we really don't have
any beef with you guys
That's why I'll let you off the hook
if you back down right now
What if we don't?
We're up against the Prefect Team
Fighting them might
not end well for us
It could also cause
huge political issues
I'm frustrated with this situation too,
but the gap in power is too big
Wouldn't it be wiser
to back down for now?
We can't do that
She's right, We still need to
make Problem Solver 68 pay
But⋯
The master was injured, and he
had nothing to do with this
Serika⋯
We won't stand down
Those kids turned down
the Prefect Team's offer
Seriously? They don't know
what they're getting into
Aru, now's our chance
Let's leave while
they're distracted
Aru?
Hey, To continue regretting
something you've already done
isn't very hard boiled, is it?
Blaming others for
your own mistakes
and running away isn't
very hard boiled, either
What are you saying?
Now isn't the time⋯
An outlaw⋯
Being a real outlaw means
not compromising our beliefs
no matter who our opponent is
Aru
Is that your final answer?
Yes
I did all this diplomacy
for nothing
Your funeral!
Ayane!
Iori, not again
Not bad
Shiroko!
How dare you!
Serika!
Just a bunch of nobodies
Stop!
Who are you?
Hold your fire, Iori!
Run, Sensei!
Sensei?
Are you, by chance,
from Schale?
Keep your guard up
Is everyone okay?
Y-Yes
It really is you, Sensei
I didn't expect to run into you here
You're⋯
It's been a while, Chinatsu
If I had known you were here⋯
My apologies
I'm Okusora Ayane from the
Abydos Foreclosure Task Force
You may be the Gehenna Prefect Team,
but what justification do
you have to attack us?
It's because⋯
Allow me to answer that question
Hello, Abydos students
I'm the senior administrator
of the Gehenna Prefect Team,
Amau Ako
Let's start over
Foreclosure Task Force members,
I apologize for any inconvenience
caused by this incident
Don't you think
you should lower your weapons
before saying such things?
Oh, Yes, yes
Everyone, at ease
They actually did it
Now,
allow me to apologize
for our foolish actions
Foolish actions?
I just followed orders
Iori
Do you know where to
find the self-reflection form?
A-Ako!
Did your orders include
firing indiscriminately
as you pleased?
Not exactly, but—
And this isn't Gehenna
Since you're in another school's district,
it should be a given to
proceed with caution, no?
Let me ask again, Iori
Do you know where to
find the self-reflection form?
In the left drawer of your desk
Please complete it when you return
Now, back to business
We're here to apprehend
criminals from our district
Will you cooperate
with the Prefect Team?
Is that a request? Or⋯
It's a request,
at least for now
We won't cooperate
Oh my, Why not?
No matter your justification,
this is our district
Openly attacking us like this is
a clear violation of the law
Problem Solver 68's discipline
falls under our jurisdiction
Sensei of Schale⋯
Are you of the same opinion?
Yes, For this matter,
I'm on their side
I really did want to
resolve this peacefully,
but I suppose we have no other choice
Everyone, prepare for battle!
Huh?
Wh-What?
An ambush?!
Calm down!
Secure the perimeter!
You dare attack Aru?
Unforgivable!
Unforgivable! Unforgivable!
Iori!
Hey! Long time no see
All according to plan
Shall we have some fun?
You guys!
- How dare you attack the master—
- Sorry
I'm surprised you gave
yourself up so easily
But it saves us the trouble
of hunting you down
A double envelopment?
Ah, I thought it was too easy
It appears this unexpected encounter
has gotten out of hand
From chasing Problem Solver 68
to running into Schale's Sensei⋯
That's pretty shameless, Ako
- Huh?
- Kayoko?
None of this is a coincidence
You were aiming for this exact
result from the beginning
Your methods are inefficient
So many forces, just
to confront Abydos⋯
The Prefect Team never
handles business like this
Your goal is Schale
From the beginning, you came
all this way to target Sensei
Me?
What does she mean?
As expected of you, Kayoko
Always so clever
Since it's come to this,
allow me to explain
It all started with the Tea Party
Gehenna has a long-standing
rivalry with Trinity
Trinity's student council got
a hold of a report about Schale,
according to findings from
our Intelligence Committee
At that time, I had no idea
who or what Schale was,
but since the Tea Party
was privy to that intel,
I made it my business to find out
That's when I remembered a report
Chinatsu had submitted
But I sent that report so long ago--
The General Student Council president
left Sensei at the head
of this shadowy organization-
Who knows what kind of
influence it might wield?
Therefore, at least until the Eden
Treaty is safely concluded,
we plan to put Sensei
under our protection
And just who's calling those shots?
Do you think we'll surrender
Sensei without a fight?
We're the ones protecting Sensei
I expected as much
But we need him too,
so there's no other choice
If the head prefect
hears of this,
I'll have to complete the
self-reflection form with Iori
Ako
Do you think you can take
us on with just you five?
It's nine people!
They're not here for you guys!
Running away without repaying
our debts at a time like this?
That's third-rate villain stuff
How eloquent, Aru!
I won't be able to rest easy until we've put
that cocky Prefect Team in their place
- Yeah
- That's right
⋯Kuromi Serika
We should know each other's names
if we're going to fight together
I'm not just "Part-Timer,"
Rikuhachima Aru
- Onikata Kayoko
- Asagi Mutsuki
I'm Igusa Haruka
Nice to meet you
And I'm Izayoi Nonomi
My name is Okusora Ayane
Sunaookami Shiroko
Listen up, there's no
turning back now
Even if you beg, offer money,
or lick our feet⋯
That's a tempting offer,
but I'll have to decline this time
I never expected
you all to join forces
Well, fine
We'll show you how terrifying
the Prefect Team is—
Enough yapping
Charge!
Nonomi, Haruka,
head to three o'clock!
- Yes!
Serika, Mutsuki
Take our nine o'clock!
Leave it to us!
Shiroko, Aru
Advance forward!
Twelve o'clock!
-Yes
- Okay
Ayane and Kayoko,
provide support!
- Yes
- Okay
Haruka, what should we do?
For now, I'll take the lead
Wait!
- Please die
- Haruka!
Please die
S-S-Sorry
No, don't worry about it
Let's go, Part-Timer
You're pretty good, Part-Timer
- That goes without saying
- Well then,
shall we continue?
Here they come again!
Seriously?
Shoot!
The rats come crawling out
You won't get away!
As expected, you're skilled, Haruka!
Not at all, It's thanks
to your support
No, not at all
Drop your weapon and surrender
Playing games and sneaking around?
Just give up and come out!
Fast!
Final blow!
Counting on you, Part-Timer
What?
I told you, my name isn't Part-Timer!
Now then, what to do?
Who said something about a rat?
Damn, I can't believe they
pushed me to this point
I'll crush you!
What're you waiting for?
Bring it on!
Enemies at both 3 and 9 o'clock
have been taken down!
Good! That just leave our 12!
Shiroko, Aru
Just a little more!
The meddlers got in the way earlier,
but what would've happened
if we'd fought back there?
Isn't it obvious?
Yes, It is obvious
Of course we'd win!
They're coming!
Open fire!
Shiroko, we need to close
the distance!
Even as a team,
what can you do in the
face of such sheer power?
Did we get them?
This is it!
Looks like you won't give up Sensei
that easily, hm?
You're still talking
big in this situation?
Won't you admit defeat?
You still don't get it?
You'll have no choice
but to accept our terms
I still have plenty more troops behind—
- Ako
- Huh?
Head Prefect Hina!
Explain very clearly the situation here
Um, well⋯
We're apprehending criminal students⋯
You mean Problem Solver 68?
Where are they?
What do you mean?
They're right there⋯
Huh?
No way, They were just here!
Head Prefect,
I'll explain everything
No need
I got the gist of it
Ako, we're the Prefect Team,
not the student council
I know, but⋯
We'll discuss this later
You're on probation until then
Understood
Well then
Gehenna Head Prefect
Do you fully understand
the situation here?
Deploying forces
in another school's district
without prior notice,
and engaging in combat with
students from said school
- Yes, that means⋯
- However
You also interfered with the
Prefect Team's official duties
Didn't you?
Oh boy, here we go again
with another commotion
Hoshino!
Where have you been all this time?
Sorry, sorry, I was taking a nap
A nap?
Hoshino from Abydos
Could it be Takanashi Hoshino?
I'm not sure what happened,
but why did you bring
all these kids here?
Head Prefect
You've changed a lot
since you were a first year
I almost didn't recognize you
Huh? You know me?
Back when I was
on the Intelligence Committee,
I had a pretty good grasp
of the key students in each district
An old-timer like me was that famous?
Takanashi Hoshino
I couldn't forget you even if I tried
I thought you left Abydos
after that incident
I see now
- That's why Schale⋯
- What?
If you don't articulate
your thoughts clearly,
you might put me in a tough spot
Prepare to withdraw
W-We're withdrawing?!
Head Prefect?
For deploying forces
without prior notice,
and causing a disturbance
in another school's district,
I, Sorasaki Hina, would like to
officially apologize to the
Abydos Foreclosure Task Force
We're withdrawing, Let's go
Yes
Sensei, what was that about?
Kaiser Corporation has
been up to something
in the desert of Abydos
Sensei?
Oh my, This old-timer still
has no idea what's going on
What exactly happened?
Get it together, Hoshino
She's right! You can't just disappear
at such a critical moment
Sensei, they're being mean to me!
Then, let's head back
Ugh, I'm tired
I'll take a window seat on this journey to find
the place where my heart belongs
So I can see beyond this sorrow chasing me
We were losing track of time without ever knowing why
With all those laughs we shared⋯
Even if⋯those moments were just ordinary
Those days⋯
One more time, one time more,
Knowing they won't come around again!
If only I could stay as resolute and beautiful
As the moon hanging in the bright noon sky
Would that let me finally forgive
All those regrets we made so willfully?
We only recognize the important things
Once they're gone and lost out of sight
We stretch up to the moon in the bright noon sky
Even though it will always be beyond our reach
Oh, those unforgettable, beautiful days⋯