It was my mistake.
It was my decision that led us down this path.
It's ironic, really.
It had to come to this for me
to finally realise you were right all along.
Do you remember when you explained
what it meant to take responsibility?
I couldn't really understand what
you meant at the time, but now I get it.
It's not experience that matters. It's choices.
Choices only you can make.
That's your duty, your responsibility, as an adult.
You were the one taught me that.
I have faith you'll find a choice that
will lead to a better outcome.
Away from the dark, twisted destination that lies ahead.
So please, Teacher.
Save them.
It's nice out.
Amidst the General Student Council's turmoil
following the President's disappearance,
Sanctum Tower has been re-lit,
and administrative functions are underway again.
Following this, the unrest throughout our
academy city of Kivotos is expected to slowly subside.
Oh, and...
Meow, meow, meow.
Next stop, Abydos High School.
This is my stop!
Shiroko, are you serious?!
Yeah.
You biked to the industrial district and back?
Do you have any idea how far that is?!
I wanted to go since
I've never seen it up close before.
And it ended up being the perfect distance.
You're crazy, Shiroko.
What did you do over the weekend, Serika?
I, uh...
I went to the library.
Huh? You were there too, Serika?
I was there yesterday, but I didn't see you.
W-Wow, really?
We must've totally missed each other!
What were you reading, Ayane?
I wanted to do a bit of research on the DOHC
I found while doing repairs the other day.
Oh, by the way, DOHC stands for
"Double Overhead Camshaft".
It's a type of engine.
I thought it might come in handy later.
Um, what about you, Hoshino?
Same ol' routine for an old-timer like me.
Figures.
Sounds like everyone had a fun weekend!
What about you, Nonomi?
Me?
I went shopping!
I picked up a couple of snacks,
some everyday necessities I was running low on...
Oh, and about forty dumbbells!
What.
Let's begin our regular meeting.
For starters, let's review
the current major news event.
The president of the General Student Council—
the GSC—has gone missing.
They are tasked with maintaining harmony
among the schools in the academy city of Kivotos,
which they would normally do
under the guidance of their President.
This incident may be what sparked
the recent unrest in various school districts.
Speaking of the GSC prez,
wasn't she involved with that treaty thing?
The non-aggression pact between
Trinity General School and Gehenna Academy?
The Eden Treaty.
Yes, that's the one!
Has that been signed yet?
The President was the one who proposed it,
but now that she's missing,
it's difficult to say what will happen with it.
I see.
Oh, speaking of which. Ayane.
The boss of Shiba Seki Ramen said
the Kata-Kata Helmet Gang is up to no good again.
Their ramen is really good.
D-Do you go there often, Shiroko?
Sometimes.
Is something wrong?
N-Not really.
Still, Abydos is getting more
and more dangerous as time goes on.
I'm starting to get concerned.
I've been trying to request aid from the GSC, but...
Their president has gone missing,
so they probably don't have time for us.
Well, not like we've got time to spare, either.
Thank you for choosing Kaiser Loans!
At this rate, you'll have paid everything off
in 309 years and 2 months!
See you again next month!
309 years and 2 months
until we've paid off our debt.
We still have a long way to go.
See you tomorrow.
Goodbye.
Bye-bye.
That took longer than expected.
Hey, did I hear that right, punk-ass ladies?
Did you just say I have "lame-ass hair"?
You dare insult my glorious pompadour?!
Boss, you're so cool!
Boss, we love you!
Yeah, that's right, gang!
So what?
If you got lame-ass hair,
what else we gonna call it?
Y-You're doubling down, you punks?
That's it! Light 'em up, gang!
Yessir!
Let's see you talk smack now!
Did you seriously think...
...your lame-ass bullets...
...could stop us?!
Oh, you're still alive.
Are you sunbathing?
Or did you collapse?
Water...
Help me...
Here.
I've got an energy drink.
Want a sip?
Man, you saved me there!
Thank you!
Shiroko, did you kidnap this poor man?!
Has Shiroko finally turned to a life of crime?!
Calm down, everyone!
We gotta cover this up
before the cops come knocking!
I didn't.
He says he has business with our school.
Huh?
So he's a client?
That's right.
Makes sense.
So that's it.
I knew Abydos was a desert,
but I didn't think it would be this hot.
I got so dehydrated on the way here that I collapsed.
Um, if you wouldn't mind,
could you tell us about yourself?
Oh, of course!
I'm a teacher from the Independent Federal
Investigation Club S.C.H.A.L.E.
Pleasure to meet you.
Huh?!
Hold on, so this guy's with the GSC?!
Yeah!
Looks like they finally accepted our request for aid!
Aren't you glad, Ayane?
I am! Sending all those requests finally paid off!
Now we can get our supplies!
On that note, may I have your attention, everyone?
I-Is this...?
I wanted to give you this.
Thank you so much!
Now we can start receiving ammunition and supplies!
Oh, we should tell Hoshino the good news as well.
She's probably napping in her usual spot.
I'll go wake her up.
Oh, right, Teacher.
Hm?
We haven't introduced ourselves yet.
That girl just now was Kuromi Serika, a first-year.
My name is Izayoi Nonomi. I'm a second-year!
It's a pleasure to meet you.
My name is Okusora Ayane. I'm a first-year.
I'm Sunaookami Shiroko. Second-year.
But I already told you earlier,
so I guess I didn't have to tell you again.
Ah, but I'm not trying to
make a big deal out of it or anything.
And finally, there's the president of the Task Force,
Takanashi Hoshino.
Together we make up the
Abydos High School Foreclosure Task Force.
Pleasure to meet you.
The pleasure's all mine.
Slow down, Serika.
My poor legs aren't what they used to be!
Quit messing around!
You're the club president, so act like it!
Meow meow, I'm Takanashi Hoshino.
Nice to meetcha.
Nice to meet you. I'm a teacher from Schale.
Hey, Teacher.
I'll give you a tour of our school.
The desertification around the Abydos district
has really taken a toll on this place.
Yes.
The school was already like this when I enrolled.
I haven't seen any other students so far.
Is it really just the five of you?
Yes, it's just us.
Truthfully, this school is in a lot of debt,
so everyone else left.
As the Foreclosure Task Force,
we take on all sorts of requests,
and we put the payouts towards paying off the debt.
You have it pretty rough.
The other day, we cleaned out a gymnasium.
Oh, Ayane was sick that day,
so it was just the four of us.
There was a lot more trash than expected,
but we got through it no problem.
But when we got back,
Ayane was really upset with us.
Huh? Why?
And this one?
Nobody is using this room.
Feel free to use it from now on.
Huh? You sure?
Yes.
The faculty office is full of sand, so...
Is it too small?
Not at all. Thank you.
Good.
Shiroko, why do you want to protect this school?
Gunfire?!
Attention, Abydos High School!
Today is the day you finally submit to us!
What?! It's the Kata-Kata Helmet Gang!
Of all times for them to show up...
Man, I can't even nap in peace.
Hmph. We'll just send 'em packing
like we always do.
Everyone, let's hurry to the yard!
Teacher, stay here and keep your head down.
Shiroko?!
Watch out!
Thank you, Arona!
You're welcome, Teacher!
Shiroko, here!
Thanks.
They just won't give up.
We're running low on ammo.
What should we do?
If only they showed up a bit later,
we'd have restocked.
It's not an issue.
Wait, Shiroko!
Give up already!
We know you're almost outta bullets!
What? Where did they get that information?
Doesn't matter, Ayane.
Ammo or not, we can take 'em on any day!
We gotta back up Shiroko!
Got it!
Come on, eat it!
We're not letting you have Abydos High School!
Shiroko?!
Shiroko! Nonomi!
Hoshino!
Everyone! We need to regroup!
These scrubs are all over the place!
Looks like the tip about their ammo
was right on the money!
It's time we end this once and for all.
All right!
Get 'em, gang!
Teacher, the Abydos students won't last long like this.
Let's go!
You guys hanging in there?
Just barely.
Everyone, stop bunching up.
We need to spread out!
Ugh, c'mon. Still not giving up?
You know you can't beat us.
We're just getting started!
This is bad. We have to do something
before they overwhelm us!
Dammit! I can't believe
we're about to lose to these jerks!
Everyone!
Who's this chump?
Why do you want to protect this school?
Teacher...
Why?
Because...
Because this school is the place where we belong.
Does everyone else feel the same way?
Of course!
Who the hell are you, anyway?
I'm their teacher.
Their teacher?
I came to help these girls.
Sorry, but I'll have to kindly ask you
to leave the premises.
First you show up outta nowhere,
and now you're bossing us around?
I'll turn you into Swiss cheese!
Let's do this, everyone!
Nonomi! Suppressive fire!
Leave it to me!
Serika, take aim!
Damn! I can't see a thing!
C-Calm down!
You ain't gotta tell me!
Nice going, you two!
What the hell is going on?
Oh no, you do—
Can't let the youngsters steal the show.
Coordinates locked in!
Shiroko, catch!
Nice timing, Ayane!
You think you're so tough!
Hey, get it together!
No, don't look!
H-Hey!
S-Stay away!
Checkmate!
Shiroko!
I said stay away!
W-Wait, hold on. I-I surrender!
It's over.
Ow!
Ow, ow, ow!
Hey, that hurts! Stop!
Leave already.
Fine!
We get the message! We're leaving!
We'll get you for this!
We did it, Shiroko!
Great work!
Never thought we'd swing that around.
It's all thanks to Teacher.
Who, me? I didn't do anything.
I'm your teacher. I couldn't ignore students in need.
Hmph!
We could have handled those losers on our own.
Ah, Serika, always gotta be so independent.
Quiet, you!
I could just eat you up, Serika!
You don't have to hide your appreciation.
Just shut up already!
Lemme go, Hoshino!
So this is what a teacher is like...
Strawberry milk...
Hey there, Arona.
I've been expecting you, Teacher!