Sorry for the wait!
Huh? Am I the first one here today?
What's this?
No way.
Oh, morning, Ayane!
Why?!
How could she?!
To everyone at the Abydos Task Force:
To start, please forgive me for using
a letter to say goodbye like this.
This kind of old-fashioned thing
suits an old timer like me, you see.
The thing is, I've actually been
receiving offers for a while.
They want me to work as a mercenary for Kaiser PMC.
In exchange, they'll pay off over half
of the debt Abydos still owes.
That's the gist, anyhow.
I may not look like it, but I've
actually got a bit of a reputation.
I know I got ahead of myself
a little back at the Black Market.
I'm sorry for not keeping that promise.
But this should give the Task Force
some breathing room at least.
This is all my responsibility to bear.
I need to do this as the last remaining
member of the Abydos student council.
So this is goodbye.
To our teacher:
To tell you the truth, I hated adults.
The day Shiroko brought you to us,
I was already thinking you were
just some no-good grown-up.
But you quickly got everyone to open up,
and eventually they all came to trust you.
So that's why I'm leaving the rest to you, okay?
You're their teacher. They trust you.
I'm sure they'll be okay.
I'm glad that I was able to
meet an adult like you before...
Nah, I've written enough sappy stuff for one day.
Shiroko.
Nonomi.
Serika.
Ayane.
Do this for me.
Protect our school.
Sure, it's covered in sand.
But for me, it's the only place left
that still means anything.
One last thing.
Just in case somewhere down the line,
I show up again as your enemy.
If that happens,
Destroy my halo.
I'm counting on you.
What the hell!
She'd just told us how people
do anything when they're desperate!
How can she expect us to accept this?!
Shiroko!
I'll go find her.
I have to help her!
Calm down, Shiroko!
She's right! We need to confirm the situation first.
But Hoshino's -
Keep up the fire until the area is secure!
The last remaining student council member
has withdrawn from Abydos.
The time has come.
We, the Kaiser Corporation, will seize control of Abydos High School!
Several hundred Kaiser PMC troops on approach!
They're firing indiscriminately on the city!
Of all times, why now?
We have to engage.
But what about Hoshino?
Everyone, stay calm.
Evacuating the civilians comes first.
How could they...
Are you okay?
Yeah, I'm fine.
What on earth is going on?
We're not sure, either.
Abydos Task Force spotted! Over here!
Shiroko.
Get to someplace safe for now!
Shiroko!
I've got you now!
Come on, get a grip!
You get that side!
Got it!
Damn! These guys are tough!
Nonomi!
I've got it!
Is everyone okay?
Yeah, I'm all right.
But...
They just keep coming.
No choice. We have to hold the line.
I had intended to find you at the school.
But I appreciate you meeting me halfway,
students of Abydos High School.
You're just attacking the city at this point!
It doesn't matter if you own the land here.
Nothing gives you the right to do that!
Besides, the school still belongs to Abydos!
This kind of invasion is a clear violation of the law!
I'll report you to the GSC!
You scumbags!
Give Hoshino back!
What are you all going on about?
Report me to the GSC, you say?
Interesting little theory.
Why don't you test it out right now?
You've already tried countless times to tell
them about your situation, haven't you?
Did any of it ever help you fix your debt problem?
Finally starting to get the picture?
Struggle all you might, but nothing will ever change.
And now, Takanashi Hoshino, the final member
of the Abydos student council, has withdrawn.
With this, Abydos no longer has a student council.
And all of you are no longer anybody at all.
Don't be ridiculous!
Student council or no, Abydos still has the Task Force!
You can't get away with that while we're still -
The Task Force isn't an
officially sanctioned organization.
Huh?
Ayane?
By the time we formed the Task Force,
there already wasn't a student council anymore.
That's right!
You're merely an unofficial club.
No documentation, no official approval.
In other words, you have nothing to prove that you exist!
But here's the good news.
Once Abydos High School is no more,
you'll all finally be free of that debt for good!
What? But if that happens, then what about
all of our hard work until now?
Oh?
Were you actually planning on paying
everything back over hundreds of years?
What a surprise.
I was convinced that you were only doing this
so you could say "Well, we tried" at the end.
Why did you all work so hard, then?
What was it all for?
Why, you... If you say one more word...
I'll shoot you.
Will fighting here even change anything?
Ayane?
Even if we did win here, what would we do after that?
Even if we somehow took back our school,
we still have a huge debt to pay off.
All the land we lost wouldn't come back, either.
And above all, Hoshino's gone.
The student council is gone.
Just look at us.
We're nothing but an unofficial club.
What more could we even do?
Ayane...
Why?
Why us and nobody else?
Hoshino...
What are we supposed to do?
A large explosion reported north of here!
Bravo Squadron got caught in the blast!
What?
One to the east, too!
Mike Squadron got hit by a massive C4 explosion -
What's going on?
Give me a break.
I'd rather die than listen to
one more second of this complaining.
An eye for an eye. A tooth for a tooth.
We tread a path that none may follow,
and we do so without mercy.
Wasn't that supposed to be your motto,
Masked Swimsuit Gang?
Y-You're...?
I didn't fall in love with a bunch of pushovers.
Come on, Aru.
I'm sure they get the message.
Girls with glasses are quite delicate.
They can't help it sometimes.
W-What are you doing here?
But you know...
You make a girl with glasses cry,
there's blood to pay.
So you asked for this.
I'm gonna paint the town red with your guts!
That's Problem Solver 68!
Lost in the road, not knowing right from wrong.
Everything you try, ending in failure.
And even if you make it through,
it's just more hell you're walking into.
They're here!
So what?!
Your friend is in danger, isn't she?
Are you just going to sit there feeling sorry
while they take everything from you?
Is that really what you want?
Are you telling me that's the kind of people you are?
Damn you, Problem Solver!
You're nothing but dogs! How dare you turn on me!
Oh, shut up.
I prefer working with these girls.
That's all this is.
It's only natural for a villain to turn
on her employer, don't you think?
You guys...
You're right.
That's how a villain should be.
Of course. It's so simple!
We don't have time to be doubting ourselves!
Yeah! Who cares if we're unofficial?
None of that matters right now!
We save Hoshino.
That's all that matters.
You still waste my time with your pointless resistance?
How dare you -
How dare you do this to my precious students!
We'll be taking Hoshino back!
Don't screw with me!
You think you can just come out of
nowhere and start making demands?
Fine then, I have just the thing for you!
B-But sir, it's still a prototype!
It's too dangerous to deploy!
Silence!
I will teach them what it means to defy me!
Behold!
This exosuit is the pinnacle
of our company's technology!
Its armaments and armor are
forged from only the purest materials.
It is the cutting edge of weaponry!
My my, that's quite large.
W-W-What do we do?
This could get messy.
True, this won't be easy.
However...
That's if we assume
it's only the four of us against it, right?
Back us up.
You can do that, right?
Yeah.
In that case,
Alley-oop!
Can't dent it.
It's useless!
That's just cheating!
Would not recommend
taking a direct hit from that.
There has to be some way...
Bombs.
How many do you have left?
I'm down if you have a plan.
Don't worry.
I got this.
Honestly, I don't care how bad the odds are.
That's just how outlaws are, right?
You're wasting your time!
Go!
We should go, too!
You got it!
You thought you could flank us that easily?
You're in the way. Move, please!
Thanks!
Oh, no, um...
Come on, eyes forward! Let's go!
Right!
Dammit! Don't let them through!
What do we do? We can't just destroy the store.
Ta-da!
Is that a bomb?
Yeah! But it'll be fine!
Wow! That's a neat little trick!
I know, right?
Leave the rest to me.
Thank you!
Break a leg!
When will you learn that resistance is futile?!
Just a little more...
I don't know what it is you're plotting.
But I've had about enough of this little game.
So that's where you were hiding!
Serika!
Yeah!
Why you! Hold still!
It'll be dangerous.
I know.
But I can't always let other people protect me.
Go get him.
Yeah.
Be careful.
I've got your back!
You're dealing with me, now.
Why, you little...
It looks like they've started.
Well, then...
Shall we get started ourselves, then, Haruka?
Yes, let's.
Looks like Mutsuki and Haruka are doing fine.
Nice try.
It looks like you're set on getting in our way.
You're ruining the atmosphere.
Mind cutting that out?
Filthy rats!
Scurrying around in the dirt!
You should have just buried yourselves in the sand!
Your entire existence is an eyesore!
You call this cutting edge?
You little shit!
Did you really think you had me cornered?
Your puny form is too weak!
Just try and stop the 12,860 horsepower of this craft!
What the -
And there you go!
We did it!
Shiroko!
You've got some guts, not running
away after witnessing this firepower.
Save it for someone who cares.
Now if only you had the brains to match.
At least as much as that Hoshino,
or whatever her name was.
Why don't you just give up already?
He's not...
Shiroko! Five meters behind you!
Where do you think you're looking?
It's over!
Sensei!
Shiroko!
Hoshino...
It's not easy up front, huh.
What? How?
This can't be happening!
Shiroko!
Are you okay?
Yeah. No problem.
Thank goodness it worked.
Thanks, Ayane.
Nonomi and Serika, too.
All according to plan.
Still, cutting it a bit close there.
Well, I figured they of all people
would be able to pull off that much.
Mr. Chairman! Are you all right?
We need to get you to medical!
Why don't you just give up already?
I'm not done yet!
What? You really want to keep going?
Honestly, I'm fine with going for round two.
We're falling back. For now.
Regroup our forces!
Y-Yes, sir!
Fall back!
Chairman's orders! Fall back!
I say again, the chairman is ordering us to fall back!
Don't think this is over.
There'll be hell to pay, mark my words.
Hostile forces are retreating.
L-Looks like it's over.
Man, that's the first time I've ever heard
someone say "mark my words" in real life.
Great work, everyone.
It was a difficult situation,
but you did very well to get through it.
Yeah.
You girls, too.
You saved us back there.
Thank you, truly.
T-That was nothing.
After all, we're first-class outlaws.
Yeah, I saw you were all fired up from the beginning.
You don't have to tell them that!
Now, for the next part.
We're coming,
Hoshino.
What? Why?
Why did you attack Abydos?
I'm certain I don't know what you mean.
What is there to be confused about?
I will be sure to repay over half of the school's debt.
This was the promise that we made between us.
That aside...
With your withdrawal, there is no longer anyone
in the student council at Abydos High School.
It could hardly be considered a school at that point.
This whole situation with Abydos is
a mere preamble to the real event.
Miss Hoshino.
Our eyes were set on you from the start.
We needed you to sign that contract
and surrender all of your rights to us.
And to reach that end, we cooperated
with the Kaiser Corporation.
It's as simple as that.
I do apologize for any misunderstanding.
But I was never a member of that petty corporation.
You've attained the strongest Mystic in Kivotos.
I could never waste your potential
on mere mercenary work.
This fascinating experiment here
is what we've yearned to witness.
That's all there is to it.
I see.
So once again...
I've been tricked by an adult.
I'm sorry, everyone.
It's all my fault.
Shiroko.
Nonomi.
Serika.
Ayane.
Sensei.
Yume.
I'm sorry.