Sorry I'm⋯
Huh?
Am I the first to arrive?
(To the Abydos
Foreclosure Task Force)
(To the Abydos Foreclosure
Task Force) What is this?
(To the Abydos
Foreclosure Task Force)
It can't be!
- Hi, Ayane!
- Why?
(Withdrawal Application I am withdrawing
from the student bo dy for personal reasons,)
(Withdrawal Application I am withdrawing from the
student bo dy for personal reasons,) What's going on?!
(Withdrawal Application I am withdrawing
from the student bo dy for personal reasons,)
(Third Year
Takanashi Hoshino)
The sky blue archive!
I pedal on my bike seeking new sights
We'll break the monotony,
no longer trapped in place
Daydreaming on the rooftop,
gazing at a sky so blue
Those clouds like whales are always changing
We'll embrace a past that can't be altered
Sharing juice in this world made of sand
Is a taste so divine
If I were here alone, here without all of you
I couldn't laugh, I couldn't cry
A fateful coterie
Even if the world's memories blow away
like grains of sand one day
The sky, sea, wind, and you,
our youth will never end
It's easy to see why we protect what we do
Because this is the only place where we belong
(Abydos Foreclosure Task Force)
(Abydos Foreclosure Task Force) “To
the Abydos Foreclosure Task Force,"
"First of all,”
forgive me for doing this
with a letter
It felt more old-fashioned,
which suits me perfectly
The truth is, a recruiter has been
after me for a while now
Become a Kaiser PMC mercenary for life
in exchange for Abydos' debt
being paid off
That's the long and short of it
They must value the skills of
a wily old veteran like me
I know I talked a big game
at the Black Market
(Contract Agreement) I know I
talked a big game at the Black Market
(Contract Agreement)
I'm sorry I couldn't
keep my word
But things should be easier
for the Foreclosure Task Force now⋯
Let me take responsibility⋯
⋯as the final member
of the Abydos Student Council
So this is goodbye
"Sensei,"
- "To be honest⋯"
- To be honest,
I've never liked adults
When Shiroko carried
you in on her back,
I couldn't help but think
you were damn useless
But in the end,
you won those kids over
and earned their trust
So I'm leaving things
in your care now
Everyone believes in you⋯
and that has to be enough
And ever since I met
an adult like you,
I really⋯
Well, some things are
better left unsaid
Shiroko, Nonomi
Serika, Ayane
I'm counting on you
Please look after our school
It may be half-buried in sand,
but it's the only place
(964,217,852 yen until we're fully
repaid! We've got this!) that matters to me
(964,217,852 yen until we're fully repaid!
We've got this!)
Also, if we ever end up
facing each other as enemies,
then⋯
Don't hesitate to destroy my halo
Please
What is this?!
How can she just give up?
I won't accept this!
Shiroko!
I'll go! We need to
rescue her!
Shiroko, hold on!
She's right
Let's assess the situation
But Hoshino⋯
Keep firing!
Pacify this district!
The Abydos Student Council
has disbanded!
Which means that Abydos High School
belongs to the Kaiser Corporation!
An army of Kaiser PMC soldiers is invading!
They're attacking the
district indiscriminately!
Why now, of all times?
We have to stop them
But without Hoshino⋯
Hold on a minute, everyone
Evacuating the citizens
has to be our first priority
How cruel
- Are you hurt?
- J-Just a little
Why are they attacking us?
We're still investigating
the situation ourselves
Abydos Foreclosure Task Force
spotted! This way!
- Shiroko!
- Yeah!
Everyone, evacuate this area!
O-Okay!
Shiroko!
This is it!
What are you doing?
- You take that side!
- Okay
- Damn it!
- They're tough!
- Nonomi!
- Got it!
Are you all right?
Yeah, I'm fine
But⋯
They just keep coming
It's all down to us
My, have you really
come out to greet me?
You saved me the trouble
of visiting
Abydos High School myself
Why is your corporation
attacking the city?
You have no right
regardless of how much
land you own!
And the school building is
still Abydos property!
You're breaking the law!
The General Student Council
won't overlook this!
Where is Hoshino?
Give her back to us!
I have no idea what
you're talking about
But the General Student Council?
Don't make me laugh
Call them all you want
How many times
have you requested
their assistance?
Did they even once help
with your debt?
Now you understand
it doesn't matter how much you struggle
Nothing will change
And the final member of
the Abydos Student Council,
Takanashi Hoshino,
has dropped out
Which means your student council
no longer exists
You are nothing now
What are you talking about?!
Even if the student council disbands,
Abydos has the Foreclosure Task Force!
We're right here!
The Foreclosure Task Force⋯
isn't an authorized club
- What?
- Ayane?
The Student Council was long gone
by the time the task force
was created
She's right
You're an unauthorized club
without official documentation
You may as well be ghosts
But look on the bright side
With Abydos High School dead,
you're finally free from
all that tedious debt
No way⋯
But that would mean all the
hard work we've done⋯
You actually intended to work
for hundreds of years to
pay off that debt?
You can't possibly be so deluded
I thought you only
kept up appearances
because you were embarrassed
to admit the truth
Did you really exhaust yourselves
to repay that debt?
Why bother?
Shut your mouth!
I'll shoot
If we fight⋯what difference
will it make?
Ayane?
Even if we win somehow⋯
What are we supposed
to do next?
And even if we get
the school back,
it won't erase our debt⋯
The land that's been sold
isn't coming back
Without Hoshino
or the Student Council⋯
What can an
unofficial club like ours
hope to do?
Ayane⋯
Why⋯
Why are we always alone?
Hoshino⋯
What are we supposed to do?
Massive explosion detected to the north!
Our reinforcements from Bravo Squad
were caught in the blast!
What?!
Mike Squad was hit in the east!
Massive C4 explosion detected!
What's happening?!
Come on, I can't believe my ears!
What are you idiots doing?
An eye for an eye,
a tooth for a tooth
Forsake mercy
and walk the path of chaos
Wasn't that the motto
of the Masked Swimsuit Gang?
You guys are⋯
How am I supposed to admire you
after that pathetic display?
Sheesh, Aru,
lighten up a little
Little Miss Four-Eyes
Is the anxious type
She can't help it
What are you doing here?
Making adorable Miss Four-Eyes cry
Is a pretty serious crime
Which is why⋯
⋯I'm gonna rip you guys apart!
It's Problem Solver 68!
When there's no
finish line in sight,
and everything you do
ends in failure⋯
And you know that tomorrow
will only bring you more
hardship and hard times⋯
Finally
Well who cares?!
Are you really going to
let such useless feelings
stop you from rescuing
your friend?!
If you're okay with
losing everything,
you're all even stupider
than you look!
Damn you Problem Solver dogs!
You dare bite at the hand
that feeds you?!
Shut up!
Working with these kids is way better
than taking your orders!
Villains are supposed to stab their
employers in the back, you know?
You all⋯
Yeah, you're right
That's what villains do
That was just what we needed
We can't stand around here
Who cares if we're
unauthorized or whatever?
Whether we're above board
or not doesn't matter
We need to save Hoshino
Who cares about anything else?
You! It's useless to resist!
How dare you attack my students!
We're taking Hoshino back
Don't be ridiculous!
You're just some teacher!
You don't have the right to⋯
This calls for emergency measures
But sir, the prototype's untested!
- Using it is too risky—
- I don't care!
I'll force them to accept their bitter end
Behold!
My cutting-edge exosuit,
the pinnacle of our battle tech!
Its high-purity armor and
powerful actuators
make it the ultimate weapon!
Wow, it's gigantic!
What should we do?
That looks tough
Yeah, it's not going down easy
Or at least⋯
It wouldn't if there were
only four of us
Try to keep up
You can do that, right?
Yeah
All right, let's go!
Not a scratch
You can't stop me!
What an insane
amount of power⋯
A direct hit
would be devastating
We need another way⋯
Explosives
How many do you have left?
Enough to give us a chance, maybe
Then we've got this, Trust me
I'll try anything, no matter
how long the odds!
That's what it means
to be an outlaw!
Children, What a pathetic attack!
Go!
- Let's move
- Okay!
Sneaking away? It's too late!
You're in the way,
SO move aside!
- Thanks
- N-No problem
Hey:-
Just keep looking forward,
all right?
Y-Yeah!
Damn it, Stop them!
What should we do?
A fight here would destroy the store
Ta-da!
A grenade?
Yeah, but don't worry!
Amazing! How fun!
Isn't it?
- Leave them to me
- Thanks!
Do your best!
You brats really
don't give up, do you?
Only a little longer⋯
I don't care what you're up to
It's time to end this
There you are!
- Serika!
- Yeah!
Damn it, they're running!
This seems dangerous
Well⋯
I can't sit by and
let others protect me
- Go for it!
- Yeah
- Be careful
- I'll cover you!
I'm your opponent
You!
Looks like it's started
In that case,
let's handle these guys, Haruka
Yes, let's sweep them away
Looks like Mutsuki and
Haruka are doing fine
Not going to happen
You're all so eager to
interfere with our work
You think you buzzkills
can stop us?
Stop dodging, you rats!
Get back in your hole!
Ugh, what a nuisance!
This is your ultimate weapon?
Don't make me laugh!
You think you've won?
That puny body can't stop
this 12,860-horsepower machine!
Th-This—
Mission accomplished!
Got him
Shiroko!
Still willing to fight
after that attack?
You're brave⋯for a rat
Choke on your compliments
You would live longer
if you were smart,
like Hoshino
Just give up already!
No way⋯
Shiroko, five meters back!
You dare look away?!
This ends now!
Sensei!
Shiroko!
Hoshino
Protecting the front line is tough
Wh-What?!
How could this be?!
- Shiroko!
- Are you okay?
Yeah, no big deal
I'm glad we're all safe
Thanks Ayane,
Nonomi, Serika
We pulled off our plan
Wasn't that a bit much?
Well, they're no outlaws,
but I figured they could handle it
Director, can you stand?!
The medical team is—
You should just give it up
I still--
What, you want to keep going?
We can beat you up some more,
if you insist!
Retreat for now
Regroup our soldiers!
- Yes, sir!
- Everyone, pull back!
The director has ordered a retreat!
I repeat, the director
orders you to retreat!
This isn't over⋯
We'll repay this defeat tenfold
They're withdrawing⋯
We did it
That's the first time
I've heard someone
actually say "This isn't over,”
Good job, everyone
That was a tough battle,
but you all fought well
Yeah
Thanks, Problem Solver 68,
for such timely assistance
Ah, it's nothing, really
No matter what anyone says,
we're hard boiled outlaws
Aru was super nervous
from the start, though
Don't tell them that!
Then, our next step⋯
- Yup!
- Yeah!
Wait for us,
Hoshino
Why⋯?
Why are you attacking Abydos?!
What's the matter, Hoshino?
I kept my word
Your former school's debt has been settled,
exactly as promised
However⋯
Now that you've dropped out,
Abydos no longer has
an official Student Council
Unfortunately, that means
the school must close
Of course, Abydos
has always been
a secondary concern
Hoshino
You have been our prime objective
from the start
Having you sign that contract,
coercing you into signing away
your rights⋯
We only worked with the Kaiser Corporation⋯
because our interests aligned
My apologies if you misunderstood
But I was never part
of such a trifling company
I didn't claim the most promising
Mystic in Kivotos
just to waste her as a
mercenary soldier
You'll be helping us with
something more important
An experiment we've
truly longed to run
Welcome to your new life
Now I get it
I was being manipulated
by adults yet again
I'm sorry, everyone
This is my fault
Shiroko, Nonomi
Serika, Ayane
Sensei⋯
⋯Yume
I'm sorry