Come on, hurry up!
Hold on, Serika!
My, my.
Look how excited they are.
Hey, watch your step.
I know, I know.
Let's go join them.
Yeah.
Hey, Ayane, what should we
look at first when we get there?
Good question. I think I'd like
to go see the sea turtles.
Huh? Wouldn't you normally start with the fish?
Back me up here, you two.
You have a point.
Let's start with the seahorses then.
That's also weirdly specific...
Does sound like something she'd like.
I agree.
Wow! Just look at this place!
It's like we're in the middle of the ocean!
Hey, come on, there's sharks over there!
Hey, be careful you don't trip and fall.
This aquarium is so big!
We may not be able to see everything.
What? Is it that big?
It seems like in addition to the fish tanks,
the penguin area, and the dolphin show,
they also offer a variety of other attractions and shops!
That's a lot. Do we try to rush through all of them?
Now, now, the aquarium isn't gonna run away.
We can always come back
another time if we have to.
I'm glad to see all you're all having fun.
Yeah!
Yes!
It keeps opening its mouth!
Maybe that's how it breathes?
Probably.
I never really thought about it,
but how does it breathe underwater?
Fish have a special organ that
lets them absorb oxygen from water.
You've heard of gills, right?
Water goes in through their mouths
and exits after passing over their gills.
That's how fish acquire oxygen
and expel carbon dioxide.
In a sense, they breathe just like we do.
We may look different on the outside,
but inside, we're built the same.
Well, we're ignoring animals like whales
that actually hold their breath while underwater.
But that doesn't really count.
Whales are mammals, not fish.
Why's everyone gone all quiet?
Oh, sorry. I was just a little surprised.
You actually said something smart for once.
Didn't expect that.
Hey, rude!
Wow, you're quite the encyclopedia.
When it comes to fish, she really is.
Shucks, you're making me blush.
Aw, yeah! I love jellyfish!
Me, too! The way they glow is so cute!
They aren't shining lights
on them or anything, right?
Nope. They glow all on their own!
That's curious.
Wouldn't glowing in the middle of the ocean
just make it easier to be eaten?
Well, fancy details aside,
some of them use light to protect themselves.
They can even use it as a weapon of sorts.
Come on, let's go look at
the tropical fish next, pretty please?
It looks like they have a great selection!
Good idea. Let's go check it out!
Ooh! Look at that!
Look at those ones! Don't they look just adorable?
Yummy!
Huh?
No way! Are you out of your mind?
But look at how plump they are!
They're great to look at and even better to eat!
That's crazy talk!
You agree with me, right, Ayane?
I, um, probably wouldn't think to eat them, myself.
I mean, they're so cute.
But think about it this way, Ayane.
If we could eat these fish,
we'd save on food.
T-True...
Oh, come on, Shiroko, not you too!
What do you think, Nonomi?
Who, me?
I think they're cute, of course!
Nonomi!
But I also think they look quite tasty!
Sorry for the wait, girls.
What are you all chatting about?
Hey, Serika, at this point,
why don't we let him decide?
Good idea, Hoshino.
Decide what?
Teacher, we have a question about the tropical fish.
They look cute, right?
They look tasty, right?
You agree with me, right?
Uh, well...
Personally...
I think all of you look much cuter?
Yeah, no. Just... no.
This is why people make fun of you, Teach.
S-Sorry! Let me try that again, please?
That fish looks like an old man!
It must be Hoshino's spirit animal!
What? It doesn't match her at all.
If I had to pick a spirit animal for her,
I'd pick something like a jellyfish.
She's always so laid-back and squishy.
You think so?
What would you pick, Nonomi?
Hmm, let's see...
If I had to pick one...
Maybe a penguin?
Huh? Really?
Yes, I think they're quite similar!
Like how cute they are when they waddle their feet!
Did you see that?
Yeah! It just jumped higher than our heads!
Hey, look, does that mean
they'll jump even higher next?
The teacher looks like he's having fun.
Yes, he's acting almost like a child!
Look! They're gonna do something!
Wow, what a show!
Yeah.
Hey, Hoshino.
Can I have a word?
What's up, Shiroko?
You wanted to talk with me privately?
Oh! Is this the part where you reveal
your undying love for me?!
No. It isn't.
Aw, bummer.
By the way, while we were
watching that show, I was thinking.
You're kind of like a dolphin, Shiroko.
What do you mean?
Well, the others were talking about
what animal I reminded them of earlier.
And I was thinking, you're cute and real sporty.
Kind of like a dolphin, y'know?
I guess.
Totally!
What animal does li'l ol' me remind you of the most?
A whale.
What? No way. I'm too tiny!
That's a bit of a stretch.
Not really.
I think you're similar.
Like how they can swim while sleeping.
Or how you can only see a part of them, even up close.
And...
How they're always holding their breath.
Back then, you said you had been taking a nap.
But that wasn't true, was it?
Shiroko?
Is there anything I can do to help?
I just feel like something has been weighing you down.
Something you don't want to share.
I want to help you however I can.
Just like you helped me once.
You're a sweet kid, Shiroko.
Hoshino?
But you know, that's exactly why...
I wuv you so much!
Gosh, you make me so happy!
I'm lucky to have you in my class.
Looks like you girls are getting along well.
Shiroko was just revealing
how much she loves me!
Oh, my!
Ayane, let's go to the feeding area next.
Good idea. I wonder what fish they're feeding there.
That's pretty cute.
Aren't you going to get one?
Oh, uh, I mean,
I think I'm a little old for a plushie.
Not at all!
Look at this beauty!
I wonder if we can even bring him back with us.
Even if you did buy it, where would you put it?
True.
I'm sure Teach would figure something out.
Doesn't Hoshino look
just adorbs with that huge whale?
Did you find anything you like, Shiroko?
Well...
I thought this was cute.
That's a surprisingly normal choice,
coming from you.
But it probably costs a good bit.
Eh, you don't have to worry about that part.
Right, Teacher?
Huh? Oh, uh, yeah...
But you know, we could go for
something smaller, like a keychain...
It's fine, right, Teach?
Well, I mean...
Teacher?
O-Of course!
Sweet!
Thank you, Teacher.
I'm happy if you're happy.
Hey, now that we're all here, let's take a picture!
Great idea.
I'm down.
In that case, I'll take the photo,
so go line up over there.
Huh? Aren't you joining us?
Oh, no. It's okay.
Not happening.
What are you getting shy about now?
You're part of the gang now, Teacher.
We can't leave you out of this, now!
Well, I guess, but...
Would you like me to take it for you?
Yuuka!
Fancy meeting you here, Teacher.
Thank you again for your help the other day.
It's been a while.
How have you been?
I've been well, thank you.
I thought I might take the opportunity
to discuss something with you.
But it seems it would be better
to save it for another time.
If you'd like, we can take the photo for you.
Are you sure?
I'll gladly take you up on that.
Is everyone ready?
Ready!
All right, here we go.
Say "cheese"!
These are the kind of moments
they deserve to have more of.
I hope I'm just imagining things.
The way I am now...
Am I doing well in your stead,
Yume?
Hoshino?
Was it just my imagination?
Wasn't that...
Is this really Hoshino?
She looks gorgeous in profile.
She's gorgeous normally.
Oh, right! Why don't I send this
in the Momotalk group chat?
We should all upload the photos we took.
Good morning.
If you're looking for Hoshino,
she's not here yet.
I'm sure she's off napping somewhere again.
I see.
Could you also send over
the photos you took yesterday?
Sure.
That reminds me, I hadn't sent
anything besides the group photo.
Whoa, where did you take this?
There was a specimen area.
They said we could pick them up, so...
You look like you're posing with the day's catch!
I feel like Shiroko would be pretty good at fishing.
I guess I might try it out if we get the chance.
Maybe we should go to the actual ocean next time.
That underwater tunnel was really cool, too.
I'd love to go diving or something one day.
I agree. If that happens,
we should all go together again.
Oh, in that case...
Heya, gang. How's it hanging?
You're late!
Sorry, sorry.
I was just so comfy in my bed,
I didn't wanna move.
So, what's everyone up to?
We were looking at the photos
from yesterday's aquarium trip.
Ooh, nice!
Let me in on the fun, too!
Didn't you take any pictures, Hoshino?
At my age, it's hard to keep up
with all this fancy technology.
Fancy technology?
Don't worry!
I made sure to take plenty of pics
of both you and everyone else!
Nice thinking, Nonomi!
Is what I'd like to say, but I knew
you'd be too busy taking pics of us,
so I made sure to take plenty of you as well!
I also took pictures of you!
Serika, Ayane...
Thank you!
You're both so thoughtful! I'm touched!
Hey, Shiroko. Aren't you going to join them?
Actually...
Of course, I love you two as well!
Well then, everyone, that's it
for today's regular meeting.
Got it.
Great!
See you tomorrow.
I'm also heading home now.
I'll pay Teacher a visit before heading back.
Okay.
I think I'll go home and have a nice snooze.
Hoshino.
Hm? What's up?
Where were you this morning?
I already told you, didn't I?
I didn't go anywhere. I just overslept, that's all.
Really?
What's the matter, Shiroko?
Did something happen?
Well...
I thought I saw you in town this morning.
I'm sure you had the wrong person.
There's plenty of girls who look just like me.
Maybe you were so tired from yesterday
you started seeing things?
Let's take it easy for today and go home.
Hoshino.
You're hiding something from—
Huh? You took pictures of me, too?
Yes! I'll send them over along with everyone else's.
Oh, uh, thanks.
Owwie...
You're hurting me, Shiroko.
Hoshino, what is this?
It's just a form.
It doesn't mean anything yet, so relax.
As if I can relax.
What do you mean, "yet"?
How should I put this...
Hoshino? Shiroko?
What's going on, you two?
We're... I mean...
What on earth happened?
Shiroko?
I'm sorry, but please leave us alone.
I'm afraid that's a no.
There's no keeping secrets in the Task Force.
After all, we're all in this together, as a team!
But—
Sorry about that.
It's really no big deal, so no worries.
Shiroko's such a worrywart.
But I really do appreciate the thought, honest.
Wait, Hoshino, I'm not done—
Shiroko.
I don't know what happened between you two,
but maybe you should leave her alone for a while.
But Hoshino's—
Everyone has things they'd rather not talk about.
Hoshino...
Thank you, Shiroko.
But I have to do this.
So, the time has finally come.
Remember, this is the point of no return.
Once we move forward with this,
there's no going back.
Are you okay, Shiroko?
Yeah, I've calmed down a little.
Teacher, look at this.
What is it?
Oh...
Hoshino is hiding something from us.
But I couldn't...
I don't think it's that Hoshino doesn't trust you.
Could you leave this to me for now?
I want to help her, too.
If you say so, Teacher...
I'm sure there are things she can't tell you
because she trusts and cares about you.
You're right.
Thank you, Teacher.