Hurry, hurry!
Wait for me, Serika!
My, my, They sure are excited
Hey! Be careful!
I know! Don't worry!
- Shall we go too?
- Yeah
What do you want to see first, Ayane?
Let's see⋯Maybe the sea turtles?
Huh? Most people go for fish first!
Right, Shiroko? Hoshino?
Actually I think you're right
- Then, let's do the seahorses
- That's weird too
- Just like Shiroko though!
- Definitely!
The sky blue archive!
I pedal on my bike seeking new sights
We'll break the monotony,
no longer trapped in place
Daydreaming on the rooftop,
gazing at a sky so blue
Those clouds like whales are always changing
We'll embrace a past that can't be altered
Sharing juice in this world made of sand
Is a taste so divine
If I were here alone, here without all of you
I couldn't laugh, I couldn't cry
A fateful coterie
Even if the world's memories blow away
like grains of sand one day
The sky, sea, wind, and you,
our youth will never end
It's easy to see why we protect what we do
Because this is the only place where we belong
So cool! Awesome!
It's like we're under the seal
C'mon, there's sharks over there!
Hey! Careful not to trip!
This aquarium is super big
It'd be hard to see everything in one day
Really? It's that big?
She's right⋯
On top of the penguin and
dolphin areas,
there are all kinds of rides
and exhibits here!
What should we do?
Go through everything super fast?
Whoa there, it's fine to take our time
She's right, We can always
come back, after all
Heehee, I'm glad everyone's
having so much fun!
- Yup!
- Yeah!
Look at it gulping!
- Is it breathing?
- Probably
Now that you mention it,
how do fish breathe underwater?
Fish have special organs
that extract oxygen from the water
You've heard of gills, right?
Water goes in their mouth
and they extract the oxygen
through their gills
They take in oxygen and
then expel carbon dioxide
In that sense, fish aren't
so different from us
We look different
on the outside,
but we're similar on the inside
Well, there are creatures like whales
that just hold their breath while
they dive underwater, though
Oh, but just to clarify,
whales aren't fish
They're mammals!
What's wrong?
Have you all gone mute?
No, it's just⋯
I was taken aback, I guess?
Hoshino started spouting
some smart people stuff
- Unexpected
- What do you mean?!
Impressive! You really know your stuff
Hoshino knows everything
there is to know about fish
I wouldn't go that far
Jellyfish really are the best!
I agree! Their little glow is so cute!
It's not that they're
reflecting light, right?
No, they glow by themselves
Fascinating
But if they glow in the ocean,
isn't it easy for other fish to catch them?
Well, that's a bit complicated,
but sometimes their
light actually protects them!
They even use it to scare off enemies
Hey, hey! Let's go to the tropical fish now!
I heard they have lots of different species!
That sounds great, Let's go!
Oh, cool!
Look at these guys
Don't they look⋯
- Cute
- Tasty
How could you say that?!
Are you serious, Hoshino?
They just look so meaty!
And I bet they taste even
better than they look!
Absolutely not! Right, Ayane?
I-I wouldn't want to eat them either
They're cute⋯
Think about it, Ayane
If we ate them,
we'd save on food costs
Th-That's true
What the heck!
That's barbaric, Shiroko!
What about you, Nonomi?
Me?
They're adorable, of course!
Nonomi!
But they do look tasty too
Everyone! Did you wait long?
What's all the commotion about?
- Serika
- Yeah
Should we make Sensei decide?
We should, Hoshino
Decide what?
You see, Sensei
It's about these tropical fish here
- They look tasty, right?
- They look cute, right?
- Which is it, Sensei?
Ah, that's⋯
I, um⋯
Y-You guys⋯are the cute ones⋯?
He's no good
She's right, Sensei
Sorry! Let me try again!
This one's called "Old Timer"!
It's just like Hoshino!
What? Not at all
When I imagine it,
Hoshino is rather like a jellyfish
Always relaxed and such
Really? What about you, Nonomi?
Well⋯
In my opinion,
maybe⋯a penguin?
You think so?
Yes! There's something similar about them
Especially their cute little mannerisms!
- That jump was amazing!
- Yeah
The trajectory was well above our heads!
Hey, look! They're gonna
jump even higher!
Sensei's having fun
Yes! He's like a little kid
Guys, there they go again!
- Wow, How impressive!
- Yeah
- Hey, Hoshino
- Huh?
Do you have a moment?
What's up, Shiroko?
You wanted some
one-on-one time, huh?
Oh! Are you trying to
profess your love?
No, Nothing like that
What a shame
You know, I was thinking
earlier during the show
that Shiroko really
reminds me of a dolphin
What do you mean?
Well, Nonomi and the others were
guessing what animal I look most like
You're so cute and athletic,
so I was like, a dolphin!
- Is that so?
- Heck yes!
What would you
pick for me, Shiroko?
Whale
Wait, wait, But I'm so small!
Isn't that totally off?
Not at all
You're like a whale
Swimming while asleep
It's impossible to see all of you,
no matter how close we get
And...
You're always holding your breath
You said you were
napping the other day,
but you were lying, weren't you?
Shiroko
Is there anything I can do?
Eh?
You're always⋯
shouldering the heavy burdens on your own
I want to help you with those burdens,
just like you did for me
You really are kind, Shiroko
Hoshino
But your kindness⋯
might make this
old-timer fall for you!
I'm so blessed⋯
to have such a wonderful junior
You two get along so well
Shiroko professed her love for me
Oh my!
Let's go to the feeding area now, Ayane!
Ah, yes! Which fish⋯
That's cute
Are you going to buy it?
Oh? Well--
It's kinda childish⋯
Not at all
This one's humongous!
Am I gonna be able to carry it to the club room?
More importantly, where
would you put it?!
- Good point
- Sensei will figure it out
Hoshino and the whale are so cute together
Do you see anything
you like, Shiroko?
Well⋯
This is cute
Shiroko's pick is a little plain, no?
Maybe she's worried about money?
Well, you don't have to
worry about that
Right, Sensei?
Um, you're right
How about a little keychain, though?
It's okay, right? Sensei?
Y-Yeah, but⋯
Seeenseiii
O-Of course
Great!
Thanks, Sensei
As long as everyone's happy
Hey! Let's take a group picture
since we're all here!
- That sounds good!
- Let's
I can take it for you,
so stand right there
Huh? Shouldn't Sensei
be in it as well?
- No, I⋯
- That won't do
Why're you acting all shy now?
You belong in the picture as well!
You're gonna feel
left out if you don't!
But still⋯
Do you want me to take it for you?
Yuuka!
What a coincidence, Sensei
Thank you again for last time
It's been a while!
Have you been well?
Yes! We owe you
Since you're here, there's
something I need to tell you⋯
Actually, maybe next time
Um, would you like us
to take your picture?
Oh! Are you sure?
In that case, yes please!
Everyone! Are you ready?
- Yes!
- Yeah
Okay, Here we go!
Say cheese!
I hope we have many
more moments like this
So why can't I shake this feeling⋯?
Am I⋯
living up to your legacy?
Yume
Hoshino?
Am I imagining things?
Just now...
(Abydos Foreclosure Task Force)
Are you sure this is Hoshino?!
Her side profile!
What a nice picture
She's naturally pretty!
Oh! We never take pictures
Should we post these
to our MomoTalk group chat?
That way everybody
could upload their pictures!
Good morning
Mm, Good morning
You looking for Hoshino?
She's not here yet
I bet she's passed out somewhere
Is that so?
Shiroko! Would you mind sharing
your pictures from yesterday?
Sure
Come to think of it, we only
posted the group picture
Where was this?
At the specimen exhibit
They said I could touch it
The way you're holding
it makes it seem like
you caught the starfish yourself
If anyone could do it,
it'd be Shiroko
I have always wanted to try fishing
Perhaps we can take a trip
out to the sea next time
I thought the underwater
tunnel was super cool!
It made me want to try out diving!
Okay! Then let's make
that happen next time
Then⋯
Hey, hey! Didja all sleep well?
You're late, Hoshino!
Aw, sorry!
I was so tired and just so comfy
I couldn't get out of bed!
Anyways! What're we up to?
We're looking at all
our aquarium pictures
Ooh, fun!
I wanna see!
Didn't you take any pictures, Hoshino?
This old-timer can't handle all the
newfangled technology these days
Is it that complicated⋯?
Don't worry
I took lots of pics of Hoshino
and everyone else
You always do this, Nonomi!
Is what I'd normally say,
but I saw you were taking
pics of everyone but yourself,
so I took a bunch of you!
I also took a lot
of you, Nonomi
Serika! Ayane!
Thank you so much
I'm delighted you care
about me that much
Hey, Shiroko, you
don't want to join?
Ah, I—
Of course you two are included!
(Foreclosure Task Force
Daily Meeting)
Daily Meeting) Well, everyone,
Well, everyone,
today's daily meeting is adjourned
-Yes
- Okay
See you tomorrow
We're heading out first
I'll say goodbye to Sensei before I leave
Okay
Time for me to get more shut-eye too
Hoshino
Hm? What's up?
Where were you this morning?
I already told you!
I wasn't anywhere, I just overslept
Really?
What's wrong, Shiroko?
- Is something bothering you?
- Yeah
I swear I saw you
downtown this morning
You probably saw someone else!
There are lots of girls
that look like me, after all
You gotta be real tired to mistake
me for someone else, Shiroko!
- Go take a nap—
- Hoshino!
Are you hiding something?
(Sensei's Room)
What? My pictures?
Yes! So I can send
them to the others!
Oh, thank you
Owww
That hurts, Shiroko
What is this? Hoshino!
Just some piece of paper
Don't worry about it
It's nothing for now
You expect me to not worry?
And what do you mean "for now"?
Well, what I mean is⋯
Hoshino! Shiroko!
What're you two doing?
It's that⋯
What on earth is happening?
Shiroko
Sorry, Can we have a moment?
That's impossible!
There's no secrets
between the members of
the Foreclosure Task Force
We're all in this together,
no matter what
- But—
- My bad, my bad!
It's okay, It's not a big
deal in the slightest
Shiroko worries too much
Well, I really appreciate
the concern though
Wait, Hoshino
We didn't finish—
Shiroko
I don't know what happened,
but I think it'd be best
to give her some space
But Hoshino⋯
Everyone has some things
they'd rather not talk about
Hoshino
Thank you, Shiroko
Regardless, I⋯
The time has come
There'll be no going back after this
You won't be able to
stop halfway, after all
I'll take a window seat on this journey to find
the place where my heart belongs
So I can see beyond this sorrow chasing me
We were losing track of time without ever knowing why
With all those laughs we shared⋯
Even if⋯those moments were just ordinary
Those days⋯
One more time, one time more,
Knowing they won't come around again!
If only I could stay as resolute and beautiful
As the moon hanging in the bright noon sky
Would that let me finally forgive
All those regrets we made so willfully?
We only recognize the important things
Once they're gone and lost out of sight
We stretch up to the moon in the bright noon sky
Even though it will always be beyond our reach
Oh, those unforgettable, beautiful days⋯
Are you okay, Shiroko?
Yeah, I've calmed down a bit
Sensei, this
What is it?
(Withdrawal Form)
This is⋯
Hoshino is hiding
something from us
But I⋯
It's not that
Hoshino doesn't trust you
Are you okay with me handling this?
I want to help Hoshino too
If you say so, Sensei
Sometimes, the closer you are,
the more you trust each other,
the harder it is to speak up
Yeah
Thank you, Sensei